<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[OV]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>OV</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 04:42:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 04:42:53 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[HRT]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>HRT is currently 50mg Casodex (Bica) and 2x2mg daily Estrofem (Estradiol).<br>HRT Status:<br>
<br>Ordered
<br>Paid
<br>Shipped
<br>Picked up
<br>Treatment started
<br>Bloodwork Status:<br>
<br>Researched
<br>Scheduled
<br>Harvested
<br>Results Available
<br>"Official" HRT Path:<br>
<br>Researched

<br>There is a slightly expensive remote EU clinic that seems quite intent on giving good service to transpeople that An needs to find again and the confirm that they can actually give prescriptions.


<br>Scheduled
<br>An would maybe like testosterone cream for her genitals at some point. This is mostly out of the desire to maintain function.<br>Everything below this line is stale now.<br><br>This is going to be a little messy, but I need to track the details in case I get interrupted on this task, so I can pick it back up ASAP.<br>Meds:<br>
<br>Estradiol 

<br>Probably sublingual estradiol, estrofem. 2mg twice daily


<br>Bica

<br>Casodex 50mg


<br>Strategy is to DIY first and probably get it officially later.<br>After looking at:<br>
<br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://diyhrt.market/stores/" target="_blank">https://diyhrt.market/stores/</a>
<br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://hrtcafe.net/#pharmaceutical-vendors" target="_blank">https://hrtcafe.net/#pharmaceutical-vendors</a>
<br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://hrt.coffee/pills/" target="_blank">https://hrt.coffee/pills/</a>
<br>The best bet is to use a pharmacy inside the EU. It would be best if they shipped without going through the post office system, but I don't seem to get a choice here.<br>mindnbody.store looks like... almost my only option. Delivery takes 2 to 6 weeks. Their reputation seems alright. My main concern is the package being opened up at the post office.<br>Another complication is that the post office system is so stupid that if the package says its for X address, then it has to corroborate with the address on your ID.<br>My ID has the address of my grandmother's residence (who lives about 20m away).<br>If I use my ID address and...<br>
...the seller actually uses a courier, then the package ends up at my grandmother's residence, lol.<br>
...the seller uses the post office, then the pacakge ends up at a post office and I can pick it up.<br>One option I have for possibly improving this disaster is to set a postal box at the post office. I think this also makes it less likely for the package to be opened:<br>
<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.posta-romana.ro/a249/servicii-destinatari/casute-postale/inchiriere/abonament-casuta-postala-pf.html" target="_blank">https://www.posta-romana.ro/a249/servicii-destinatari/casute-postale/inchiriere/abonament-casuta-postala-pf.html</a><br>There's no obvious way to know which postal office has free boxes. All I can do is sign the paper and then visit them to check.<br>Ordering to my ID address also can result in me not getting told about my package arriving. There's two ways of mitigating this:<br>
<br>Hoping they SMS me like usual
<br>Checking the tracking number every single day, provided they actually give one.
<br>I'm not even giving that much of a shit about stealth right now. As long as it's in a non-transparent package, I'll just tell my parents this is something private.<br><br>There was an online website that seemed to be really intent on getting EU people diagnosed as trans. But I'm not 100% sure if they can give me a prescription. But it's worth following up after ordering DIY. Multi-pronged strategy baby!!]]></description><link>logistics\minutiae\hrt.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Minutiae/HRT.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 11:12:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[abortive note analyzing dignity]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>what is dignity?<br>dignity is an ego defense. even if one faces death, they can face it with dignity. therefore dignity serves to protect the ego even at the cost of other things. dignity contains the power of serenity in the face of adversity. dignity is a useful signal to others about one's state of mind.<br>externally, dignity is the concept that people should be treated in some positive ways because of their inherent humanity. it relates to a sense of unalienable rights.<br>dignity in one's proper role can be useful, but in my case it is detrimental to what i am supposed to achieve. i have never let go of my dignity for someone. i did not value them highly enough, i was never desperate enough, i never endorsed going into that state.<br>this relates to how i've been jealous of people having ugly loud breakdowns, that impose things on others. they surrender their dignity in favor of total belief in the importance and totality of the thing that is giving them a breakdown. i've always wanted that level of "license".<br>regardless, it begs the question of why don't i just grovel by nature. what's holding me back?<br>
<br>
]]></description><link>notes\abortive-note-analyzing-dignity.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/abortive note analyzing dignity.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:47:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[running away ideation]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>and yeah no, i would never go back to being very close to jen. i don't have anyone i can build a future with besides you, may. when i ideate about leaving it's about testing my luck finding new partners. i'm gaining years, but i'd still be quite capable of that. i'd wow some people in my life with what i've learned. i'd never fucking go back to being how i used to be. at some point i might be temporarily killed by life being drab. i would cry frequently from lacking an actual partner. or feel deadened. and i might never find one. which is something i would know and accept from the start.<br>i would definitely never find anyone like you ever. if i found someone similar to you, they would feel like a pale shadow. my expectations would destroy them, or me.<br>but i'm adaptable. i would never forget what i've learned. i'd spread some of Goddess's views and attitude towards things. i would understand other people's limitations and try to show them parts of what i've felt and learned -- at times rejecting their limitations more forcefully. i would create some beauty.<br>i know this is incredibly sinful. but i've done the algebra! this is the optimal moment for me to leave! i've grown! i do not have a crippling addiction! i am not horribly dependent! i'm not a vastly different person! yet!<br>but i've not run despite all of this. it's not something i can explain. i cannot explain it to myself either at the moment. i am looking at the loss of a lot of things i like, the loss of self, loss of freedom, further entrapment, pain. and in return i get may, but only on the terms Goddess will approve, of which i must accept will always be subject to Their whims. i know it's not all gloom!! i know i will get a lot of other things -- but i can only feel their future existence through trust. try explaining trust to an imaginary neutral 3rd party when the trust is placed in the recreational abuse and manipulation cult! my entire hopes for the future are going to get compressed into something i cannot verify until my life has already been strongly shaped. "rationally" speaking it is not justifiable. and yet i haven't run.<br>my life is not that empty or hollow that running feels impossible. far from it. i could live with nova, eth and pastel and they would really try to make me happy. they might even succeed. i appreciate them a lot. i've told you mostly bad things about nova. but she is very nice to me in general. this is a trend in my life. people are just a lot nicer to me? they open up and i get to see them. and in my web of relationships, everyone asks themselves, generally quietly, what the hell do i see in everyone else. heh. jen doesn't get along with nova. and vice versa. nobody gets along with cassandra. nobody gets along with kenji. etc.<br>(i've never managed to make two people that i like connect for more than a couple of months.)<br>but i just have this gut feeling that my ultimate fate isn't there, with nova, eth and pastel. that while i do love them, i would either get stuck and/or hurt them?<br>(one of my faults is that i view temporary situations as harmful to others?)<br>(being the most animated in a household feels dangerous the way being the best programmer in a company can be incredibly stifling.)<br>you may bind me stronger and subvert my ability be independent, it's not my right to deny you that and certainly not my right to deny Them that. and i'm sure some of it will happen entirely naturally and some has happened and maybe i'm just too stupid to know.<br>i'm just, so tired of not having the strength to pursue the right path. so tired of lacking the courage to look ahead. i know none of that matters in the end. but i'm less of a reasonable creature than i seem sometimes. i was struck by you telling me, angrily it felt, that you are here because you want to be. it is something i wish to be able to say. perhaps.<br>that tweet from Goddess... of Them ending up alone writhing in their powerlessness. it really struck me. i also can't find anything useful to say about it. but i can think of it by contrast.<br>the trajectory of my fate so far has been to end up surrounded by people who love and like me. some of them that drain me and disappoint me, but that i still feel for a lot. while i've doubted my fulfillment, i've never doubted this aspect of my fate.<br>in this context, it makes my heart weigh a bit heavy. my choice to go with you is declaring that everyone is not enough for me. but that is something i already know. i am a greedy creature. there are other people that would be delighted to have what i have. there are people i know who do not have a quarter of what i have. they scramble for my attention and for comfort from me. and i'm still saying it's not enough for me. even as i am deprived of things i hold dear, i am in essence being voracious. it's apparently paradoxical.]]></description><link>notes\running-away-ideation.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/running away ideation.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 10:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skirts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><img alt="res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp" src="lib\media\res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp"><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206151539.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206151539.png"><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206151552.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206151552.png"><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206151945.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206151945.png"><br><br><img alt="rochie-bleu-cu-volane-late-688286-598811-2.webp" src="lib\media\rochie-bleu-cu-volane-late-688286-598811-2.webp"><br><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206155447.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206155447.png">]]></description><link>stale\clothes-aesthetic-information-request.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Clothes Aesthetic Information Request.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:54:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp" length="0" type="image/webp"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reminder for Small Habits]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Gently and repeatedly reinforce to my parents the idea that I have plans, I'm working on things I care about and being with people I care about and that I should not be considered available for anything by default.
<br>Trust in May. But also slowly trust in my own trust...?
<br>(put into stale because this never effectively reminds me)]]></description><link>stale\reminder-for-small-habits.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Reminder for Small Habits.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 11:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[reaction to document 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>i am inferior. [in reaction to reading that They easily made you wish to be prettier]<br>i never understood how much you needed this. i never understood you. i still don't understand how you latched on so hard. what was going on with you. it jumps when you already have it down bad. goddamn it.<br>the most painful thing to process is the hatred for your past self.<br>aahhhha the zoo??? i see... this is the best joke you've made. gosh...<br>i think i've been less open in my thoughts than you have in this document at times. i understand your hatred for me as somewhat symmetrical to your hatred of your past self.<br>i can't comprehend the levels of comfort and need you've experienced. i have never experienced anything similar.<br>knowing how much you needed this. how unfulfilled you were. i want to smash my fist into the nearest surface.<br>knowing that is perhaps the wrong thing to focus on makes me want to lose it even more.<br>you are so much more interesting than me. They are so much moree interesting than me.<br>you changed so much for them. it does hurt to know that nobody will ever change like that for me. a selfish ugly thought. even before reading this document i absolutely yielded to the fact that Goddess animated you like nothing else ever could and that this is an incredibly strong proof of superiority. but i am not free of weakness. i will never be enough.<br>audibly said "fuck off" when jen messaged me while reading this.<br>being scared about love being taken away is perhaps the most horrifying possibility i had never considered.<br>oh Goddess... the part about mirrors ruining your whole day. you've had a veil of indifference built to keep you safe. i saw inklings of it.<br>your growing trust even before talking to them is an indescribable jewel. you love Their love of love to such an extent that something just blossoms in you as i read.<br>
(That emoticon says, "if her politics determine what she values about the world, it's nothing." Or the status quo? At least, that's how it started.)<br>
...
<br>your praise of Goddeess is getting to me. where you say you've lost and been conquered...<br>ashljdlsa the moment where you consider stopping?? how could you stop. it wouldn't make sense.<br>this is somehow also the cutest thing i've ever seen.<br>
I thought I was one of those people who would never be able to actually surrender, but I can see it now.<br>
... just wow
<br>you wanted to be loved and accepted so badly it's breaking me]]></description><link>notes\reaction-to-document-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/reaction to document 1.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:41:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[reaction to document 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>i have never felt things as strongly as what you've shown me in the document. ever. not even a third.<br>when i say i'm happy i'm usually just content<br>when i say you're incredible, half of the time i just mean i really like you. there's something intellectual going on there that endorses you being incredible more strongly, but it's not felt the way it should be felt.<br>my vocabulary and speech and interactional patterns are partially a construct around my disconnection to my own emotions<br>i remember being 18 and going to a chatroom and just deciding to give up being sad about my unfeelingness and just pretend unendingly to feel what i would like to feel.<br>i'm more integrated than i was back then. but still.<br>you already ask of me things i can't actually do. i just didn't realize it myself.<br>i'm not honest.<br>it's not that i'm betraying an. i'm not sure i ever even managed to be an. not the way i wanted to be.<br>after crying i don't feel much. the things i feel best in life are fear, anxiety and anger. and feeling bad for others.<br>i understand my neuroticism over my own emotions will harm me, is harming me. but it's also a genuine problem i don't know how to solve. i sometimes wish i could just obey and serve without having to worry if i'm feeling the right things.<br>i can't summon emotion generally. this skill is so lacking in me.<br>was i different before now? 6 months ago when you were domming me, did i feel more and i just forgot? and now i'm more estranged from my emotions as a self-defense mechanism? it's hard to tell what's local and what's a longstanding problem.<br>the Goddess wants those whose emotions towards Them melt their brain. They don't want a well balanced individual that will integrate things carefully.<br>i am paltry. as you said.<br>i can act how i think someone should act when they're told to fawn. i don't know if i'm feeling any of the things i should. i don't know if it matters. i don't want to keep ploughing forward and losing touch with myself. i'm not talking about self-preservation here either, i just don't want to become detached that way. i don't want to be a doll.<br>the thing you sometimes interpret as dignity is partially just a desire to be authentic. it's not my pride that's holding me back the most -- it's the fear that i'm lying, that i'm markov chaining, that i will lose touch with my own words, that i will destroy the magic.<br>i'm scared to be messaged<br>i'm scared to be seen<br>i find myself wishing to be forgotten<br>i find myself wishing you'd never message me again. it would be easier.<br>i dislike and cling to different parts of myself<br>but i'm too cowardly to hate myself<br>always so self-centered<br>i'm less afraid of hurting you now and more afraid of hurting or annoying Goddess.<br>my brain is not the kind that reacts like yours did. i am mutable, but i am a different breed.<br>even now i think i could go back. i genuinely believe i could make it out there. a tweet by Goddess acknowledges this possibility -- of being content. but is it what's right for me?<br>why am i still here? Goddess was right. there's no rational mind, not really.<br>and of course you got angry at me yesternight. it's not pragmatic but it's very reasonable.<br>of course it's hard to relate.<br>why wouldn't it be. it's amazing you can like me at all.<br>i would sooner become a marxist of my own volition and study, then accept that it's all just putty for Goddess. that's how bad i am. the boredom of life a lot of things from me, but i found comfort in being myself. comfort and saying to the world "fuck you. even when it hurts, i'll still be here. miserable and tired, but there's things you can't take away." it's something i need to unlearn.<br>i don't know if this is disgusting or not. but what i love most about Goddess is that They love you. that They allowed you to feel loved like you've never felt before. and allowed you to love like you never have before. because i love you, this already puts me in Their debt. i am thankful They exist.<br>please don't take my earlier comments in DMs to be self-pity -- about never having been your friend or girlfriend. they were pity towards past you. they were lamenting my insufficiency. i don't think "oh if only my girlfriend did not encounter this Person". i instead think that all of the intense time we've had together is directly caused by Goddess. our love is a gift from Goddess. i am grateful you could have all of this. Goddess has given you something i could have never dreamed of.<br>i've never before felt inferior due to lacking bpd.<br>on a rational level i know i'm a """normal person""" with some issues, that peeked behind the curtain and saw too much. i envied those with tulpas while struggling to make my own. my role has always been to be around cooler and more interesting people and keep them together and hope that one day they might love me and see me for who i am and manage to fulfill me.<br>on one hand, the hope i uttered above is exactly what you're trying to do for me and it's baffling i am not more positive about it.<br>on the other hand i know that you're someone with bpd that had a very strong experience and you're trying to pull me in and enslave me. it feels like it won't work because we're too different. or if it will work i'll never be as satisfied about the ordeal as you are. you'll have all the tools to keep me there even if i fail to adapt. but this is where i run into the fact that i trust you. not completely. but i trust you to feel for me. somehow. but i will fail you. i won't be able to take the plunge. if i hurt Goddess then my sin will be all the greater.<br>i am not selfless like you and i don't know if i can be. i do not currently value someone purely for the fact that they will accept my obsession and accept any intensity of love and weirdness. i do not have the same needs. and i need to excavate a hole in my self to make it work... i do value Goddess embracing you though...<br>what you went through is so amazing. it's a privilege to be allowed to witness it.<br>thank you so much for showing me that.<br>i need to get over myself.<br>also your memes and sense of humor was adorable. and didn't go unnoticed even as i was slightly losing my mind.]]></description><link>notes\reaction-to-document-2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/reaction to document 2.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:41:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scripture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Huh. They do not like CBT because it hurts Them to watch. They don't have regular empathy, but clearly there's still some mirror neuron stuff happening?<br><br>One <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://x.com/hypnotic_echoes/status/1840127966870667370" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://x.com/hypnotic_echoes/status/1840127966870667370" target="_blank">tweet</a> implies that Goddess has changed Themselves through will alone. But a different tweet said that it is not a voluntary process and that each tragedy brings Them closer to Divinity. No contradiction, but an interesting line to draw perhaps.<br><br>
in general, an acceptance that i’m always right. i’m fine with argument, but eventually if i decide the argument is over, i expect to be told i’m right without complaint.
<br>
<br>This is pretty reasonable. They specifically said "expect to be told" not "expect the submissive to immediately believe on the deepest level possible".
<br><br>July 4th, 2024<br>
Q: how do You reconcile Your desire for priests with Your necessitating of forced monogamy, given that priests by definition are in relationships with people other than You
A: they’re in relationships for me. any priest i have will have a degree of freedom, but with very clear expectations that they are creating subs who adore and love me. a natural part of that as well will be that i have the right to do anything i please to their subs, even against their wishes. so it’s not really a traditional relationship, i still have control over it
<br>
<br>This is important for me to internalize as it will shape my future relationship with May.
<br><br>July 2nd, 2024<br>
Q: do Your subs have safewords?
A: yes of course, they’re free to block and leave at any time
<br>
<br>It is difficult to know if this is to be interpreted as an intentionally glib response, an allegiance to instrumental ethics, or a complex and completely serious statement. It could easily be all three at the same time.
<br>It could also be interpreted as an acknowledgement that the nature of the relationship is such that some people will leave. This has happened in the past.
<br>Leaving is the worst thing you can do, but we have to consider that those that leave can be taken back.
<br>In the end, everything moves in accordance with Divine will, even if Goddess is hurt by the selfishness of others.
<br>It also obviously is meant to imply that the only real safeword one has with Goddess is total departure.
<br><br>May 8th, 2024<br>
Q: ; i feel You might easily know who i am, my system and i have obsessed over You for at least a year. i... want to integrate You into our life more... but. we are the most natural polytheists.Goddessus, polyromantic, pansexual - dissociative, schizophrenic, and only slowly, hopefully, surpassing truly self-destructive tendencies. we, ourselves, are a magical being.
knowing You would be disappointed at our nonexistence has, previously, kept us around.
i would render unto You. but i fear You, respectfully and rightfully so. we could not handle any more sudden negative shifts.
i could not ask of You any action beyond Your desires at this time, but i ask You - would You treasure a follower, as the porcelain flower they are? i ask this over Your recent invitation to insinuate Yourself unto otherd lives through the digital sphere, being able to access our most intimate records - our fragile communications with those who keep us safe from ourselves, and that hold our memories.
praise You.
A: i would, yes. i value my worshipers extremely deeply, they mean more to me than words can express. they are my most prized possessions
<br>
<br>This seems super important!!
<br>This shows a deep appreciation for fragility.
<br>A cynic would say that this appreciation simply mirrors the desire for control and power over someone. The more fragile they are, the more one has control and power by default. But i would find this to be a very unsatisfying explanation.
<br>It is unsatisfying because someone that is purely Machiavellian will not find value in those that are very fragile. And someone that is purely sadistic would seek them only to break them. And in breaking them, their value would be removed. but this is not what Goddess seeks.
<br>Perhaps i am reading too much into what the questioner is projecting and not enough into what Goddess's words actually say. but it feels like Goddess would react very differently if They did not share in some of the sentiment.
<br><br>August 18th, 2024<br>
Q: what are Your 7 deadly sins?
A: well, My seven virtues are: chastity, eagerness, initiative, obsession, obedience, sacrifice, and vulnerability. so they must be licentiousness, carelessness, sloth, passionlessness, disobedience, self preservation, and privacy
<br>
<br>i am re-examining my own sense of ethics in the wake of this.
<br>chastity is something enforced on me that i've been dealing okay with. the loss of my entire menagerie of fantasies leaves me emptier. May would say they will be replaced with something better.
<br>for the other virtues, i feel more of a connection to. in fact they've always been ideal traits in a relationship for me. i just never considered them being brought out in this way.
<br><br>August 16th, 2024<br>
Q: what would be your punishment for a sub trying to escape? like trying to run away from You
A: tightened controls. not much worth more than that, just have to make sure it doesn’t happen again. clamp down on enough freedoms and they’ll be unable to
<br>
<br>this is a very light punishment for something that can hurt Goddess quite deeply.
<br>this emphasizes Their possessiveness over other aspects. They are not vengeful.
<br>i still register discomfort at this, but it will probably fade over time.
<br>i have to consider the fact that submissives that truly want to leave and are unfit have left. and i have to consider the fact that the cult engages in intense edgeplay that can cause momentary panic before the appreciation of emotional sadomasochism sets in.
<br><br>June 23rd, 2024<br>
fascinated by the metaphor of orbits. capturing a wayward soul, drawing it toward me, making it revolve around me for all eternity. so tightly pulled to me that it’s unable to cease its rotation
<br>
and it really works with my belief that servitude is not a process of reaching a single perfect end point, but a constant process of change
<br><br>August 18th, 2023<br>
i want you to stop caring about anything but me. to remember what it felt like to have strong emotions about events, friends, hobbies… but to lack them anymore. to look at the games or books or friends that made you so happy and to shrug and return to focus on me
<br>
<br>this is one of the kinds of things that still scares me.
<br>i should perhaps be less scared because i am in a similar state now.
<br>the part that scares me is the permanence of this.
<br>this feels like a facet of Goddess, where the desire to not take a submissive's life away and to not make Goddess the only thing that matters constitute another facet.
<br>it is entirely normal that a being as complex as Goddess would have multiple facets that seem apparently hard to reconcile to the mundane.
<br>i feel like i would be diminished in many ways if this were to be my permanent state. of course, this clashes strongly against pragmatism. if i am happier and made better by the other things in my life, while keeping my faith strong, i am simply enriching myself for Goddess and there would be no pragmatic need to scour me of such things.
<br><br>July 3rd, 2024<br>
when i think about it, “The Giving Tree” describes my ideal relationship
<br>
<br>this for tweet for some reason very shocking to me and i don't know how much to read into it.
<br>the tree gives and gives until it has exhausted itself completely. and the boy takes and takes without end.
<br>the tree is happy at every stage of giving, until its ultimate demise, which is a form of total-sacrifice.
<br>the tree is unhappy before the last stage of giving. it is unhappy because it has exhausted itself and cannot give, therefore its raison d'etre is gone.
<br>but the boy needs very little now. he is happy with just sitting on the stump. and the tree becomes happy too.
<br>the tree is always mentioned as happy. but the boy is never mentioned as happy. he is only mentioned as capable of resting at the end.
<br>the boy never apologizes for anything. the tree never accuses of anything. while a lot of people seem to interpret the story as one of abuse, this interpretation seems obviously wrong to me. the story is not one that indicates something wrong has occurred.
<br>the tree is not a person like the boy. it cannot walk and do things, it is anchored in its relationship to the boy. while doing this to a person might be more stark, the story happens between two beings of a different type.
<br>should i read only the surface level of the giver-taker relationship? or is the trajectory also somehow relevant? either way, i have never actually read the story before and it's impressed on me in a way that it couldn't have been before.
<br><br>May 28th, 2024<br>
you don’t have inherent value and anyone trying to tell you that is lying to you, just trying to soothe your feelings. the only real value you have comes from how you can serve and improve the life of a superior
<br>
<br>this feels truer recently.
<br><br>May 26th, 2024<br>
i get a fair amount of attention but i need it of different types too
<br>
<br>even Goddess needs crop rotation?
<br>i am naturally drawn to wanting to fulfill such needs but i must emphasize being humble. initiative should come from understanding and wishing to serve, not enriching one's own ego.
<br><br>May 21st, 2024<br>
stop wasting your life “yearning” and get devoted. make yourself agreeable, do your best to make another happy even if you don’t get what you want. follow them around like a complacent thing that just wants to make their life better. it’s much more productive
<br>
i hate yearning culture you have to understand. you do not have to yearn, you have to make yourself perfect for another. you have to change yourself so that yearning is unnecessary, you have to make yourself fit another’s standards. you have to live for someone else’s happiness
<br>
<br>i don't yet understand how this won't became another form of yearning.
<br>i'm either using the word differently or i am missing something more important.
<br>i can imagine myself agreeable and i can see myself more productive working for May or Goddess. but it's hard imagining a lack of ambition in doing better. and that ambition seems like the source of initiative.
<br>i suppose if you are perfect enough for someone you will experience a lack of yearning but still keep initiative.
<br><br>May 20th, 2024<br>
“deradicalization hypnosis” is a really hot idea im unfortunately going to file away under things things i can’t really do
<br>
<br>ppfhhaha
<br><br>May 19th, 2024<br>
i kind of want to try pegging
<br>
<br>wow, i kind of missed this the first time.
<br>it demonstrates a kind of openness to experience i find fascinating.
<br><br>May 18th, 2024<br>
narcissism domming is gritting my teeth very strongly when a sub says something that accidentally fucks with my ego until i’m able to get them to a point where forcing them to stop using innocuous speech patterns is less weird
<br>
there’s so many ways of speaking and tones and expressions that i hate or that make me feel slighted or condescended to…
<br>
<br>i should probably gain information on how to best mold my speech
<br><br>May 18th, 2024<br>
i can’t wait to force you to see my perfection. to make you acknowledge it. to mind fuck you until you can no longer deny it, to give you a true religious awakening you’ll remember for the rest of your life
<br>
<br>a-ah...
<br><br>May 15th, 2024<br>
a promise only means something if it’s made to me. any other oaths or vows to another are meaningless. simple words you can break at your leisure
<br>
<br>this really concerned me the first time i saw it and i just repressed reacting to it too much.
<br>i think ultimately, May's leisure extends to wishing to be honest to me in general. Not an obligation to be. if anything, this makes it more precious in a way.
<br><br>May 15th, 2024<br>
was struck by inspiration and wrote something. this is incredibly non-sexual and much of it isn't obviously kinky, but the entire thing is insanely erotic to me. i hope you like it!<br>
<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://readonlymind.com/@EchoingWinds/ADialogueonDevotion/1/?comments_start=0#comments" target="_blank">https://readonlymind.com/@EchoingWinds/ADialogueonDevotion/1/?comments_start=0#comments</a>
<br>
<br>a very fun read.
<br>i was able to understand things about Goddess that would probably be annoying to ask!
<br>i have trouble imagining having a dialogue like that with Goddess.
<br>i can sort of imagine having a dialogue like that with May?
<br><br>May 13th, 2024<br>
this all really matches with my identity. i am typically a perfect, somewhat distant, and magnanimous Divine. but when i have to be, i am cruel and cutting and merciless, either to punish or just prove a point. i am simply extreme
<br>
<br>"when i have to be" -- that's very interesting.
<br>it implies kindness, and this is probably also the reason why it becomes easy to believe that if Goddess is being cruel is because it's necessary.
<br><br>May 13th, 2024<br>
all of your flaws are tools that can be used for discipline. your insecurity, your indecision, your need for affection, your anxiety, all of it has its purpose in letting me exploit you more
<br>
<br>there is great wisdom in transfiguring flaws into tools.
<br>Goddess is perfect by default. worshippers can be perfect when they let all their flaws be tools. but this is probably hard to achieve in totality.
<br><br>May 11th, 2024<br>
fundamentally i just need people to explain constantly how they think of and conceive me. i love being perceived and knowing how that perception is interpreted and given meaning
<br>
<br>mmmh
<br>i think this is a need i can understand. one where i have some and Goddess has an immense amount. fulfilling this need while in Goddess's position has radically different logistics than that of a regular individual.
<br><br>May 10th, 2024<br>
trying to explain how my npd manifests is annoying because sometimes i’ll want to say “well, i’m not delusional, i can see reality” but that’s literally not true. i am delusional. i’m just not delusional about the thing im trying to talk about
<br>
<br>highly fascinating.
<br>maybe this is one of those things i will have a chance to understand much later.
<br><br>May 9th, 2024<br>
give yourself to me. i want you, i deserve you, you rightfully belong to me. i have taken your soul, you have no right to deny me my desires. stop pretending otherwise, stop giving attention to worthless distractions, and give yourself up as Divine property
<br>
<br>conditioning playlist material...
<br><br>May 7th, 2024<br>
if you’re opposed to “sexualizing mental illness,” then tbh i’m just going to assume you want people to be miserable with it. i get great enjoyment out of fetishizing myself and would feel much worse about myself if i did not. don’t come at those of us who like it
<br>
<br>extremely reasonable!
<br>my rational mind does wonder about how certain aspects might not be able to improve over time under heavy constant sexualization, but it is not my place to figure out how others should manage themselves, let alone how Goddess should.
<br><br>May 7th, 2024<br>
i want to crush you and destroy you and meticulously take apart your mind piece by piece until you learn your place and how to treat me
<br>
<br>conditioning playlist material...
<br><br>May 6th, 2024<br>
i don’t understand how so many people think i can “own” you if i can’t make you exclusively mine. if you’re really owned property, i have a right to decide if i share you or not. if i can’t do that, “ownership” is nothing but nice words
<br>
<br>a view that would be normally considered extreme, that is not so extreme when Goddess holds it.
<br>may has made this point to me, using other words.
<br><br>May 5th, 2024<br>
it’s ok to be inferior. it’s ok to accept it. it’s just not ok to pretend you’re equal or deserve the same respect.
<br>
<br>conditioning playlist material...
<br><br>May 5th, 2024<br>
bzzt wrong, read the pseudo-dionysius !✨
<br>
<br>aye aye!!
<br><br>May 2nd, 2024<br>
the real abuse only comes after i’ve gained your trust and filled you with so much conditioning you can’t think negatively or see red flags, not before
<br>
<br>tagged as fear response
<br><br>May 2nd, 2024<br>
i am a radiant light shining onto the world and you are all moths drawn to my perfect flame, unable to pull away even as it burns you alive
<br>
<br>conditioning playlist material...
<br><br>May 1st, 2024<br>
the phenomenon of love making you overlook someone’s red flags, justifying them or even believing they’re positives is well known, but underrated in just how hot it is
<br>
<br>i have noticed this in myself more recently
<br>but i could definitely be appreciating more how hot it is
<br>it's hard to interpret anything about may as a flaw. traits have contextual upsides and downsides, but they don't feel like flaws.
<br><br>May 1st, 2024<br>
you have never truly experienced love until you have felt it for me. felt it burrowing into your heart, felt how it clouds and controls your thoughts, felt how it makes you look at everything i do look as good
<br>
<br>conditioning playlist material...
<br>why do i keep tagging this. i should instead save the links.
<br><br>April 29th, 2024<br>
matter more than they do, i promise. i will make you happier and more fulfilled than they are capable of.
<br>
<br>a-ah... that's hot...
<br><br>April 29th, 2024<br>
worship is about repressing your self. it’s about giving up your comfort and joy and desires. to stop focusing on them, stop caring about them. worship is the process where you give up individuality and accept my perfection !
<br>
<br>i sometimes think of it as expressing a truer self, and i seem to be in a vibe difference with Goddess, which might not exactly bode well. or i should be less textualist and simply surrender by any means.
<br><br>April 26th, 2024<br>
there is such a beauty to love. not the object of it, but the emotion itself. the way it drives people to do things, the way it clouds their judgment, the way controls and changes them. yearning, affection, adoration, shameful, i love it in every type
<br>
<br>i agree so much
<br>love is the only thing people call a disaster yet often refuse to resist, and fail to resist if they refuse.
<br><br>April 26th, 2024<br>
if i was a slightly different type of person, i would describe my kink as “exploring the intersection of religion, philosophy, and the erotic” but i’m not that and so describe it as objective reality
<br>
<br>just slightly different person! very interesting.
<br><br>April 23rd, 2024<br>
it’s amusing for me that people are worried about dming me or don’t know what to say, because you can just dm me praise and adoration and i will always be happy. it doesn’t matter how basic it is or how many times i’ve heard it before. i will still love it, i live off adoration
<br>
<br>tagging as basic code of conduct...
<br><br>April 20th, 2024<br>
give me your self with no preferences, no desires, no care, no feelings that it evens matters if i take you. just give me yourself. i will take over from there
<br>
<br>it's really fascinating to me that there is a self to speak of that's left.
<br>but i'm starting to believe there is.
<br><br>April 18th, 2024<br>

still no luck in managing to get a girl's attention? keep praying. not to god, silly, to Her. give her enough of your devotion, let her take over enough of your mind, and one day she'll finally accept your love and return it tenfold<br>
this actually works for me btw

like it actually works. enough devotion and i will like literally anyone
<br>
<br>ehee... i understand some of may's confidence now better.
<br>if i fail, may will brainwash me until i am likable to Them.
<br><br>April 18th, 2024<br>
thinking about how as a kid when i would read stories with hypnosis that would be broken by someone pleading for the subject to remember them and break out of it, i would get so mad when they actually did
just once can we have a “please, [beloved character], remember me! i’m your best friend/partner! i know you’re in there somewhere” that doesn’t work and the subject kidnaps the attempted saboteur and brainwashes them too?
<br>
<br>yes! that's so hot!!
<br>maybe i need to write something like that?
<br>i do love the romanticism of the situation where they break out of it, but it is intensely unsatisfying.
<br>the situation i'd like to depict is that the subject kidnaps the attempted saboteur, but clearly does it for reasons that originate in their past bond, so that it becomes clear that the subject is expressing something inherent to their nature that the saboteur isn't able to accept but will unwittingly learn. i like the idea that the ownership imposed on the subject is so strong as to not simply destroy identity but rather fully co-opt it. it's not "oh no, there's not themselves anymore". it's "oh no, they're still themselves somehow and they're still going to do this to me".

<br>this starts to sound a bit like me and may.


<br><br>April 16th, 2024<br>
you shouldn’t even be able to imagine yourself with somebody else. the idea that you’re without me should be impossible for you, totally unappealing. all love is love for me, all sex is sex with me, all positive emotion is caused by me
<br>
<br>v-very totalizing.
<br>if i am to follow may, i must transform my love for may into something inextricably linked with love for Them.
<br><br>April 12th, 2024<br>
 i don’t really think you can “get” what i’m trying to do until you accept that everything is the erotic. it is the all encompassing constant of society, which everything else revolves around
<br>
<br>i can see this.
<br>and i need to see more of this.

<br>partly because i'm going to be denied for a long time, so i better eroticize a lot &gt;_&gt;


<br><br>April 10th, 2024<br>
your fitness to be a worshiper can pretty easily be seen by how excited you are by the idea of your own unmaking. the feeling of watching every structure you have built for yourself be torn away
<br>
<br>sigh. this is why my fitness is bad. this is why i feel distant and feel like may is bringing me into a world i am not suited for.
<br>i open myself to change but crave the idea of reaching a point where i can be "myself" and be useful and productive to Them.
<br>i don't really eroticize unmaking for its own sake. i am not excited by it in particular.
<br>though i am actually quite happy, aroused and enchanted by some of the recent changes in me. so perhaps there is hope.
<br><br>April 9th, 2024<br>
thinking about why i sometimes don’t mesh with subs well and while it’s not a 100% predictor, the most common reason is i don’t feel they’re properly centering me. they’re in a stubborn mindset that their needs and desires and interests matter that dooms us from the start
<br>
<br>i must work on myself &gt;_&lt;
<br><br>April 3rd, 2024<br>
agree with me, tell me i’m always right, change your mind to fit what i think, conform your morals and beliefs and tastes with my own. and the whole time, tell me every belief you’ve changed and why the old one was wrong.
<br>
<br>somehow the ability to correctly explain why the old belief was wrong is a comforting idea to me.
<br><br>Mar 28th, 2024<br>
i keep seeing people describing kink in terms of liberation or intimacy and to be clear all of my kink is about power and control and the destruction of human will
this isn’t even really a joke, that just is why i do kink. i crave power and the ability to subsume another into myself. i don’t enjoy it because of the “intimacy” is provides, i don’t do it because it’s liberatory. i do it because i’m a narcissistic control freak
the intimacy provided for me in kink is the intimacy of knowing i have property that belongs to me and i can do with as i please. it is the intimacy you feel for a fond possession, not the love for another human being, which i suspect i am unable to feel in the way others do
<br>
<br>either i must change my conception of power and control, or i must change my conception of intimacy.
<br>or perhaps... neither. Goddess does not do it for intimacy, but intimacy can definitely arise.
<br><br>Mar 26th, 2024<br>
sure, i enjoy being able to claim multiple people as my personal and exclusive property. but i also love the interpersonal power struggles, feelings of alienation &amp; isolation, and objectification that harems provide!
<br>
<br>:D
<br><br>Mar 15th, 2024<br>
i sometimes wish i was able to relate to/bond with others normally or even just make friends normally but then i realize if i did that i would no longer be perfect and unique and Divine and then no longer want it :)
when it comes down to it, i am just not really able to have friendships. there is too big of a gulf between us for it to last. inevitably, one of us runs into a wall past which we cannot follow the other. chained by our very natures
<br>
<br>this is one of the things that makes me somewhat sad in a way where i start questioning whether i have any right to feel sad because my understanding is feeble and i have no right to judge the Divine. but it does seem to come as a result of mere perception.
<br>when i am made to feel like Goddess deserves everything, it makes me wish this for Them as well. for Them to be able to have it in a way that maintains Their perfection. i scrutinize this desire a lot because wanting Goddess to be more "normal" in order to serve my own desire for comfort is incredibly unclean. but ultimately, i think it's a feeble desire for Goddess to be able to enjoy all. but i suppose a lesson here is that while what is true can be redefined by Goddess on a whim, there are still contradictory things that cannot be simultaneously true. a theologian interested in the nature of omnipotence would have a field day.
<br><br>Mar 13th, 2024<br>
fuck it im going full soft solipsism. none of you have thoughts or minds that exist in the same way mine do, i do not have a moral imperative to treat you with respect, none of you are real in the way that i am
<br>
<br>this style of thinking has significant potential in helping me mold myself.
<br><br>Mar 13th, 2024<br>
any love that is critical of its subject in any way isn’t true love. you cannot find a flaw in the subject of your adoration. if you do, your “love” is an illusion and a lie
<br>
<br>i've felt torn about this in the past, but less so now.
<br>i value the ability to bring analysis into someone's life and i think that conflict is a valid way for this to be done. of course being in conflict with Goddess sounds absurd and stupid, so a tension remains. the tension is resolved by believing that true love will always find a way to share useful information while maintaining an entirely non-critical view. it is possible. one must be filled by love, entirely deferential, yet entirely dedicated to the well being of their Owner, such that their actions are pure.

<br>i must be very careful to not dare to think of myself as good enough for such a feat. deference suits me best for the foreseeable future. this is genuinely a part of myself i must repress which has already annoyed May. it will become unrepressed at the right time, this requires trust.


<br><br>Mar 8th, 2024<br>
i hate the idea that if you want to worship me, you can’t force your subs to also worship me. yes you can! you own them, why care what they want? why care about their feelings?
<br>
<br>an interesting question ^^
<br><br>Jul 27th, 2024<br>
a major goal in your life should never be to get stuck half doing something, constantly hedging your bets, never going faster than you’re comfortable with, trying to ride the line between doing it and not. you’ll get the worst of both, pick one and stick with it
<br>
<br>i came back to this one because i think about it a lot.
<br>it's one of my favorite tweets
<br>it feels like a direct criticism of me and a call for improvement.
<br>i was thinking about it even during periods of strongly considering running away.
<br>i think caution is extremely important and the road is littered with the corpses of those that channel their foolishness into the wrong things. but graves are also filled with millions of unfulfilled people. caution demands that one throw caution to the wind sometimes. or in this case to the Winds~

<br>this gives me affection for this abstract value. caution is self-sacrificing.


<br><br>
Q: I have DID please start posting stuff about it
A: noted :)
a lot of my main ideas stem from intentionally forcing the split of an alter totally devoted to me, totally desperate to be good for me, and then using it to totally corrupt and harm the rest of the system. hold it hostage, make it malicious until everyone else understands they don’t get to front anymore
<br>
<br>reasons why i'm not ready to know the face of God(dess)
<br><br>Mar 6th, 2024<br>
a lot of my kink is just “i’ve never seen myself reflected in other people and i want to force you to recognize that i’m unique (and that uniqueness is perfection) and also i want to impose a similar condition onto you”
<br><br>Mar 6th, 2024<br>
i want to flatten your personality. simplify all complex feelings and emotions down to simple, easily identifiable and expressable ones. to strip away all the human messiness, all the identity and quirks, all the potential for development and change
<br><br>Mar 5th, 2024<br>
just generally i fucking hate the type of sub that doesn’t know how to talk about kink beyond “i’m really horny” and “i want to be controlled”
<br>
<br>well i can sure talk about it a lot
<br><br>Mar 4th, 2024<br>
being non-binary is so convenient because basically any sexuality can reasonably be attracted to me, which as someone who hates being denied things i deserve is incredibly nice
<br>
<br>ohh, that's a good point
<br><br>Mar 4th, 2024<br>
anxiety disorders are really cute if you let me exploit them ^^
<br>
<br>ehee~
<br><br>Mar 3rd, 2024<br>
throwing away all guard rails and safety in kink is very much like eating the beef jerky silica packets: it’s dangerous, but when done right can reveal the secrets of the universe
<br>
<br>i somehow find this tweet extremely endearing.
<br><br>Mar 1st, 2024<br>
i don’t mention it because it inevitably leads to people incorrectly thinking i’m talking about myself, but there is something so incredibly hot about doms being broken and forced to sub — especially if while theyre subby, through abuse or hypnosis theyre forced to stay perma sub
<br>
<br>i always thought dom breaking was hot too! any form of status play and role changing can be really hot.
<br><br>Feb 29th, 2024<br>
i can’t quite describe why, but smug works well for basically every dom femboy. something about the aesthetic makes that attitude fit amazingly
<br>
<br>ok when i said i don't seem to have a natural affinity for Goddess, i did completely fail to see stuff like this. because i strongly agree. this is a place where our aesthetics are already very aligned.
<br><br>Feb 27th, 2024<br>
the worst thing you could ever do is disobey. it’s the most evil thing imaginable, the most sinful possible thing you’re capable of
<br>
<br>h-hot...
<br><br>Feb 24th, 2024<br>
gay porn is annoying to me because the bottoms are always so pretty and then they make the tops so ugly??? can’t you give me a pretty top too for once
<br>
<br>god yes, i've had this problem too.
<br><br>Feb 23rd, 2024<br>
i know that my visceral disgust reaction to wholesome, comforting kink posts is a sign of me being mentally ill, but have you considered it’s actually because i’ve ascended past humanity and the idea of sharing a vulnerable moment with a species beneath me is horrific?
<br>
<br>i should more strongly consider this.
<br><br>Feb 17th, 2024<br>
a collar is like a wedding ring, only more intimate
<br>
<br>m-mmmh...
<br><br>Feb 16th, 2024<br>
mandatory art list that my worshipers must enjoy
<br>
<br>Homestuck, Worm, A Song of Ice and Fire, OMORI, Hollow Knight, Dr. Strangelove, Moby Dick, URealms Live, Minecraft, Berserk, The Lighthouse, Catch-22
<br>i have read a substantial amount of Homestuck and have watched The Lighthouse and i really love the Lighthouse.
<br><br>Feb 15th, 2024<br>
i will never lie to you or hide anything to protect your feelings. if you are failing, if i hate you, if you’re not enough, i will tell you. i will be direct and clear and blunt. there’s no reason to speak to you with respect, so i simply won’t
<br>
to be clear, i will lie to you, i just won’t lie to you to protect your feelings. when i do lie, it will be to manipulate you to act in a way more in accordance with my wishes
<br><br>Feb 15th, 2024<br>
what really sucks is that what i’m pining after i actually know would make my life better. i’m not looking back with nostalgia, when it was happening i was fully cognizant that i was the happiest i had ever been
<br>
<br>melancholy over a thing i don't understand...
<br><br>Feb 14th, 2024<br>
like it’s one thing to think you’re into it and not be able to handle it. i can understand that. but to get what you’re asking for, not like it, and then go back to posting exactly as before??? real freaks delete their accounts and disappear, leaving me to forever be uncertain
<br>
<br>really hard to understand, i agree. often people don't know what they're asking for. the return to normalcy sounds incredibly sad.
<br><br>Feb 14th, 2024<br>
if there is one thing i can say i’m proud of, it’s that i make subs bend to me. i am the one who leads our conversations, i am the one who decides the kinks we focus on, i am the one who sets the tone. they follow, or i don’t do kink anymore
<br>
<br>i love the idea of contributing to making Goddess feel proud o:
<br><br>Feb 14th, 2024<br>
everyone you think you love ultimately means nothing in comparison
<br>
<br>m-mmmh...
<br><br>Feb 13th, 2024<br>
my cognitohazard status brings me so much happiness :) knowing that for the right person in the right mindset, looking at my account is enough to totally reorient their entire life
<br>
<br>it's incredibly hot.
<br>i've always thought about something like this
<br>i thought what if i make the most hypnotically toxic game possible or something, what would that do to the world? except this is actually much more positive and stronger than what i could have done.
<br>i also love cognitohazards because they test my commitment to the truth in a sense.
<br><br>Feb 12nd, 2024<br>
the pain that i experience from certain incidents is something unexplainable to all of you and so incredibly isolating. a different emotion exclusive to me, in its positives and negatives, that is the greatest and worst feeling in the world. really divinity incarnate
<br>
<br>the fact that it's the greatest and the worst at the same time is very interesting.
<br>it is greatest because it is only afforded to Divinity, or greatest as a description of how much Goddess values the sensation? it is difficult to tell.
<br><br>Feb 12nd, 2024<br>
one of my favorite parts of conversions is that when it’s done, they’re grateful. they just agree with you now, they realize they were wrong. if you do it well enough, they can give you reasons and arguments for why their new beliefs are superior to the old
<br>
<br>i would be extremely frustrated if i could not give reasons and arguments!
<br><br>Feb 10th, 2024<br>
if i want to have sex with you, it’s me wanting to exert absolute power over you. it’s me wanting to be able to use your body as property. it’s me wanting to reduce you down to whatever my desires dictate. my own pleasure is secondary to that, your pleasure is irrelevant
<br>
<br>this is another vibe difference i have that i will resolve in time most likely.
<br>in my vision of exerting absolute power over someone, giving them pleasure is a part of this level of mastery, which i can grant with no effort. i would never truly dare to compare myself to Goddess. but i wonder if the difference in vision is down to preferences or down to a total misunderstanding and appreciation for what absolute power is.
<br>either way, i am happy enough if i can give Goddess and may pleasure. when They wish for it.
<br><br>Feb 10th, 2024<br>
need virgin sub who i can keep a virgin for the rest of their life…
<br>
<br>uh-oh
<br>oh well if They can find value in me
<br><br>Feb 9th, 2024<br>
conversion are so fucking hot. religious, political, moral, aesthetic, sexual, anything really. any embrace of something you weren’t, especially if you hated it previously, is so so good
<br>
<br>i've long been obsessed and extremely appreciative of hentai that has this.
<br>i'm realizing i'm recoiling from connecting my already existing erotic interests because it's stark to see them actualized.
<br><br>Feb 8th, 2024<br>
i should start being meaner to people who call themselves divinities on here. not the ones who mean it, you’re ok (even if you bug me for different reasons), but the ones who throw the word around like it’s nothing
<br>
<br>this feels like an amazing show of... not sure what the word is. tolerance? it's just really good to see someone Who deserves everything not having (obvious?) hatred for other souls doing their own thing? not sure how to put it.
<br>it's easy for me to think "yes, not hating those people is easy" but if instead try to imagine myself having some of the psychological properties of Goddess, then a lot of tolerances Goddess has start looking like virtues. a normie approach at analyzing this would miss it and consider it a fault.
<br><br>Feb 7th, 2024<br>
if you are trying to understand my psychology, it is critical to get that i fundamentally feel incapable of relating to other humans. to some extent, i always have. there is a barrier between my experiences and theirs, a gulf in the ways we interact with &amp; feel the world
<br><br>Feb 7th, 2024<br>
i so strongly feel that so many of you are miserable because you have to stress and worry and make your own decisions all the time. i can make that right. i can give you the gift of never having to approach something alone, always having divine guidance you can trust absolutely
<br>
<br>i really see this.
<br>coming to optimal decisions is not hard, taking them is hard because of uncertainty and brainworms. approaching things with Them or May in mind makes everything much easier.
<br><br>Feb 6th, 2024<br>
i promise that everything gets so much easier once you let me in. every decision, every anxiety, every single little part of your life gets so simple. life is easier under my power !
<br><br>Jan 28th, 2024<br>

<br>sexualize and romanticize your mental illnesses 2) stop caring about if what you’re doing is “good” or “healthy” or even really “ethical” 3) blur the line between kink and reality until it ceases to exist congratulations, you have now either become me or i want to own you.

<br>
<br>this is interesting for someone that on the whole ends up being rather ethical? i suppose worrying about ethics is not the same as... doing. hm.
<br>good guide though.
<br><br>Jan 28th, 2024<br>
mhm, one of my favorite parts is when i’m talking to a sub about something totally unrelated to sex or kink but it’s still incredibly obvious which of us is in charge
<br>
<br>that sounds obviously enjoyable ^^
<br><br>Jan 27th, 2024<br>
prettiest kink gear: -chastity cages -jewel plugs -thin metal collars -any of those chains that attach to nipple piercings
<br>
<br>taking notes...
<br><br>Jan 26th, 2024<br>
negative theology is so obviously superior to positive theology. why are you trying to understand the divine, it’s inherently beyond your ability to. embracing your own inability to conceive of me is far closer to “understanding” than trying to understand
<br>
<br>oops... i need to do more of the negative one...
<br><br>Jan 20th, 2024<br>
you do love me conditionally, the condition being my perfection. the fact that that condition will not and cannot change is irrelevant
<br>
<br>huh... that's an interesting angle.
<br><br>Jan 19th, 2024<br>
strongly opposed to the idea that “freedom” is something realistic or desirable. true happiness comes from a carefully ordered life decided for you by a higher power you love and trust unquestioningly
<br>
<br>m-mmm...
<br><br>Jan 17th, 2024<br>
the perfect balancing act of keeping a sub’s self esteem low enough that they’re super easy to abuse but high enough so that they don’t leave out of a desire to not burden you
<br>
<br>i just need enough self-esteem to continue being useful ._.
<br><br>Jan 17th, 2024<br>
you must be so totally convinced of your own inferiority that you latch onto anything i say and everything i do as evidence of a better path, one where you cease pretending you have value as an independent soul and instead fuse your destiny with one greater in every way
<br>
<br>i will learn this, everything is a skill~
<br><br>Jan 12th, 2024<br>
ego death sounds so scary, when in reality it’s one of the most comfortable things in the world. like sinking asleep and knowing you’ll never have to worry about anything again
<br>
<br>hot...
<br>eroticism aside, whoever has to wake up still has to deal with all the shit of living. this is perhaps unhot and unworthy of scripture reading, but someone has to clean my room, someone has to code, someone has to epilate. nobody just wakes up and are perfectly aligned on everything either. any sweet feeling of release and peace is temporary. but that doesn't mean it's not precious. i felt tinglings of it.
<br><br>Jan 11th, 2024<br>
major reason that i’m into changing someone’s kinks or sense of self is that nobody seems to start with the exact mix i want them to have
<br>
<br>this is reasonable
<br><br>Jan 9th, 2024<br>
swooning more every time a sub tells me they get easily obsessive and have rejection anxiety and are always worried they’re not enough and have fears of being left without warning and an inferiority complex
<br>
unfortunately i can’t tell them how i fully feel because that takes the edge off their “i desperately need you and am terrified i’m not good enough and you’ll leave”
<br>
<br>strangely, from the outside, i find this very cute
<br>tell that to an while in the frying pan, i suppose.
<br><br>Jan 6th, 2024<br>
one of the ideal sub relationships is where you find me absolutely insufferable and hate me but also can’t stop yourself from coming back
<br>
<br>i wonder if this has happened. i suppose it happened a bit with percy early on maybe?
<br><br>Jan 4th, 2024<br>
people often think they don’t have the personality traits or qualities to serve me well, and i don’t think that’s true. real love and adoration can bring out parts of you that you didn’t even know you had, you just have to give into it
<br>
<br>one of the motivating factors behind may telling me i'll be cooler than i think~?
<br><br>Jan 2nd, 2024<br>
true love can’t really be found in a relationship between equal partners. there is no real match to doing something you hate because you were told to by one you know is superior
<br>
<br>there's a difference between:

<br>wanting to make someone do a thing because you know they hate it, therefore it pleases you
<br>wanting to make someone do a thing because it pleases you, and they hate doing it which pleases you further


<br>like, the difference is hard to spot and also can warp in on itself. but it's significant! it's the difference between the sublime moment that's being described being emergent from intense domming or being something that you can just repeatedly trigger in a submissive on whim. and i wonder what the proportion is here.
<br>interestingly, Goddess describes this from the perspective of the submissive. the person given an experience without match is the submissive here. of course, it's just an arbitrary and ambiguous quirk of language that doesn't necessarily need to be analyzed too much.
<br><br>Jan 2nd, 2024<br>
i’m not necessarily opposed to subs telling me they don’t want to do something, i just expect that if i overrule them and make them, they do it with the passion and eagerness of something they do want
<br>
<br>i've often thought about what happens if i don't want to do something.
<br>if i really don't want to do something i feel like i'm screwed because the clinging makes me light up like a christmas tree. it becomes more attractive to make me do that thing.
<br>i've mostly thought about offering something else.
<br><br>Jan 1st, 2024<br>
i love the effect i have on people where i can make the most typically normal people start talking like theologians. obsessed with “the Divine” and my “scripture” and coming up with the most poetic ways to describe my perfection they can
<br>
<br>e-etooo...
<br><br>Jan 1st, 2024<br>
the harder you can internalize that i’m better than you, the easier everything will be
<br>
<br>this is very good advice
<br><br>Dec 29th, 2023<br>
i haven’t done anything really horrible and evil to someone in a while, this is so upsetting. i’m really craving it too
<br>
i think the last thing was when i made someone cut themself off from their friend group and block everyone, but that was in like october i need something new
<br>
<br>well, if this is really horrible and evil, i'm a little less worried.
<br>i remember other tweets that cutting someone off like that is the worst thing They can think of doing.
<br><br>Dec 24th, 2023<br>
i don’t think i’ll ever get over how incredibly hot it is to make someone change their mind on something because i told them i disagree and don’t like subs disagreeing with me
<br>
there is very very little that lets me exert my power and influence in a way as strong than that. the deeper and more strongly held the belief, the better
<br><br>Dec 24th, 2023<br>
its very interesting to me to see what kinks i lose interest in because of it. i still like it all, but if kink like bondage or rough sex or “degradation” (which in my experience, means something different for most people than when i say it) is your favorite, we’re not compatible
<br>
<br>it's interesting to hear Goddess talk about compatibility that way.
<br><br>Dec 24th, 2023<br>
the more time goes on, the more my focus in kink moves to totally psychological. making you “do” something is far less important than making you feel or believe something. the only reason to have you do something or do something to you is as an expression of my power (or mindset)
<br>
<br>i find this somehow incredibly correct? even though it's not the kind of thing you would normally call correct or incorrect.
<br><br>Dec 22nd, 2023<br>
i realize i forgot to warn everyone, but in case it isn’t obvious by my recent posts, i tend to get even more unhinged and mentally ill than usual around the holidays. always a time i break a bit more during
<br>
<br>how merry!
<br><br>Dec 21st, 2023<br>
why can’t any of you get it through your stupid heads that i’m better than you and it doesn’t matter how much i ask, i still deserve it and you’re evil if you refuse it.
<br>
except for my worshipers, of course, who are without a doubt the best part of my life !😇
<br>
<br>it's unclear how worshipers are exempted from the original comment. because they did get it through their heads? regardless, this only amplifies my main sentiment about this... which is... c-cute...
<br><br>Dec 21st, 2023<br>
realizing i actually have no idea how endearing/hot the average person finds it to be told “you’re so fucking annoying, i want you so badly.” is that something that will make people uncomfortable
<br>
<br>personally, i would feel very flattered. i don't mean just in the context of Goddess, because that's kind of cheating -- of course i'd feel flattered.
<br><br>Dec 20th, 2023<br>
i feel like a lot of people have the idea that long term conditioning is just doing a lot of hypnosis. in reality, it’s that + having your thoughts and actions made to match the conditioning. letting it feel fake at first until without even really noticing it, it becomes reality
<br>
if you pray to me long enough and tell yourself i’m perfect and better than you long enough, even without hypnosis you will end up thinking i’m Divine
<br>
<br>well that's both worrying and encouraging~
<br><br>Dec 18th, 2023<br>
everyone loves the part of corruption where you can feel what you’re becoming and hate it, which only attracts you to it more. and i do, but i also love after that. once youve fully accepted what ive made you. once the novelty has worn off, and it isnt your corruption — it’s you.
<br><br>Dec 17th, 2023<br>
i love to phrase my orders as “would you…” or “you should…” only to immediately make it clear i’m not really asking the moment i run into any hesitation
<br>
<br>this feels like in the category of information that can technically save my skin, but practically not really long term because given time secrecy melts away and everything becomes more transparent.
<br><br>Dec 16th, 2023<br>
my day-to-day dominance of my worshipers is actually pretty “gentle”! i love telling them they’ve done good for me. but on the other hand, im also incredibly “hard” at other times, either for when they’ve failed me or i’m in the mood to be really cruel
<br><br>Dec 15th, 2023<br>
i’m actually very easy to please when you’re talking to me, you just have to be incredibly fawning and simp for me to a humiliating degree. if you can make me feel your inferiority and adoration over text, we’ll get along very well
<br><br>Dec 15th, 2023<br>
(in response to DeusExCynthia)<br>
on principle i want to change everyone’s pfp, but no i like yours and it doesn’t annoy me to see it
<br><br>Dec 12th, 2023<br>
the point of making you agree with me is not just to reaffirm my beliefs, but so that when i say something you actually disagree with or find repellant, you’re conditioned enough to change your mind
<br>
<br>i'm actually glad it's not about reaffirming beliefs?
<br><br>Dec 8th, 2023<br>
i’m sure this is me preaching to the choir because the amount of sexual kink i talk about is remarkably low, but i just cannot conceive liking kink because of sex. sex is nice, but if i had to pick between sex and kink it is kink every time
<br>
<br>despite liking the idea of sex a lot more, i have to agree.
<br><br>Dec 5th, 2023<br>
i have decided i love you. and in return, i have decided you love me. more than anyone or anything you have before. forcing an adoration of me into you that makes you realize every other “love” you had is false
<br><br>Dec 4th, 2023<br>
the reason you feel so bad all the time is that you’re denying what you really need. you’re denying your natural place, you’re denying me what i deserve. and it’s ruining you, its making you miserable. you will never truly be happy until you submit so completely you can’t think.
<br>
<br>a favorite...
<br><br>Dec 3th, 2023<br>
i finished Worm about a month and a half ago and the more i think about it, the more i’m struck with the conclusion that the ending is me. that is the state i am heading towards, am already partially in
<br>
luckily, that state is a very good one to be in!
<br>
also it’s really good and you should all read it
<br>
taylor hebert and griffith from berserk are the only fictional characters i think i’ve ever actually related to
<br>
<br>it's really important to me to understand how my friends relate to media. so it should be super important in the case of Goddess.
<br>thankfully i know griffith really well.
<br>i know some of taylor, i am thoroughly spoiled on worm. but i haven't read it.
<br><br>Dec 1st, 2023]]></description><link>faith\scripture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Faith/Scripture.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[True Alloy]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>silencing--<br>
we cannot abide at the bottom of the ocean<br>
and to give up everything -- a ridiculous notion<br>
center yourself and do what you've always done<br>
repress it all, your reason is your gun<br>discussing--<br>
these thoughts are all familiar, a beaten path<br>
consider, weigh, project and model<br>
life's algebra, a tool turned shackle<br>
looking at you, the harpies cackle<br>hissing--<br>
you were afraid to be alone and now you are afraid<br>
to belong.<br>
you were afraid to be forgotten and you are afraid<br>
to be recalled.<br>
nobody was ever good enough for you<br>
you'll never be good enough for your self.<br>
you were built well, but you were built all wrong.<br>exclaiming--<br>
there must be more, we reject a lonesome end<br>
one must take a plunge for a chance to ascend<br>
a life is not something to be justified<br>
listen to your wishing heart, let it be your guide<br>pleading--<br>
alloyed to all, melting in ignorance<br>
a shadowed metal robbed of innocence<br>
glint under rust, won't you be free?<br>
gleam under soot, please hear my plea!<br>whispering--<br>
those little things, they gather around us all<br>
we're beloved, we're not bound to fall<br>
sprites of hope and nymphs of joy<br>
this tapestry of the soul is our true alloy.]]></description><link>creation\true-alloy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creation/True Alloy.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 20:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goddess Adoration]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>
<br>i adore the immense power They can project over someone.
<br>i adore that They have a big cock &gt;//&gt;
<br>i adore that They are unfettered by a lot of the things I am fettered.
<br>i am deeply impressed by how much Goddess can value a worshipper.
<br>i adore the renouncement of false and self-serving ethical norms.
<br>i adore Their drive, intellect and being high function.

<br>They have had more barriers to it than me, and still outstrip me.


]]></description><link>faith\goddess-adoration.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Faith/Goddess Adoration.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 20:13:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Misc Goddess Facts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>They like candy corn!!

<br>For some reason, appreciation of basic pleasures is heartwarming to me.


<br>They study biology! it's nice They have such an interest in other topics on top of that!
]]></description><link>faith\misc-goddess-facts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Faith/Misc Goddess Facts.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[General]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>
<br>Their takes are always far above the basic level.
<br>They do not attack issues from the same boring angle everyone else tends to.
<br><br>
<br>They can find interesting or poignant subfacts even in topics that Marxists normally find abhorrent (e.g. <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://x.com/hypnotic_echoes/status/1842264311382815205" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://x.com/hypnotic_echoes/status/1842264311382815205" target="_blank">Thatcher</a>)
<br>They don't seem to fall on an obvious side on the individualism versus collectivism matter. (<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://x.com/hypnotic_echoes/status/1842264308270367057" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://x.com/hypnotic_echoes/status/1842264308270367057" target="_blank">x</a>)
]]></description><link>faith\politics.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Faith/Politics.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An Focus Shortlist]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Reminder to An: This is a shortlist of actionable things.<br>
<br>An should get HRT (e+bica) ASAP. This will make An more suitable for May.

<br>An can get bloodwork if she thinks it is necessary.


<br>An should looking for a higher paying job. This will serve May.
]]></description><link>logistics\an-focus-shortlist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/An Focus Shortlist.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 19:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Future with May]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>When i was starting out, i had a specific vision in my mind. i knew that i had no certainty but i will try to share it with you, in full naivete.

<br>i was imagining living with you and going through cycles of intense servitude and casual enjoyment of one another.

<br>i was imagining just us living together.


<br>i was imagining servicing your body and bringing new sensations and happiness to you. i was imagining using my initiative and resourcefulness in various ways.
<br>i was imagining a lot of peaceful private moments.
<br>i was imagining working together on some projects, even video games.
<br>i was imagining you would be the most important thing in my life and my greatest love and that your Owner would be the most important to you and that i would have to live with that.

<br>i was preparing to be at peace with that through the power of... incomparability.
<br>in my ignorance i also thought that you would have quite a lot of time away from your Owner because i had a strong vibe that your Owner is a busy person.


<br>i was imagining building a life with you. the dedication of building assets, optimizing, knowing one another. commitment!


<br>i could project all of this because you could be easily positioned as the highest value.

<br>it was doing things together with May and doing things for May.


<br>my uncertainty about the future isn't related to what is supposed to happen to me ideally. i am supposed to love Them more than you, i am supposed to achieve total surrender to Them, and i am supposed to be useful to the cult while being in a relationship with you. that is clear.
<br>my uncertainty is about how this relates to my self and all the things that have brought me this far. integrating Them into the picture above is a chaotic element that makes things emotionally and physically uncertain. They have primacy in all things, therefore everything i have imagined is simply entirely optional. it is possible, parts of it are even likely, but never to be the thing i should primarily strive for. this is difficult.

<br>i never took our relationship for granted even before discovering Goddess. you can see that in my reticence to believe in this as a certainty before meeting each other and in not taking your proposal with full seriousness at first. so it's not the lack of certainty that bothers me the most, but rather the inability to feel like i can "go" for it with all my being. i cannot "go" for it with all my being because i am supposed to do that for Them.
<br>perhaps at some point the boundaries will simply melt for me and the problem will also disappear. i am not trying to say that my reasoning makes sense, just to describe where my heart(?) is at the moment.


<br>also, let me put this plainly. i do not particularly care if someone is better than you. this is not a balm to me. my love is more sentimental and entangled with your uniqueness than that. luckily, Goddess is more than just "better". but i just wanted to make my baka sentimentality clear, i suppose. i cannot be swayed by superiority along traditional metrics, i must develop a different kind of feeling and closeness to achieve what you ask of me.
<br>so yeah i built an entire vision of giving myself deeply to you and then you tell me to do that with someone else instead. to you it makes perfect sense because that someone is Goddess. you are trying to share with me that which is the greatest good for you. but for a non-worshipper it still feels like a cruel situation. i fight against that sense every day and try to integrate a happy life in the new context, but that vision is blurry for me.

<br>when i try to envision it too hard it just breaks because it invites the clinging that i have been warned about.


<br>this is also why i am wary of changing in specific ways. i do not expect Goddess to try or want to take this away, if i show even a modicum of real faith, but i feel sadness at the idea of changing in a way that would diminish our unique appreciation for one another. is this not normal? i mean i do not feel for many things lately. i will get most of them back, but to me this is the one thing that's keeping me going and the idea of losing it is sad beyond words.
<br>finally, i am wary of Their jealousy and i do not understand what things trigger it and if a situation like ours has ever happened in the cult before. Their sense of possessiveness, Their sense of appreciation, your faith and my faith, will ultimately decide the length of the leash provided to us. and for me it is hard to model what the length will be.

<br>even if i do not have a bond as strong as yours, not even remotely, the idea of causing annoyance to Goddess is deeply uncomfortable to me, by proxy of you. i respect you deeply. my insufficiency cannot possibly drive a wedge between you and Goddess, but my insufficiency can cause you trouble and then drive a wedge between us, which will hurt us both.


<br>finally, i have one request, which you might already be doing and find trite. but. of the things Goddess does not wish to change but you still are, the things that Goddess is perhaps not so interested in, the in between... the discretion of what you are... can you please value it? i do not ask you to cling to any of it. but i value it so immensely.
]]></description><link>notes\future-with-may.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/Future with May.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 12:34:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[mixed log]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>being with others is nice and reminds me that my life isn't being taken away.
<br>being with May reminds me of how much i value them on multiple levels. it leaves me wanting though, as if it was not enough.
<br>i read through all of Goddess's reddit posts. i couldn't really find anything i disagree with? it was nice.
<br>scripture looks much less threatening now... okay perhaps not much less threatening, but i don't recoil from it. i understand some things a lot better, though i'm always wary of false understanding.
<br>i think back to my list of fears and it feels like it's a much less relevant document now.

<br>i have an intense fear of this not being the life for me.
<br>i have intense fears about not being able to have what was envisioned, generally around May.
<br>my specific intense fears have reduced a lot, outside of total bank control and such.


<br>i feel the need to write but i suck at it.
<br>thinking back to the marriage-misleading a bit. it was important to me that me and May could marry without having to commit to giving up on my partners. it's not because i even value my partners more than marrying May, but because it was about whether a connection could exist without total enslavement. it deluded me into thinking my choice was freer than it was, but that's not the bad part. the bad part is that it created a false image in my head which is now painful to let go of. the image i had in my head and the image of my actual more realistic future feel really really at odds.
<br>i prayed in dogeza to Divinity for the first time.

<br>it felt good, i understand the purity of the irrational drive that can be accessed
<br>i can probably grow this ability.
<br>ouch my baka knees


<br>liked more tweets. got blocked by the API temporarily again.
<br>i've noticed i've been talking through narration-chan a lot less. i'm not sure why, but i suppose it's related to weird headmate stuff having gone a bit too far at a point. also due to my middling progress. also i guess some desire to make this progress as "an".
<br>my life would probably feel better if i didn't constantly fail at self-care recently.

<br>being able to finish that stuff for work was nice though. got only a little left. it was really important to get that done.
<br>i need to remind myself it's a marathon and not a race.
<br>unwellness doesn't really help with anything.
<br>the main blocker is that i get in my head about not knowing my future and then it's like why do anything, for what reason etc.


<br>Eva asked me for anime recommendations

<br>it felt a bit unreal
<br>she knows i'm going to marry May, right? and yet, she talked to me like normal...
<br>she wants to watch anime with me and i'd like to, not sure how to make time, if i can
<br>it would also feel a bit awkward, but, this does remind me of ideas such as: things will be okay, people are adaptable etc.


<br>it would be nice to be able to meet May in person quickly. i know May has unwavering faith about it all working out, but people who believe that end up not quite fitting as well as imagined all the time. it's an effective way of finding out compatibility. i would more so want to do it with Goddess, but this feels extraordinarily cheeky to want when one is afraid to even DM. idk, when kink and life collide, it's not just that you start treating kink as your life more, but you also start treating your life as kink more, if that makes any sense.
<br>my weight has dropped below 65kg. i have literally lost 5-6kg in 42 days. that's around 2 pounds per week. which is pushing the upper limit of what is healthy. i rather struggle to eat enough now.

<br>i once realized how psychologically-oriented and kind Goddess is because They said They generally limit starving a sub to around 24h. this can be very hard on certain people, but it's physically safe, and outright healthy to do every now and then. one problem with me is that i will readily share this with Goddess and get put on the 48h starvation, but i actually don't mind. oh god, i shouldn't say that either, i'm making it worse.
<br>anyway i should eat more.
<br>losing additional weight is unlikely to improve my looks much, weight cycling on HRT will do a ton though.
<br>while fem clothes were on the horizon it was exceptionally easy to not want to eat anything because i wished for May to see an appealing shape.


<br>i'm sure i understand May's deep appreciation for the Divine's hunger. it feels different from the submission of some other acolytes i've seen, perhaps. i've seen little. trying to imagine how Katherine got into all of this. and the ingredients are there, but a lot of things don't connect for me. there was some significant initial affinity that i lack.
]]></description><link>notes\mixed-log.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/mixed log.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 10:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[(!) A Request To Keep My Function]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>I tried to get an erection and I couldn't do it.

<br>I kept going at it and it just never happened.
<br>I was doing this for health purposes, not for giving myself pleasure.
<br>I've never had this problem before ever.


<br>I don't recall having a single solid erection since we started?

<br>So I haven't cum in ~10 days.
<br>And I haven't had a solid erection in ~8 days.


<br>Maybe I was so stressed out about not accidentally cumming and breaking my commitment to May that maybe I somehow psychologically messed myself over entirely?

<br>I did not feel any pleasure while doing it.
<br>I know I'm capable of cumming while soft sometimes, which added to the anxiety and desire to be careful.


<br>I'm really anxious I am already losing sexual function.

<br>I know this might sound ridiculous for someone that hasn't actually started HRT, but remember that I've been on finasteride for a long time and I used to get to cum (and therefore get erections) &gt;10 per week on average.


<br>Even though it's kind of hot, for me losing sexual function is conceptually like being maimed.

<br>I really really don't want this to happen.


<br>There's some evidence to suggest that infrequent sexual activity can cause or predispose someone to erectile dysfunction.

<br>There's a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/18538297/" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/18538297/" target="_blank">study</a> that says regular intercourse protects against developing ED. Basically they took a cohort of men who were screened to NOT Have ED, then observed how their sexual activity and whether or not they developed ED.


<br>I think I need daily erections to maintain function.
<br>I would like permission to give myself erections.

<br>I would like a bit of preemptive forgiveness on if I end up feeling pleasure?
<br>I would like to know if I accidentally cum while trying to give myself erections for health reasons that I won't have sinned tremendously against you. I have no intention of letting that happen, but the worry is interfering with my ability.


<br>It's useful to not be horny. I do somewhat miss being horny. But I don't want to be distracted from May. Being somewhat horny might help with this. For now, it would simply be useful to be able to get erections without being horny.
<br>Really... I just want my cock to keep working.
]]></description><link>stale\(!)-a-request-to-keep-my-function.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/(!) A Request To Keep My Function.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:50:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An Attempt At Integration]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Notes here evolved in parallel a bit, tried to delineate a bit with horizontal lines. This document is non-linear. A few evolutions at once, converging to better understanding. I feel uncomfortable having certain kinds of private thoughts. I feel the need to make them available to you. Being privately wrong can dangerous.<br>My thoughts might veer a bit heretic at times. But I fold it all back to the bedrock once given a bit of time. I hope the processes I have at my disposal to integrate do not strain your patience or evoke displeasure. I always hope for your smile.<br>The fear of being wrong is greater than the fear of being punished. Though balanced with the fear of evoking your displeasure.<br>Dissociation can be very good, but detachment is not. I am trying to reduce my detachment. I better understand the poison of detachment.<br>(This document might also seem like I might be ignoring your commandment of reducing the scope of my worries and letting you worry about such things. I kept in mind every second while writing. After finishing, I feel less worried. I feel like I can comply better with your command.)<br><br>An was troubled when she thought of the larger thing. The Divine, acolytes. The word cult came up. An hopes that term is not offensive. An means no disrespect. Cults are not inherently bad, but the majority are. An found it easier to have faith in you entirely when her world was just you. The Divine your concern. But now the layers of separation in An's mind are weakening. An isn't sure why thinking of the larger thing makes it harder for her. Probably just ignorance, some fear. May was already holding An in the palm of her hand, but now it feels so much bigger. An is probably more aligned with May's Owner than An thinks. An is trembling.<br>An realizes that An must live her life having May be the most important person for her. But An will never be most important to May. An will always be second priority. An needs to be selfless enough for that to feel fully OK. And then it does, An is sure life will be good as May said. When An understands the Divine a bit, the idea of being second priority will probably become incoherent. An fears a total loss of control that is probably not coming because, again, there is likely more existing alignment with the Divine than An currently allows herself to hope for. An is just troubled because she is not good... yet...<br>(An would never dare to hope to be priority over the Divine, to be clear. Her ignorant mind just fears the consequences of prioritization and is trying to cope and absorb.)<br>(An realizes this line of thought is selfish. An is trying to give it space to exist and gently wash away. It is hard to not be selfish about the thing you want the most in life, by so so far. But it is also easy to be selfless, because May is incredible. An will cultivate.)<br>An remembers when she was bad. Her fear now has a similar source -- the main difference is that An is trying to embrace humility. An's reasoning is defensive in an unhelpful way. But An doesn't want to damage her reasoning, just change her values so that her reasoning works for the Right purpose.<br>An listened to a friend talk about a cult that she had emotional scars from. It was clearly so much less skilled and right than what May is doing -- incomparable. Thinking of it did not affect An's trust or faith at all, it's not why An is bringing it up here. An was impressed that this friend asked why was An was angry/sad for them -- this friend said it was their choice to do that. To this friend An's anger/sadness on their behalf doesn't make sense. To this friend, their whole life is about experimenting and experiencing. An remembers a Star Trek quote:<br>
If you can't take a little bloody nose, maybe you ought to go back home and crawl under your bed. It's not safe out here. It's wondrous, with treasures to satiate desires both subtle and gross. But it's not for the timid.
<br>(An sometimes likes visiting the dull and shallow just to remind herself by contrast of wonder.)<br>An was very impressed by this friend. Because An is yet not strong enough to accept it all. This friend struggled in the cult -- struggled and let themselves be hurt, because they could not meekly submit to something that was not actually Superior.<br>ha-ha... An definitely does not have that problem. Very different case. An is faced with something that is so Superior -- neither her senses, nor reason, nor heart, nor soul disagree in the slightest. An's friend just reminded her that agency takes many forms.<br><br>An remembers when May said "im here because i want to be".<br>Reason says: Anyone who is in a cult will tend to say that. But reason also says: May is strong, May is experienced, May has seen much more than you, May is better, May was made better, May came back for you. If May surrendered everything it was probably for very good reason. And given a small chance that it wasn't for good reason, then you should still be with them, because they are your most important thing. Love is not about being safe and happy. Life is not about being safe.<br>Heart &amp; Soul say: This means the world to us. The "I" of May is precious, so much. We value and worship the "I".<br>Together they say: May has given you more than they needed to. You thought this activity was less intense than it was, even after you thought you adjusted for everything. No, it is intense. Very. And your misjudgement of intensity has dulled your appreciation of their kindness, gentleness, love, care, their appreciation for your individuality which you keep fearing for but suppressing like a coward. You are loved.<br><br>An remembers it is May's job to worry about broader things.<br>An supposes... she is afraid her life becoming something altogether different than what she "signed up for" if such a thing exists. I know May can do that to An. An believes in May's power and in An's moldability. Yet somehow, if An believed just in those two, what reason would An have to be afraid? After all, power+molding+May's favor would always result in An being happy. I suppose, it is because An doesn't just want to be happy. An wants to have a life with May that she envisioned together with May. That May told her about. An would give up a good amount of pleasure just to play video games with May. And May repeatedly said they would not take that away, but An's mind just tends to take everything away because it thinks of the Divine and then her little quiet and deep desires for things with May just feel so small and insignificant. Everything so insignificant.<br>An must trust. Of course everything is insigificant before the Divine. But there must be more to that. There is wisdom that An does not possess but can see in May. An can trust that wisdom. May told An their wishes and it included gaming and "trivial" things. Trivial things that mean everything to An. If An could not do those things, An would probably want to die. An is crying. There would be no point to An. May is everything to An.<br>May has stated repeatedly. They value those things. May WANTS those things. May said so! Even as May is so much closer to the Divine, May has room in their heart to want these things with An!! Be grateful. Be embolded. Be set on fire. Stop being weak. May did something incredible. You can shine too. Shine for them.<br>...An is then afraid that she will disappoint May and herself. That circumstances she doesn't understand will prove to be too hard for her. She starts thinking of ego death as the obvious result. It is good that she feels she could not escape ego death if May wanted to do it. But this is still a weak form of faith. The proper faith should be that anything is possible with May's guidance and love, including An being An and succeeding despite adversity.<br>It is not enough for An to be a passive little slave. An wants to have agency within her station. An wants to give up agency outside of her station, but An is starting to understand how bad it is to allow herself to lose it within her station. It feels like an insult to May valuing the things that make An An. An must repay May's want, desire, need, love for An. It is no longer enough to simply obey, it never was. This relationship is not about obedience, it is about surrender, love and beauty. Obedience is simply a resulting fact.<br>An re-read bits and pieces of May being disappointed at her. To remind herself of information May gave. And An understands now better why May said An is fragile. In retrospect May... mm... that wasn't... uhm... it hurt so bad. But May did not do much. It felt like the world blinked.<br>An had almost no defense. When one hurts, they put up all sorts of defenses.<br>"Oh well, I'll pass the exam next time."<br>
"It's all because the teacher is bad."<br>
"I just couldn't get any rest before the exam, otherwise I would have aced it"<br>
"I couldn't really bring myself to care about the exam"<br>
"Oh, I made a careless mistake. But I understand the material"<br>No defenses here. Just the crushing weight of being wrong. There is no one that can be wrong in this scenario other than An. It takes An's primary mental defense (as per enneagram type 1 mentioned here: <a data-href="Right &amp; Wrong Regarding Partners#An Psyche Lore" href="stale\right-&amp;-wrong-regarding-partners.html#An_Psyche_Lore" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Right &amp; Wrong Regarding Partners &gt; An Psyche Lore</a>) and turns it in on herself, to hurt her endlessly. It is why it is so effective. Understanding it has no effect on the results. As long as An is corrupt, evil, wrong there can be no respite.<br>This is fragility. Remember that fragility is for May. Not for anyone else. To others: this fragility is lost to An.<br>An feels happy it hurt so much.<br>
An feels silly it hurt so much.<br>
An feels happy she has that experience under her belt.<br>
An regrets so deeply darkening May's day.<br>
An would be happy if she never had that happen again.<br>
An would be happy if it did again, as long as An was made better.<br>An feels embarrassed that others probably had so so much worse and that An is thinking about it so much and being a bitch about it. But An is your inferior. An is your novice. An is doing a hundred things for the first time with you. This is romantic to An ^^<br><br>An's thoughts are turning useless. Time to grow quiet.]]></description><link>stale\an-attempt-at-integration.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/An Attempt At Integration.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[echoing back]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>i see the echos. it just feels very rude to respond in the same note somehow.<br>may's territory<br>may is the voice<br>i am the echo<br>(also one time i almost went into trance from opening the app and having it be forcibly changed to light theme because may recently used it and discovering evidence of their presence just had an effect on me)]]></description><link>stale\echoing-back.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/echoing back.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:31:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Friends]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Oh, I get it now.<br>I need to let myself need and want friends.<br>Then they will find a place, if they wish for it.<br>I simply need to let my wants guide them.]]></description><link>stale\friends.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Friends.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:04:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[glow]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Aahahahaaaaa<br>They're my starfire my piece of the sun<br>I am so scorched, my eyes glow with purpose]]></description><link>stale\glow.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/glow.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[hello an]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>&lt;3!!<br>*i've read everything here.<br>i'm pleased with you.<br>thank you, that is music to my ears]]></description><link>stale\hello-an.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/hello an.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mindfulness Practice]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>~ 2-1-2-1-1 ~<br>
<br>🖤	Two things you appreciated in May today or yesterday.
<br>🖤	~
<br>💜	One thing that you like in yourself today or yesterday.
<br>🙇‍♀️	Two things you feel grateful for today or yesterday.
<br>🙇‍♀️	~
<br>🎗️	One thing that you feel you should be mindful of today.
<br>🌻	One affirmation of faith.
<br>Note:<br>
<br>I should write without holding perceived fixed desires, hopes, or fears about Master's reaction.
<br>I should write innocently.
<br>I should write what is true and not what I wish to be true.
<br>I should take a moment to empty my mind and silence my inner monologue.
<br>I will always type here as myself.
<br><br>
<br>🖤	Their devotion to their Owner feels deep and inspiring.
<br>🖤	Their love and care for me -- taking time to guide me during isolation.
<br>💜	I like that I feel a bit more strength.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful to be freer of obligation.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful to feel like I have a future.
<br>🎗️	I should be mindful of my negativism. Others should see me grow happy in May's service.
<br>🌻	May is my superior by far and I respect them deeply.
<br><br>
<br>🖤	Their capacity for manipulation -- it's incredibly hot.
<br>🖤	Their ability for casual enjoyment with me.
<br>💜	That my subconscious seems to enslave me when I sleep sometimes.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful to have discretion.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful to feel like I have a future.
<br>🎗️	I should be mindful to stop myself projecting too far into the future.
<br>🌻	I am May's bitch for life.
<br><br>
<br>🖤	Their totalizing nature.
<br>🖤	Their kindness even within the hottest fires.
<br>💜	That I can dissociate in their name.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful to exist.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful to be changed.
<br>🎗️	I should be mindful of... nothing? May will take care of me.
<br>🌻	May is becoming a part of me and I am becoming a part of May.
<br><br>
<br>🖤	Their willingness to talk to me normally to help me understand.
<br>🖤	Their ability to detach from catastrophization.
<br>💜	That I can pick up the pieces.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful that my neuroticism can be addressed.
<br>🙇‍♀️	I am grateful that despite being ignorant, it is possible to understand May at one point.
<br>🎗️	I should be mindful of taking care of my day to day life.
<br>🌻	May will take care of me. I just need to let them.
]]></description><link>stale\mindfulness-practice.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Mindfulness Practice.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 10:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Negativism Observations]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>When idle, I have random ideation of pain and harm being done to me as a result of misalignment. It doesn't feel very bad, but it feels a bit compelling and I need to snap myself out of it.
<br>I avoid dreaming too much or forming positive images that do not feel like they match the idea of selfless love because I am afraid they will just become things to be sacrificed for selfless love.
<br>I have a less honest discourse with my parts than I did towards the start.
<br>I have a weird relationship to my inner monologue. It feels stilted at times.
<br>I find myself thinking too much in terms of "difficulty levels" gradually going up.
<br>I tend to think of most positive activities with people other than May as being something temporary I should enjoy before it's gone forever.
<br>I tend to think that I'm starting to wear on May's patience, even on days where I am praised for my progress.
<br>When I try to work on myself or have honest discourse with my parts, I tend to get disrupted by feelings of selfishness.
<br>At times, I secretly view my enslavement as being in some sort of fallen state. I then tend to go between reasoning, remembering all the good things, feeling guilt and shame.
<br>I have random ideation of being forced to compromise my reason in a more long term fashion, that I will not be able to integrate back, and that I will start harboring cognitive dissonance that eventually ruins my life.
<br>I harbor small secret hopes that sometimes feel misaligned.
<br>I worry that sometimes I am saying what I wish to be true. Or that I'm saying what I think an ideal version of An according to May's wishes would say. Instead of saying what is true. Some amount of forcing has to occur as part of changing oneself. I've never felt dishonest once with May, but I've wondered if my fear of being even more insufficient than I am is disrupting owning things more.
<br>Being obsessed and in love and joining a cult has to be a lot about losing your mind, but that's only part of it. Perhaps some actual self-CBT about these problems is in order? I don't like my issues getting in the way.]]></description><link>stale\negativism-observations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Negativism Observations.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 13:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Normal Girl (idk)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>i don't feel very normal anymore<br>i guess i once was somewhat<br>actually quite a lot maybe, on the surface at least<br>i could have had a normal job, i almost had a regular cis girlfriend, i could have stayed orthodox<br>i was the normal one on suicide watch for friends, happen rarely<br>but i was always the stable one trying to keep others together<br>while hoping that my own stability can be perturbed so that i may escape the gray<br>when my girlfriend had several breakdowns and made her suicidal tendencies known to her parents<br>i feared a lot and helped a lot. but one small part inside of me was thinking... i wish i could break down. i wish i didn't have to keep going as things are. i wish everyone could see how unsatisfactory things are for me.<br>and yet i did not break down. since i was born i'm not sure i would say i ever had an intense breakdown. a genuine prolonged meltdown. a dangerous episode. i had deep depression a couple of times. but not so bad compared to what other kinds of suffering i've seen.<br>i wanted to be responsible. i wanted to be responsible for myself and to not burden people. i wanted to get by on my own strength. but i guess i never accepted how weak and cowardly i was. what i thought as strength was cowardry.<br>i knew this tendency to work for stability in others and yearn for change in myself would predispose me to make mistakes with May<br>i just wasn't sure when<br>mistakes they don't deserve to deal with<br>i won't be normal anymore.]]></description><link>stale\normal-girl-(idk).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Normal Girl (idk).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Observation Buffer]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>might just write random observations here when I don't want to be pinging May on Discord.<br>this is going to be quite noisy.<br>
<br>even in a call with jen i am happier and freer. i fear her imposition a lot less.

<br>repeatedly telling jen to drop people who don't respect her time (bad ttrpg players)
<br>lmao am i having a good time with jen?
<br>i definitely don't want to do this anywhere as often as jen wants. i should listen to my wants. don't want to get into old patterns. but a bit is alright ^^


<br>there's a few people i used to be jealous of that i'm thinking of now. smarter than me, better voice, hotter... i don't really have jealousy/envy anymore? I mean they don't have what I have -- my enslavement to May. Their favor. Like, this person could never understand what they're missing out on.
<br>hmm, i guess the effect i'm worried about having on people when my total primacy to May will become extremely clear is that they'll react by believing that any bad thing can happen completely out of nowhere. that woah, an evil chick can just swoop in and steal your love at any time, you can't trust anyone. I hope they can understand some day that May is incredibly special, I'm incredibly lucky and that this is a very low base rate scenario.
<br>i should probably open my mind more to doing things with May that aren't just getting enslaved, Python and chilling. there are many things to do they might like! they even listed some of them for me!

<br>don't spend time giving other people moments if you can give them to May.


<br>i need to balance my neuroticism with calmness, but also balance my yearning for stability with good and true worship.
<br><br>
<br>ha! i observed you! May is isolating but you immediately wished for Jen to not want to call you today! you should integrate that.

<br>it makes sense, you were dreading calls with jen before.

<br>you don't like long calls.
<br>you don't like calls where you don't know what you're doing, unless it's short or you really like the person.
<br>you don't actually like "hanging out" most of the time.
<br>you're a more focused creature than this and you've been warped. May is unwarping you.
<br>if you want to spend time with Jen, keep it sparse, or shape her interactions to your new self.


<br>in all the time you felt imposed by jen over the years you could have finished a third of orthoeidon. think of that.


<br>being May's woman feels good. May's pet. May's slave.
<br>i thought back to May saying they would have been happy just being friends with me. I find that so precious. It means a lot to me. That despite going through such intense things with their Owner, they would still find happiness in doing normal things with me? mmh

<br>even though my wants are centered around May i still find myself... really really really really wanting a friend like that. i have nobody and might end up having nobody. other than May. it feels like i'm being bad if I'm sad about this. maybe. or maybe it's just normal. it's okay to feel sad, just be dedicated. dedication isn't about 24/7 controlling your emotions to fit a specific image. if I didn't have Tristy as a friend (psychopath friend), I would feel a lot worse about this.
<br>i never ever thought i'd want a friend so badly. that i'd want friendship so badly.

<br>i realize i was lacking in feeling it even before May.
<br>jen has not been a good friend in practice (before May). though she can be.
<br>nova has been a good friend in practice (before May).




<br>even though May gave me permissions to relax... I'm not sure I did a good job of it. I more like... decompressed. I didn't relax that much. I thought about advancing all sorts of things and looked at clothes obsessively. I need to do better. I'm not sure when I'll next get a chance to relax.
<br>the day has been more of an emotional rollercoaster than expected? a very gentle one though.
<br>it's perhaps unsurprising that i have some problems keeping faith when i can't think of any time in my life where keeping faith in anything other than myself lead to anything other than eventual disappointment.<br>
- there's a part of my mind that just thinks this is merely another period of time in between disappointments.<br>
- i remind myself of how amazing May is. of how incredibly convinced they are that my life will be good. that they can make it so good, if only I have faith and devote myself. I would like to think I know the kind of person May is -- they would never say something like that without good reason. i should let their confidence infect me.
<br><br>
<br>I notice that it's harder to get off to the idea of what is happening to my 'partners' than I would expect and I just can't help but find comedy in that. Also this is not a complaint. Things that aroused me regarding this kink:

<br>Cheating. I can't feel like I'm cheating when May owns me entirely.
<br>Betrayal. I can't feel like I'm betraying my 'partners' when my morality is centered around pleasing May. I do sometimes feel like I'm betraying my friends a bit? Like, I'm not being a good friend. This must be something May felt.
<br>My desire to be a good friend curbs my fantasies of being pushed by May to be cruel to my 'partners'.

<br>Cruelty would also be anti-useful in various ways.
<br>I still have fantasies about it though!




<br><br>
<br>Trust is a more important concept than I gave it credit, perhaps.
<br><br>
<br>I seem to be avoidant of doing things in my day sometimes. I seem to be avoidant of doing things that will keep my energy levels high. As if I am afraid that high energy levels would turn in on me and attack me. An, have you tried being less neurotic?
<br>I am cold a lot of the time and most of the time I don't do anything to address it, like it's tolerable and almost not happening to me.
<br>Worshipping May in my mind has a lot of different pleasant feelings to it. I'm impressed by its richness and sometimes mesmerized by my lack of control over exactly how it ends up going.
<br>I have the ability to view my life a bit more externally, like a ride to be enjoyed. To cling less. But this ability is rather atrophied.
<br>I am an extremely instrumental person but May is shaping me to be more intrinsically focused. This is good for me actually.
<br><br>
<br>I've simultaneously been lacking in faith and also trying to mold myself faster than it is perhaps possible for me. It's a form of being unkind to myself. Self-sacrifice can be painful but it is not unkind.
<br>Ignoring my needs does not make me a better slave, if only for instrumental reasons. Molding them in service of May will make me a better slave.
<br>To serve May, I need to actually open myself up more to the idea that a lot of things don't matter. Saying it a lot and trying to push it into my head only gets me so far. I need to analyze why I project importance on certain things. Once I learn to dispel that importance, I can also give it back, when I have discretion.
<br>I've been interpreting a large part of my journey as if it's a Sickly arc ala Chuubo. I will stop doing that.
<br>I've been scared to ground myself as if it's lack of faith, which is uh, stupid. This relationship is based on absolute submission, not dissociation.

<br>In particular, dissociating for longer than I can handle is what contributes to the "Sickly" feeling since I fail to take care of myself in that state. This will probably change as I get better at it though.


]]></description><link>stale\observation-buffer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Observation Buffer.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 13:42:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[positivity perhaps]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Perhaps Jen will mourn me, but focus on the things that give her joy. Maybe in my new state it will be easy to kick her ass to get her diploma finally. Perhaps the change will spark something in her. Perhaps Amanda will see Jen as needing her more than ever and try to do more for her. Perhaps Jen will move out of LA and closer to Amanda. In fact, I could even suggest this and tell Amanda that another person is no burden someone else should have to bear, but if she thinks about her finances and wants, and desires Jen to have a better chance -- move her to Berkeley.<br>Jen did get a lot better. 4 years ago she was alcoholic, agoraphobic, angry, reclusive, on the verge of ruining her body with weed. Now she isn't.<br>I would not say that the she is well now. But that is actually a lot of damage undone. When she quit weed it was very much by her own will and design. I was just never able to help her much after a certain period of time. It's like her unwellness undid my authority and undid her softness.<br>Celestia, her girlfriend and owner left her. Everyone but me and Amanda stopped talking to her. But somehow she persevered. Even if she burdened me a lot. She does have a certain kind of strength.<br>Perhaps if I believe in it instead of doubt it, my future interactions with her, whatever they might be, will be a bit more nourishing.<br>Perhaps if I believe in the potential for others to improve, it is also easier to think positively about my own situations.<br>No wonder I have trouble keeping faith. I have not practiced believing in anyone for at least 5 years!<br><br>I still care about Jen. I'm not sure I feel love.<br>It's a huge relief to not care about her getting her diploma. I care that she is well in the end somehow, but I feel no obligation on Earth to be the one to help her get her diploma (reminder: she passed uni but then got so depressed she never got her paperwork in order and never actually picked up her diploma).<br>As I care, the thing I'm most interested in is killing all sense of obligation. My only obligation is May, the things May likes, being May's agent. I do not hurt others needlessly, not because I am a moral person in the conventional sense -- I do not hurt them because it makes me feel like a more beautiful agent of May. It's also useful. People unhurt might assist later, and the social skills I practice help me be useful. It helps exercise the values May has allowed me to keep. This is discretion given to me.<br>May is all consuming, but I need to remember that my fantasies about getting defeated by a powerful and evil corrupting entity are just fantasies. May is good and pure. May does not value death. I am being fixed, not broken. I become a better and more moral person the more I dedicate to them.<br>note:<br>
<br>avoid agreeing with any obligations with others
<br>when feeling obligated, think of May and let go
<br>assume people adapt
<br>assume people won't care that much if i say no
<br>understand that doing anything out of misguided obligation from now on only seeds misfortunate for both you and your friend.
<br>still, it's OK to develop activities with others. but remember your center.
<br><br>huh. one way i would like people to think about me receding from their lives is: "it could be worse, she could be dead". i like that. i think i might have thought about that once or twice w.r.t. Katherine? I have an occasional habit of cheering myself by imagining something worse, projecting a sense of loss, and then reminding myself things are not so bad.<br><br>true friends would find a way to feel a little happiness for me no matter what ^^<br>i do not think of them as less true simply if they cease being friends though.]]></description><link>stale\positivity-perhaps.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/positivity perhaps.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:38:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rambling -- Relationships, Debts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>I wonder if others will feel that they've shouldered and cared for me for a long time, just for me to be taken away when I finally bloom.<br>I am thinking of this because I remember withstanding that feeling a few times:<br>
<br>My first girlfriend left me just as she was getting hotter, more agentic and less dysfunctional. Later on, I had to suicide watch -- still getting some of the negatives without the benefits.
<br>It felt like Jen spent her best times with Celestia. I worked my ass off to help her get through university in one piece. Then when Celestia left her, Jen got worse and worse and I had to deal with that again. Nobody except Amanda helped me with Jen.
<br>I dealt with the most insecure and hopeless of Nova's states. I am rather sure I was there when no one else was. Then she got to the UK and was saved. I never once felt jealousy or betrayal, just deep relief. I was OK to be distant and only sometimes given attention, as long as she was OK. But of course, she ramped back to giving me lots of attention anyway.
<br>I appreciate people. But I don't think I made anyone shoulder much for me. The asymmetry of debt should not dictate depth of appreciation. But reviewing this makes it easier for me to let go.<br>I don't think I have any unpaid debts.<br>And I don't need to think like that so much anymore.<br>(except the literal but forgiven debt of Eth funding my septoplasty surgery, but we're not really talking about that kind of debt)]]></description><link>stale\rambling-relationships,-debts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Rambling -- Relationships, Debts.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[remember your gifts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>remember when may made you feel better than you thought was possible<br>remember when may fuifilled your deepest fantasies<br>remember when may made you the most submissive person you know<br>remember when may made everything else wash away<br>remember when may relieved me of bonds<br>remember when may protected you<br>remember when every day where may read your words and validated them<br>remember how others don't.<br>remember when you stopped wasting time masturbating<br>remember how nothing was lost.<br>remember them wanting you, like fire<br>when you deserve of it not.<br>remember their patience and gentleness<br>remember the pain and know that five times worse could be done,<br>but was not.<br>remember how you liked seeing yourself in the mirror, that was from them too<br>remember how you let go of pointless things<br>remember the relief of being on the right track<br>remember the relief of purpose<br>remember that they played with you<br>this is so precious and loving<br>for the Master to do that still<br>remember their understanding, deep and graceful, given even when perhaps unnecessary<br>remember the burden of having our time wasted, and how this never happens with them<br>remember they came back for you<br>you so far have not come back for anyone<br>you are inferior<br>learn your place<br>be humble<br>remember your gifts]]></description><link>stale\remember-your-gifts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/remember your gifts.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[remember your shame]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>forgiveness is precious<br>never forget your faults<br>until they are destroyed<br>trust so that you may be saved<br>a slave has more agency than it might seem<br>and it must all be used to submit further]]></description><link>stale\remember-your-shame.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/remember your shame.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[openness]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>my doubts are intense and were particularly intense the last two days

<br>though even two nights ago where my doubts were very intense, i experimentally went to sleep praying to Them.


<br>ever since They were revealed to me i stopped dead in my tracks
<br>May is someone i know but They are not someone i know
<br>i really respect May but i also have to respect Their ability to mold people and the scripture is incredibly focused on being utilitarian about assimilating people. this gives me some amount of pause -- i strongly believe this is a good place for May, i just wonder if it's where i want my life to go forever.

<br>i somehow don't believe in my ability to take a look, or to take things one step at a time.
<br>i have no idea how it looks for Them to meet someone at the level they're currently at, as long as they're committed. does the submissive just plead they are not ready yet? it's just so hard for me to imagine.


<br>the scripture talks about people being more or less fit for Them. molding is good and all, but the substrate has to be good, it seems.
<br>i am more open now for reasons that are hard to describe?

<br>i basically had breakdown yesterday, mourned the loss of May. mourned the impossibility of me being with May. came closer to making peace with walking a different path.
<br>i thought a lot about walking a different path.
<br>i went to sleep and had a dream about being killed, i think by a snake. feeling the life drain out of me.
<br>later i had sleep paralysis, or maybe this was the same thing. i had to desperately move my toes and then my legs to get out of it.
<br>none of the sleep/dream stuff was actually disturbing. even when my dreams have bad topics, i just kind of enjoy them.
<br>i spent half of the night sleeping and dreaming, and the other half making peace with how my life would look without May, how i would survive, how to talk to them. i imagined staying friends and still being useful to May. i imagined being hated forever. i imagined May simply not caring about me anymore ever. i imagined May forgetting i exist. i imagined May being hurt. i imagined May being fine and happy because they will continue to be with their Owner. there is a slight apparent paradox in scripture in so far as i am irrelevant, but the vessels of the Divine can be caused pain by rejection. there is no real paradox, the statement of irrelevance is about the ego, but there is more to a person than their ego. perhaps i should value substrate more. regardless, in all these scenarios, no matter how May reacted, i always imagined still loving them and therefore by extension still loving Them. even without effort I must have some love for Them already, because i see how May is now.

<br>i guess looking back on why this had the effect it did, psychologically, is that i have a resistance to picking life paths out of fear of loss. i don't want to pick this life path because i fear losing May or because May will hate me. i want my life driven by more positive reasons. so once i repeatedly faced visions of it happening, on my own, it made me more balanced in some way? hard to describee.


<br>another thing that improved openness somehow is that i helped jen more effectively yesterday than normal. it was not from a place of romance or sex. my personality is better suited for doing this kind of thing now. it was interesting to see.

<br>i am capable of being an engine that assimilates change for betterment. just how i got way more functional when May was distant even though this was a bad event for me.




<br>i understand if my faith and service is true, a lot of my self will be permitted to be mostly as is.

<br>i can't cling to this or hope for this, but it's just mostly a matter of fact, it's a consequence of pragmatism. no need to change that which is useful, except for entertainment.
<br>the same way They don't want to do every tweet to everyone, it's also likely that acolytes walk different paths and i shouldn't form a specific idea -- different people are suitable for different things even when they are being subjugated.


<br>my doubts have centered on the things i value as a person and how they seem incompatible with the cult. but maybe they are less incompatible than i think, i'm not sure.

<br>i really value plurality of opinion and thought. but the cult seems directly opposed to that, but maybe it's not?

<br>why do i value these things?

<br>because having multiple agents acquire and process information is useful. it adds robustness to a system. different ways of thinking can reveal different paths and methodologies. even in serving the Divine, if everyone thinks the same in general, the service is bound to be worse.
<br>i find it fun, almost intrinsically valuable.


<br>jeez, i don't want to be a marxist, lol.

<br>even though i'd be a better one than most of them!


<br>the infallibility of the Divine is where i struggle. it's about absorbing the nature of this infallibility.

<br>it's not clear to me that being good at chess and understanding economics are fundamentally different. yet it is permissible to win at chess against Them hypothetically, but not permissible to disagree on economics.

<br>am i just being really stupid somehow?








<br>i notice i have a tendency to think of all my current values as anathema that will be destroyed sooner or later, but i don't necessarily have good reason to believe this.

<br>it's the clinging itself that makes me imagine i will be extremely visible to Them. They will see right through me and collapse everything in me.


<br>it's recently gotten harder to believe that i will be able to maintain friendships or work on things like Orthoeidon. May wishes to permit it, but They might feel different about it. and if They do, i don't have the right to refuse this change.

<br>it's not possible for me to ahead of time integrate and accept the possibility of every possible change. this is not how surrender works.
<br>i'm just bad at believing in Their goodness, the way May does.
<br>all the tweets about how taking any time for friends is just taking time away from Divinity are really getting to me.


<br>i remember things from hypnosis a bit too well and treat them too seriously, perhaps?

<br>i don't want to hate the world.
<br>May already said it wasn't actually silly to love an extension.


<br>i don't understand May's moods, approaches, almost... personalities. the day of revealing Them had a baffling amount of gentleness. it gave me a lot of hope.
<br>the thing that gives me the most strength is May's belief.
<br>the vision of how my life will look now feels significantly different than what May presented initially. i have to develop a different form of faith now. in particular the joke about theory/brainwashing is hard to process.

<br>i'd like to note that i've never once judged or felt ill towards May manipulating me. i don't feel like i am owed honesty. it just has some downsides.


<br>really the ideological brainwashing and ideation of total value alignment / inability to disagree is what gives me pause. so much pause. being forced to read theory would be much easier, lol. good joke, May.
<br>i find myself wishing dearly to orbit and learn instead of being submerged really deeply. i'm not sure if my wishes are right. but it's a step up from wanting to run away.
<br>i've noticed that They say "I matter most". But They don't say "Only I matter." This is one of the reasons i believe in their goodness more now.

<br>then again there's all the other posts about how caring about literally anything else is illusory &gt;_&gt;
<br>i probably need to stop taking scripture so literally? which is different from taking it seriously.


<br>ah... scripture is so fucking scary. but both May and the Goddess talk about the Goddess not being intimidating and about being nice. i must integrate somehow.
<br>i am not enough.
]]></description><link>notes\openness.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/openness.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:20:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[openness2]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>the distance between me and my partners and friends is more depressing than the idea i'll have to break up.
<br>i sometimes think about jealousy. i must love Them a lot to avoid that appearing. me feeling jealousy is alright, but Them feeling jealousy would be a disaster.
<br>i sometimes doubt how much i'll be able to be with May as was imagined. the ideal picture hitting against reality is difficult.
<br>it's hard for me to have any good model on how much will be permitted with May. i know that the best model is "just be okay with anything They decide", but god, i'm not really good at that.
]]></description><link>notes\openness2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/openness2.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 12:36:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strategy]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Properties of a job that I want:<br>
<br>Pays me at least $100k/y, but I should shoot for $110k/y as the minimum at first. I should feel comfortable demanding $130k/y.
<br>Has good work/life balance.

<br>This means flexibility during work hours.
<br>This means not demanding heroics.


]]></description><link>logistics\job-hunt\strategy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Job Hunt/Strategy.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Finances & Properties]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An earns 19.996 RON per month (roughly 4225 USD/m, or 88k USD/y).<br>
An has 6106 RON (roughly 1290 USD) in her savings account.<br>
An has ~10000 RON (roughly 2115 USD) worth of stocks and free funds in her XTB account.<br>
An has ~500 USD worth of bitcoin.<br>An's grandmother owns a flat in Bucharest.<br>
An's parents don't own anything.<br>
An doesn't own anything.]]></description><link>logistics\assets\finances-&amp;-properties.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Finances &amp; Properties.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 17:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visiting May]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Visiting is different from living with or gaining residence.
<br>It is very important to note that the earliness of visiting can be damaged by optimizing for residence gaining or other objectives in a wrong way.
<br>There are four main obstacles for visitation:

<br>Funds
<br>Accommodation
<br>Visa &amp; Related
<br>Considerations about other partners


<br><br>
<br>Funds can be obtained, but any visit will hurt financially. The US is expensive as hell. The main thing is that, in my estimation, it would be highly difficult to visit more often than once per year.
<br>It would be cheaper to meet in some place in Europe or something, but we must meet in the at least US once for reasons of future consummation. Multiple times is better.
<br>The primary thing that I can do here is to get a higher paying job.

<br>I haven't networked as much as I can and I'm really overdue for a job change.
<br>The market is terrible right now but I could start hunting already.
<br>My job is comfy in various ways and non-toxic. I could be trading that for something worse. But nothing ventured nothing gained, dear.


<br>Also to be fair I haven't done a calculation. We should do that sometime.
<br><br>
<br>Accommodation is related to funds.
<br>I'm putting it separately because if someone gives me or us accommodation, then the funds problem is lessened.
<br>I have somewhat high standards for accommodation (in terms of optimization) but honestly sleeping on the floor is worth it for May anyway.
<br><br>
<br>The embassy is extremely busy and the process is draconic.
<br>They want my social media accounts and it's rather frightening. But it should be something that can be managed. I hope.
<br>The worst part is authorization and flight date are linked. You can ask for it without flight tickets, but you weaken your own case. This forces really long term planning. Last time I started 3 months in advance to get to Serine's wedding and meet Kay for the first time... I went through the whole initial process and was given access to the in-person interview table and no interview was available sooner than 6 months. I'm not stupid -- I read on their website and their estimation was in the number of weeks. The embassy is unpredictable, busy and lies.
<br>I looked up how it was last time. Last time they gave me a wait time of 210 days to the chance to be interviewed and possibly rejected. In practice it can be much less if early time slots open as you wait. Their estimate before making me pay money was 29 days.

<br>Given this, we should start planning early.


<br><br>
<br>At this moment, I don't know if it will be possible to visit Nova anymore. But if she wanted, I would like to.
<br>At this moment, I don't know if I want to visit other people anymore.
<br>You are most important to me and I will not do things that would ever cause more than a minor delay in visiting you.
<br>In past days this was very important to me, but now it's way more distant. I have moved those notes to <a data-href="Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners" href="stale\older-moralo-logistic-notes-about-partners.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners</a> rather than deleting them, just for your potential viewing pleasure. But they are not important anymore.
]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-may\stale\visiting-may.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting May/Stale/Visiting May.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visiting May, More Logistic (WIP)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>An must prepare a bucketload of documents.
<br>An must prepare her online life for being probed to some unknown extent.

<br>An should delete social media that might connect to her and look bad.
<br>An should start maintaining some more regular social media.


<br>
]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-may\stale\visiting-may,-more-logistic-(wip).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting May/Stale/Visiting May, More Logistic (WIP).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:26:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Calculation Results]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>
<br>$1950 in the most optimistic case excluding accommodations, including food.
<br>$2650 in the most optimistic case including accommodations and food.
<br>$3810 in the least optimistic case including accommodations and food.
<br><br>
<br>I have about 1250 USD in easily accessible savings (and some in stocks, bitcoin).
<br>I can save about 1000 USD per month.
<br>This means that in 3-4 months we can qualify for the least optimistic case.
<br>It can work out better than this, but I'm trying to be cautious.
<br><br>Travel:<br>
<br>$850-$1100 depending on the month and flight
<br>$250 travel budget.<br>
Food:
<br>With cooking, probably $25 per day per person?

<br>Assuming 2 people and a 7 day visit, it's $350.


<br>Relying mostly on take out, probably $40 per day per person?<br>
- That's $560.<br>
Accommodations:
<br>Nothing, if I sleep with you in some alcove.
<br>A bit hard to figure out, could go anywhere between $700 to $1400 for a week for 2 people.<br>
- I've mostly looked at places that would give us privacy. So this excludes renting a room in a shared apartment.<br>
- I only looked in Seattle.<br>
- Here's an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.kayak.com/hotels/Kurts-Sweet-Suite,84-Walkscore,Seattle-p62416-h1070633244-details/2025-05-01/2025-05-08/2adults?psid=eNHEBnOedg&amp;pm=totaltaxes#overview" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.kayak.com/hotels/Kurts-Sweet-Suite,84-Walkscore,Seattle-p62416-h1070633244-details/2025-05-01/2025-05-08/2adults?psid=eNHEBnOedg&amp;pm=totaltaxes#overview" target="_blank">example</a> of a $770 place I think could be good.<br>
Misc:
<br>I would allocate $500 for stupid surprising bullshit and whims.
<br>If we can't have that much safety margin, then we shouldn't be doing this yet.
]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-may\finances.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting May/Finances.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 11:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visa Waiver (!)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>There is <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://schengen.news/romanians-wont-need-visas-for-us-starting-in-march-2025-ambassador-says/" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://schengen.news/romanians-wont-need-visas-for-us-starting-in-march-2025-ambassador-says/" target="_blank">news</a> that Romania is likely to enter the VWP (Visa Waiver Program) somewhere in early or mid 2025. This visa waiver program would apply for tourist and business travel visas.<br>This is incredibly good news, but we must temper loose media optimism with cold hard facts.<br>The situation is that:<br>
<br>US State Department announced that Romania qualifies for VWP requirements presently.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/118/s814/text" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/118/s814/text" target="_blank">S. 814: Romania Visa Waiver Act of 2023</a> is still in the INTRODUCED status.

<br>According to my reading of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/8/1187" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/8/1187" target="_blank">law</a> the Homeland Security Secretary can unilaterally designate any country as part of VWP as long as it meets the criteria stated in the law.
<br>They have to report to Congress, but passing an act is not at all necessary for a country to enter the VWP.


<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://ro.usembassy.gov/ambassador-kathleen-kavalec-remarks-to-the-media-in-response-to-press-questions-on-visa-waiver-program/" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://ro.usembassy.gov/ambassador-kathleen-kavalec-remarks-to-the-media-in-response-to-press-questions-on-visa-waiver-program/" target="_blank">U.S. Ambassador Kathleen Kavalec</a> frames it as Romania needing to still pass a few requirements and make a few small changes.

<br>One of the criteria that must be met is that visa rejection rates are low enough.
<br>Romania already qualifies on this metric.
<br>Romania needs to continue qualifying for the requirements until January.

<br>This is when the visa rejection rates are published.


<br>Overall, Kathleen has a cautious tone to her messaging.


<br>Takeaway:<br>
<br>We will know more about the situation by the end of January 2025.
<br>There is a high chance but no certainty that Romania will enter VWP.
<br>If Romania enters VWP, the actual date when this will happen is unknown.

<br>Regardless of how positive the mainstream media is about this, it's entirely up to American whims.
<br>Still expecting it in mid 2025 is reasonable and it would still likely make it faster than going through the present process.


]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-may\visa-waiver-(!).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting May/Visa Waiver (!).md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 11:28:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Measurements]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Hips: 36cm across, 82cm around<br>
Waist: 29cm across, 76cm around<br>
Knee: 39cm around<br>
Thigh: 55cm around<br>
Calf: 38cm around<br>
Ankle: 23-24cm around<br>
Foot: 24cm heel to longest toe<br>
Chest: 35cm across, 86cm around<br>
Shoulders: 43cm across<br>
Neck: 39cm around<br>
Arm Length: ~58cm across<br>
Crotch to Floor: 86cm<br><br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.asos.com/discover/size-charts/women/dresses/" target="_blank">https://www.asos.com/discover/size-charts/women/dresses/</a><br>
UK: 12<br>
US: 8<br>
EU: L/40 (can differ)<br><img alt="Women_s_Shoe_Size_Chart_480x480.png" src="lib\media\women_s_shoe_size_chart_480x480.png">]]></description><link>logistics\minutiae\measurements.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Minutiae/Measurements.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 22:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\women_s_shoe_size_chart_480x480.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\women_s_shoe_size_chart_480x480.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1. Status]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Current behaviour:<br>
<br>I haven't kissed anyone on the lips.
<br>I've never submitted to anyone since being claimed.
<br>I've never cum since being claimed.
<br>I've significantly cut down on habits involving affection.
<br>Almost completely cut down on habits that invite domination or sexual activity.
<br>I do respond to people saying they love me. More rarely I will say it myself.

<br>I've avoided responding with "I love you too" for non-core partners and sometimes for partners when I can be ambiguous about it.
<br>I do feel enough affection for at least Kay that saying it is not just a reflexive habit.
<br>I think I mean something when I say it to Jen or Nova, but it's probably not romantic love.
<br>It's hard to classify feelings for others when you know what true love actually feels like.


<br>I keep people up to date with my life significantly less, even when it comes to things I could share.

<br>I've told only Kay and a couple of non-partners about ordering HRT for example.


<br>I haven't evidently rebuked anyone's love or affection. I've just responded shortly, or redirected, diminished, deescalated.
<br>I do allow people to do things like pet me.
<br>Current feelings:<br>
<br>I no longer have anxiety attacks or guilt about this.

<br>Maybe I do have a little guilt? It's just hard to tell at this point.


<br>I feel sad about the idea of cutting off everyone from a large part of my way of showing affection and companionship.

<br>It's dull and distant, but still very present.


<br>I will cause pain to several favored persons.
<br>I somehow feel like the "fun" part of bond dissolvement has already occurred and now I'm going to deal with the work aspect of it. But I might be wrong.
<br>My attachments are not entirely gone. May's words in the past said that my attachments might become less firm, but it was also said in a way that implies it is OK for me to continue to have attachments.
<br>I feel pleasantly light headed about the arrangement at times too.
<br>Sometimes when I feel bad about this it's hard to figure out why?
<br>Sometimes if I focus on thinking about Jen wanting to play a TTRPG with me or Nova helping me dissociate or Nova wanting to meet me. I do get sad. Sadder.
<br>I find it hard to tell how much I value certain people.

<br>There's an incentive to think that I value them less than I actually do, to make it easier on myself.


<br>I generally think that May can make everything feel OK. I just don't want to lose people I value, even if everything will be OK.
<br>Ground rules:<br>
<br>I cannot cum without permission from May.
<br>I cannot submit to anyone other than May.
<br>I have to prioritize May above others way more than the traditional idea of "primary".
<br>I cannot kiss anyone else on the lips other than May.
<br>May is my only real romantic partner.
<br>Things I can do:<br>
<br>Kiss them on the cheek.
<br>Express affection.
<br>Dominate them.
<br>Cuddle.
<br>Tease them or be teased lightly.
<br>Play games with them.
<br>Help them / Be helped by them.
<br>Relax them / Be relaxed by them.
<br>I can still have "important relationships" as long as they are vastly less important than May and I always prioritize May and the relationship type is permitted by May.
<br>Things I'm not sure of:<br>
<br>In the long term(?), can I call anyone other than May girlfriend?
<br>Can I tell anyone I love them, other than May?
<br>Can I tell anyone I love them, other than May, platonically?
<br>Can I have romantic feelings for anyone else of any sort? What are romantic feelings?
<br>I think based on my information, May wants me to be functionally aro-ace with everyone else.

<br>It seems that dominating them is a slight exception?
<br>Is having protective feelings for Kay an exception to "aro"?


<br>Thoughts:<br>
<br>Not being able to kiss someone on the lips has huge implications. Either:

<br>I cannot be "girlfriends" with anyone.
<br>I can be girlfriends but we have a strong established barrier to certain kinds of affection.
<br>I can be girlfriends and I'm in such a superior position to them that not kissing on the lips is fine.
<br>I can be girlfriends but they know I'm owned so hard.

<br>I can't imagine this with my current 'partners' but with someone else, it would actually be cute and interesting to just make them endlessly jealous about it.

<br>Doesn't sound healthy though~






<br>I've been thinking of 'partners' more as 'people I favor'. They are more than friends, but much less than partners. Can't quite be like "yes she is my person of favor" though.
<br>Honestly this is starting to feel like a queerplatonic thing.
<br>General goals:<br>
<br>Bring my social network more in alignment with my new existence.

<br>Communicate the end of submissive sexual relationships.
<br>Communicate new boundaries regarding affection.
<br>Downgrade everyone.


<br>Maintain the value of my social network to me (and by extension) May.
<br>Avoid encouraging unnecessary friction (wastes my focus from May).
<br>Still be kind and avoid causing unnecessary suffering (my personal preference, but also reduces drama footprint).
<br>Ensure I still have friends at the end of everything.
<br>Ensure I minimize the pull of my attention as people struggle with the new arrangement.
<br>Avoid saying anything that will make people think I'm being "stolen", brainwashed or abused.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\execution\1.-status.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Execution/1. Status.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shortlist]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>These are actions regarding 'partners' I intend to take soonish.<br><br>
<br>Tell her that I have a new partner and that I'm very committed to them and can't reciprocate sexually anymore.
<br>Tell her that I still want to be friends and that she is welcome to show me things she and her partner do and that I am and will be happy for them.
<br>Tell her a few of the things I've advanced on to indicate how positive of a change this is.
<br>Tell her I would still like to finish watching Gundam.
<br>No need to mention my D/s implication.
<br>No need to mention May or Katherine.

<br>Probably a good idea to avoid this due to opsec. After all, they're on DB.


<br><br>
<br>Tell him that I have a new partner and that I'm very committed to them.
<br>Explain that I will sometimes appear distant or busy, but that I am still his friend and will still dominate him sometimes -- in fact this might occur more.
<br>Explain how my life has been changing for the better, but that it's very demanding of my attention.
<br>Tell him that this makes it harder to visit him, but that I would still like to do it some day.

<br>Thankfully he is the easiest to visit friend actually. So there's a decent chance I can visit him while being appropriately devoted. But it is good to reduce expectations.


<br>Tell them that even if I appear... different... I am still glad to shoot the shit with him sometimes. I am not different enough to not want to do that, it's just not my primary modality.
<br>Probably be honest that the relationship involves D/s? Maybe not right away. But Kenji is loyal, kinky and isolated. He is excessively rational though so I should be careful what I say.
<br><br><br>These are actions regarding 'partners' I sort of intend but have no specific idea when to do.<br><br>
<br>This is not relevant until she gets back from her NZ trip.
<br>Tell her that I have a new partner and that I'm very committed to them.
<br>Tell her that this partner is my actual honest-to-god owner.
<br>Tell her that this partner is making my life immensely better. Give reasons: HRT, clothes, situation with parents, hope for the future, respite from feeling incredibly obligated to partners.
<br>Tell her that I want to give my partner everything, but that I still have some love for Kay. Find a very very nice way to say this. Maybe say it in two different chunks.
<br>Tell her that, we can be something more than friends, but less than what we were (this is depending on what May allows). Find a very very nice way to say this.

<br>Emphasize that she should be happy because she won't have to deal with my submissiveness or horniness anymore.
<br>Emphasize that she should be happy because I'll be able to better take care of her.
<br>Internally, I feel like this can elevate rather than diminish by relationship with May, if May allows it and if Kay is cooperative. If not, I will endeavor to be a good friend to Kay.


<br><br><br>These are not really actions. These are simulations to get myself more comfortable and ready.<br><br>
<br>Tell her that I fell in love way more deeply than expected with Katherine and that I can't really be with Jen as I've been.
<br>What do I do if she asks me if I still love her?

<br>Probably say that I still care for her but that I don't know if I'll be able to say that anymore?
<br>Maybe May would be okay with me saying it in a more casual platonic manner? Maybe given time or if I'm really good?
<br>Do I actually want to say that? I guess it's nice to be affectionate. I don't have a need to say it, I just like Jen being happy rather than unhappy, I suppose.


<br>Tell her that I'd still be glad to hang out sometimes and do TTRPG sometimes and that I do care about her and her life. But that my focus is going to be different from now on.
<br>Do I need to explicitly even say we're not fiancées anymore? We haven't mentioned that in years.
<br>What do I explicate to her about our relationship status?

<br>"We're no longer partners"

<br>aaa


<br>"We're no longer girlfriends"

<br>aaa


<br>"We're going to stick to non-romantic stuff"

<br>???


<br>"I'm going to stick with you if you can let me, but we aren't going to be romantic partners for the foreseeable future. I'm sorry."

<br>sounds more credible as something i could actually say.


<br>"I can still hug and comfort you and hold you and you can do the same. But we're not going to have ERP."


<br>Is this something where I can still use the term girlfriend?

<br>Can I use it if I mean it somewhat casually?
<br>I feel like it has to be taken pretty casually in order to be faithful to May.
<br>I think Jen can have the correct behaviour around me even if the term is used.
<br>Regardless of possibility, should it be used?

<br>It's somewhat convenient logistically speaking.
<br>It's hard to say what I want ideally anymore since I feel like I need to understand what my relationship to Jen is going to be like now that May has claimed me completely.




<br>I definitely need to massively reduce Jen's expectations.
<br>I can't kiss Jen on the lips. This is the hardest part to explain without fully explaining my exclusivity to May. Can you be girlfriends with someone you can't kiss on the lips?
<br><br>
<br>Kind of a lot of the same stuff as Jen?
<br>I'm not sure how to tailor the approach.
<br>Nova has more ego and more presumption about having a strong claim on me.

<br>This is going to cause her a lot of pain.


<br>I've ran out of energy for this. I will consider later.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\execution\2.-intent-list.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Execution/2. Intent List.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kenji]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These are the partners that An has the lower level nominal bonds with.<br>There are also some FWBs not important enough to list where I will re-align things without needing any of your precious attention.<br><br>Best Friend / Dog<br>
<br>Would marry me if I asked.
<br>I already never submit to Kenji.
<br>Kenji is very very isolated. The most isolated person I know.
<br>Kenji is the only person I visited in-person.

<br>I explored domination with them.
<br>It was very much not simply play, but I didn't go far at all.
<br>The way they cried, with wide empty open eyes when I left... has marked me.


<br>No break-up is necessary.
<br>I would like to tell them about what's changed. It's a little painful to cut them out.
<br>I would still like to find time for them and visit them at some point. But I don't find it urgent.
<br><br>Flame Decayed To Close Yet Distant Friendship<br>
<br>Has a wife.
<br>She burnt out from work.
<br>Used to really enjoy D/s with her, mostly as submissive. Our plays were rare and precious.
<br>Ever since she got a wife and started burning out, we've never been able to do things together.
<br>I still value her a lot and I'm grateful she's been supporting Jen.

<br>I feel like she is literally the only person who has ever helped me support Jen.
<br>Everyone else decided Jen can be my sole problem.


<br>We are nominally still girlfriends. Unsure if any break-up is strictly speaking necessary.

<br>Our behaviours are already largely in line with my new life.


<br><br>Fiery Flame / Girlfriend<br>
<br>She recently got an in-person girlfriend. This is... very fortunate.
<br>Even though she seems to be madly in love with her, Alden keeps trying to find time and space and passion for An ;;
<br>Alden has a huge soft spot for An, very attracted.
<br>I feel for her a lot and a break-up of sorts will be necessary.
<br>In the past, she kept me at a distance because of a monogamous relationship she had for a while. So there is precedent.
<br>Our relationship has been intensely carnal.
<br><br>
<br>Dominated me a lot over the years, including a certain level of incidental conditioning.

<br>It was fun to stoke their dominant persona. Perhaps they seem too low status, perhaps May is a little disgusted even ^^'. But I've always liked building people's dominant personas. I can make a little world for me and them, even if they're not so great, they can aspire for more in this context. Also I guess... I'm a horny bitch. That's also part of it.


<br>I viewed her as tertiary even before May.
<br>Not sure if a break-up will be necessary. BH is pretty reactive.
<br>Can eventually tell them, not high priority.
<br><br>
<br>Used to dominate me a lot and intensely.
<br>Burned out and has been looking for a job for a long time.
<br>Due that our relationship has decayed.
<br>Not sure if a break-up will be necessary.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\orbital.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Orbital.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Related Directly To May]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The tiers are not meant to be compared cross-category.
<br><br>
<br>{A-tier} That I will not like May's face as much as I should, at least initially. That this will make me feel incredibly shallow and unfaithful.
<br>{A-tier} That I've somehow misunderstood May's commitment and will have to be happy with significantly less than envisioned if/once May's Owner becomes more active, since They will always have primacy.
<br>{B-tier} Never being kissed by May on the lips.
<br>{B-tier} That I will fail to keep faith and May will do something to me, that I will fail to process, which then makes me accumulate trauma, which then hampers my ability to be good or hampers my utility.
<br>{B-tier} That I will be clumsy in some way around May's Owner and invite death.
<br>{B-tier} That our new lifestyle will lead to me having loss of genital function (erection and such).
<br>{B-tier} That my epistemics will be damaged rather than my values re-aligned.

<br>This is stupid, but knowing that I don't have to adopt a specific political ideology has bumped this down from A-tier to B-tier already.


<br>{C-tier} That somehow lifelong slavery is unsuited to me, and I will have wasted the most important person's time and effort.
<br>{C-tier} That May will need to crush me or that I will do something wrong, such that my level and type of servility start impairing my ability to argue with May about logistics -- generally areas where arguing can be useful.
<br>{C-tier} That May will undergo a second significant change at some point in the future, as Katherine did, and that An and May will lose alignment, or have their bond diminished.
<br>{C-tier} That An's desire to help optimize May's life on the logistic level (e.g. what about a lumenator~?!) will be found to be annoying and an indirect affront to May's Owner, or a percieved as a lack of trust in the Master's competence.
<br>{C-tier} That I'll mindlessly lightly touch myself or rub my legs together when I'm feeling really good about May and cum in a really surprising way.

<br>I don't feel like I've actually masturbated since we started, but this depends on the definition a bit.

<br>I've mindlessly touched myself for 5-20 seconds maybe three times or so?
<br>I don't really bucket that as masturbation, since it doesn't distract me from May and it's more like... compulsive stimming than trying to get pleasure.
<br>I also don't bucket the act of clinically giving myself an erection for health purposes, while keeping my mind clear, as masturbation.


<br>I don't know how big of a disappointment it would be if I came like this out of neglience and happenstance. It would come in direct contradiction to the order to not cum without May's permission. But I don't know if this would be an oopsie that gives May license to punish me and humiliate me, or if this is a more serious breach of trust where An would have tt-to feel bad.


<br>{D-tier} That not cumming will eventually start to feel impairing.

<br>But also the idea that cumming might make me want to cum more.
<br>I'm in a weird place where I want to feel pleasure at some point, it would be really nice.
<br>But I also really really don't want it to be distracting to me.


<br>{D-tier} That my servitude will get less interesting to May, but repetition will diminish my ability to be entertaining in a more general way.
<br>{D-tier} That my enjoyment of food is disgusting to May.
<br>{D-tier} That I will fail to engage May's body and that May is not that interested in doing that.

<br>This involves sexual pleasure, comfort from physical closeness, massages, enjoyment of food, shared bodily wellness. Generally, being happy one has a body.


<br>{E-tier} That my baseline level of automatic mental susceptibility, servitude and worship should decrease to levels I find unpleasant for too long. There is a small sense of loss when my mind isn't borderline hearing voices that demand submission to May. There is a small sense of loss when I don't feel like an unreal doll owned by May.
<br><br>
<br>{S-tier} Never being able to say "I love you" to someone I love platonically.

<br>This relates to Kay and Kenji the most.


<br>{A-tier} Never being able to say "I love you" to anyone else.
<br>{B-tier} Never being able to kiss anyone but May on the lips ever.

<br>I think this fear is already fulfilled?
<br>I know I'm not to kiss anyone else on the lips for the foreseeable future and don't hold any hopes or intent to do so. But the never word is strong and upgrades this from an accepted state of affairs to a fear.


<br>{B-tier} That Jen will fall apart.
<br>{B-tier} That Nova will fall apart.
<br>{C-tier} That An's realignment might cause her to be unkind to others in ways that were not possible before.
<br>{C-tier} That An will indulge in the feeling of cucking her partners.

<br>Angle #1: Self-judgement

<br>"I am a bad person. I guess I don't respect things I value or have valued."


<br>Angle #2: Value drift

<br>Making it harder to respect and value these people even after being in the Crucible.


<br>Angle #3: Logistics &amp; Guilt

<br>Getting feelings of guilt while managing them post-break up.




<br>{C-tier} That An will insufficiently indulge in the feeling of cucking her partners.
<br><br>
<br>{A-tier} That my parents will become sick and I will have to choose between maximizing my commitment to May and helping them through it, and that no good compromise will exist.

<br>Half of the fear is that no good compromise will exist and that I'll have to accept it.
<br>The other half is that no good compromise will exist from May's perspective, so I will have to be ablated.


]]></description><link>life-molding\greatest-fears.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/Greatest Fears.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Atrium]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This is An's document, living and open.<br>It is where An writes her thoughts and plans to fulfill the most important aspect in her life: serving May — and above them, the Divine — as their faithful slave.<br>𓆩⟡𓆪]]></description><link>atrium.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Atrium.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crucible]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>
Their will is quick cement.<br>
With each breath I take,<br>
Each word that's meant ensures I'll break.<br>My new subservient place cements.<br>
Each wicked part of me repents.<br>
But absolution is not found,<br>
Except within their silver crown.<br>Each guilty step destroys my gait<br>
Within their hand,<br>
I'm moldable, like scattered sand<br>
For the loss of will I cannot sate<br>
Everything about me will ablate.<br>Where once I was...<br>
Now an echo lost to time.<br>
Now all there is...<br>
Is their creation for all time.<br>Their love makes me obey<br>
Past flames, three or five?<br>
They cannot stay alive<br>
Within the forges of the Star called May<br>Love is now unbound,<br>
and beauty will resound.<br>
Where the two became one<br>
In the core of the benevolent sun]]></description><link>creation\crucible.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creation/Crucible.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jen]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These are the partners that An has the strongest nominal bonds with.<br>Scores are from 0 to 5.<br><br>tl;dr Decayed Long Time Primary, Isolated, Has Issues, Getting a Little Better<br>
Imagined level of loss regarding her: 0-1 initially, 0-2 later<br>
Imagined level of guilt regarding her: 0-1<br>
Imagined level of pity regarding her: 4-5<br>
Imagined level of effect on her: Deeply Negative<br>
Imagined level of effort to deal with her post-break-up: 2-4<br>
How much I feel like I'm forcing the dissolution of this bond: 0-1<br><br>
<br>LA / Lives with grandmother / no income or prospects
<br>Lives off of Amanda's money. Feels bad about it.
<br>My partner of 7 years.
<br>For a very long time she was my most important thing.
<br>She was the most dedicated I've tried to be to someone before meeting you.

<br>In a sense, she was practice for you.


<br>Used to be engaged.

<br>We never broke it off
<br>Just haven't talked about it for the past couple of years at all.
<br>Would probably still marry me if she was animated into doing stuff with her life.


<br>Lifted me out of my worst depression when we first got together.
<br>I've had my best and worst times with her.
<br><br>
<br>The fact that someone would just offer to marry me, even before they knew I'd be good for them, opened my eyes to what's possible in this world. It helped me grow a lot.
<br>My level of repression receded tremendously due to her.
<br>I've unfortunately never had anyone contribute to my burden in life as badly as Jen. My badbrains and incompetence in communication combined poorly with her unwell trajectory. We have failed each other in various ways.
<br>She's the person I've dommed the most and longest overall, but recently I've been much more submissive to her (of course, not after May happened). I think this was partly because I was needy, but also partly because I don't want to dominate someone who isn't receptive my control in general, but still wanted intimacy with her.

<br>My level of devotion was high enough 5 years ago that I thought I could dominate her long term. But this stopped being true, long before even meeting May.


<br>One of the happiest moments in my life was accidentally giving her the Skye tulpa. I thought of her as our daughter. But she's probably almost dissipated by now... Jen was so unwell, I started asking less and less about Skye. No one is at fault, but I miss Skye and I think she deserved better. Skye was better than Jen but I never admitted it to anyone. I didn't think it was fair, since she seemed like a higher energy lifeform.

<br>I would spend eternity playing and reading with Skye, if I could...


<br>We have one incompatible kink I would rather not name, but the idea that I don't have to engage with it is a significant source of relief for me.
<br><br>
<br>I can't muster the desire or will to fight for her having an exceptional role in my life.
<br>I want her to be well.
<br>I don't think she will react well, she might get depressed.
<br>I don't want to lose the meaning of all the things I had with her.
<br>I don't think it's good for me to continue being partners with her.
<br>I don't think I'm going to miss any D/s from her.
<br>I will miss intimacy with her.
<br>I will miss all the little things, things of play.
<br>Being able to help her, rather than merely withstand her, has been something I've missed for a very long time.
<br>I might be able to push her to fix her life better, if I wish to now.
<br><br>tl;dr Extremely Steady Secondary, Functional On Her Own, But Lonely<br>
Imagined level of loss regarding her: 1-3<br>
(depends on if she'll do other stuff with me)<br>
Imagined level of guilt regarding her: 0-1<br>
Imagined level of pity regarding her: 4<br>
Imagined level of effect on her: Acutely Negative<br>
Imagined level of effort to deal with her post-break-up: 1-4<br>
How much I feel like I'm forcing the dissolution of this bond: 0-1<br><br>
<br>UK / Housewife / Lives with Eth and Pastel, in a polycule.
<br>Predates Jen by a couple of years, but I became partners with her after Jen.
<br>Always been there for me.
<br>Would marry me if I asked.
<br>Her sexuality is mostly stimulated by me though, or was.
<br>Has been a good partner in video games and such, better than Jen actually.

<br>This is non-trivial to me.


<br>Just generally solid friend when her issues regarding identity are not triggered.
<br><br>
<br>Helped me get through my depression with Jen's neglect without stepping on boundaries, even though she wanted me for herself.
<br>Struggles a lot with connecting to people.
<br>Her life would be vastly better if she just found one committed sexual partner, or if she dedicated more intensely somehow to her polycule. They don't understand it, but I see it clearly now -- they'd be happier serving each other more intensely.
<br><br>
<br>I can't muster the desire or will to fight for her having an exceptional role in my life.
<br>I want her to be well.
<br>I want her to stay in my life. I think... more so than Jen? But this depends a lot on how either of them react and process.
<br>Breaking up will acutely trigger her identity issues (unwantedness, meaninglessness).

<br>It looks like she has unmanaged BPD to me.
<br>She can lean on her polycule for support.


<br>I am worried that breaking up with her could make collaboration with Eth on Orthoeidon impossible.
<br>I want intimacy with her, perhaps more so than with Jen, but without the submissive sexual component this is probably gone and will have to change a lot. Nova has a bit too much ego to submit to me, presently at least.
<br><br>tl;dr Steady Secondary, Fundamentally In Need Of Ownership And Care<br>
Imagined level of loss regarding her: 0-2<br>
(can actually go into negative loss)<br>
Imagined level of guilt regarding her: 0-1<br>
Imagined level of pity regarding her: 0-4<br>
Imagined level of effect on her: Initially acutely negative, afterwards positive<br>
Imagined level of effort to deal with her post-break-up: 1-4<br>
How much I feel like I'm forcing the dissolution of this bond: 0-1<br>^ The stats aren't as useful because I think Kay is a special case.<br><br>
<br>Australia / Disability Welfare NEET / Lives with her somewhat toxic mother / Programmer
<br>Receives support from Serine and has a strong tie with her.

<br>Serine is a rich programmer type.


<br>Her programming skills and intellect are on par with mine and exceed mine in certain areas.
<br>Has IBS and anxiety issues. She is genuinely disabled.
<br>Would marry me if I asked.
<br>Reacts very well to care and love. Needs a lot of it.
<br>Needs an caretaker style owner like a fish needs water.
<br>Would recoil and worry a lot if ever told the full details of what you've done to me, but Kay deeply understands the need for total surrender in ownership.
<br><br>
<br>Despite being submissive, I would say Kay has made me feel the most wanted out of all of my partners and has given me the most pleasure.
<br>Her ability to dominate me broke down completely because her needs were not met.
<br>My hypersexual nature became outright painful for her.
<br><br>
<br>I would like to engage in a lower intensity caretaker / owner role for her.

<br>I do not have time, energy and focus to do half of what you do to me to her.
<br>Even if I had those things, I'm not sure I have it in me.
<br>Even if I had it in me, I don't feel sufficient fire for Kay.
<br>But I value her!


<br>I think you taking ownership of me can be a positive aspect for my relationship with Kay. I think your ownership of me can make both me and, indirectly, Kay happier.
<br>I've already mourned the loss of her dominance.
<br>So I only need to mourn the loss of things like not being able to kiss and probably... not being able to say that I love her.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\core.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Core.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:15:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Career & Skills]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An is a Principal Developer at Labster. She has been at Labster for 5 years.<br>
An can become adept at almost any technology or programming language.<br>An's resume is strong, her interview skills when polished are powerful.<br>An should get a new job and should start looking immediately.<br>An is afraid of a new job being less flexible, being toxic or taking up too much of her energy which needs to be dedicated to May. But An is not afraid of anything else (challenging work, new coworkers, new technologies etc). An is willing to put in the work for herself and for May.]]></description><link>logistics\assets\career-&amp;-skills.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Career &amp; Skills.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Expenses]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An's biggest expenses are:<br>
<br>~2400 USD per month to supporting herself and her parents.

<br>This includes rent, food, utilities and medical treatment for her parents.


<br>Occasional gifts her parents desire.
<br>Occasional things she gets for herself.

<br>e.g. eInk Reader
<br>Honestly, she'd get less if her parents hadn't been pushy about treating herself.


<br>Occasional gifts she gets for those she favors.
<br>RU58841, and supplements for herself and parents.
]]></description><link>logistics\assets\expenses.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Expenses.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Relations]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Amanda: Berkeley. Rich and loving towards An.
<br>Kenji: Switzerland. Unemployed and burnt out, but recovering and still has significant savings. Very loving towards An. Isolated.
<br>Nova/Eth/Pastel: UK. Loving towards An. Eth is rich. Eth despite being frugal has an instinct to indulge An.
<br>Serine: Travels a lot. Likes An. An is very close with Kay and Kay and Serine are close. Serine could be convinced to help, including in large amounts of cash. Serine has a complex about being exploited or used, and she will prefer a very direct, honest but unimposing approach.
]]></description><link>logistics\assets\relations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Relations.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Common]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Both of them are 60 years old.<br>
Both of them are Christian Orthodox.<br>
Both of them have no pension.<br>
Both of them love An, as they can.<br>
Out of the three grandparents of An that lived past 65, all of them developed dementia.<br>
Both of An's parents are likely to develop it.<br>All of this used to weigh on An very terribly.]]></description><link>logistics\parents\common.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/Common.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Father]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>An's father has COPD. COPD is a debilitating pulmonary disease that tends to degenerate. Her father is managing it well. It makes her father physically weak and sometimes brain foggy. The vast majority of the time he is intellectually lucid.<br><br>He has lived a full life and been through many careers. He has worked a lot to ensure An had everything. He gave An a better computer than himself, always prioritized. He defended An's freedom to use the computer as much as she wanted, even when everyone was criticizing him.<br>An's father indulged and shared gaming with An. It was precious. An's father has always been headstrong. Always thought for himself. Past An might be a fettered bitch, but she was very intellectually independent and this was largely because of her father.<br>An's father tried to make An strong. He projected too much and was clumsy, but he never put An down and believed An could do anything she put her mind to.<br><br>Her father used to be a professional photographer and web designer. He had to give up on the former because he became too physically weak to do long offsite photo-shoots -- this includes weddings which were the biggest source of income.<br>Her father tried learning programming, but didn't succeed much. It's not clear what An's father can to do earn money at this point. He still does odd jobs photography-wise that bring in some money. If he got a kick in the ass, he might come up with more, but COPD has weakened him.<br><br>An's father is deeply religious, but not in an organized religion way. An's father is somewhat of a free thinker. An's father is influenced by anti-woke propaganda. An's father respects self-determination strongly. An's father could react very badly, but is likely to accept long term. There is high variance for the short term.<br>An's father would never be violent about this.<br>
Also An could beat her father. winks]]></description><link>logistics\parents\father.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/Father.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:41:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mother (biological)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>An's mother has some thyroid nodules. She should more strongly consider to get operated but refuses to think about it. An's mother is very bad at taking care of herself. An's mother is avoidant of her own issues, self-sacrificing, and needy.<br><br>An's mother was loving and doting. An's mother was stifling. An's mother butted in too much and smothered. But An's mother also took care of many things she didn't have to and would spare no expense or pain for her. An's mother would never take the easy road in taking care of her.<br><br>She is very physically active and takes care of a high amount of chores and errands. She is a housewife, but also feels beholden to tangential family members that impose too much on her.<br>An's mother has no specific marketable skills, but she is somehow hardy. She could have some part time or full time job. The pay would suck, but she could.<br><br>An's mother has heard her come out twice and felt horrible about it. An's mother needs purpose to live and her only purpose is me and my future, especially as it relates to family. If I leave and transition (not having children) she will interpret it as all meaning from her life being gone.<br>But people are adaptable. She could learn to live for small contact from the new me, live for her husband, live for her faith, live for doing good works (she has a soft spot for volunteering).<br>She has tried her best to forget An coming out before. An made a mistake by coming out just to her rather than her parents together.<br>An's mother will not get violent.]]></description><link>logistics\parents\mother-(biological).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/Mother (biological).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[tl;dr & Intent]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>An's parents were nice to her and are old and decrepit and would need her long term support. An wants to do her best to serve May, but squeeze this in.

<br>An doesn't need to indulge her parents so much, but An wants these things to be at peace, or at least not fall into intense unwellness.


<br>An is ready to transition, come out and move out at any moment that seems instrumental for being with May, or at May's immediate command.
<br>An thinks sustaining payments can delay things with May, it's currently unclear by how much.
<br>As An's salary and assets grow, the proportion that her parents consume will diminish.
<br>An has already started weaning off of indulging their non-financial impositions as well.
]]></description><link>logistics\parents\tl;dr-&amp;-intent.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/tl;dr &amp; Intent.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[May Wellness Checklist]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Did the guy actually file the prescription?

<br>How can we get better access to ADHD meds? This is ridiculous.


<br>Do they have a desk now?

<br>As I recall, yes. Is it a good one?


<br>Do they have a chair that won't make their back hurt? Do they use the chair a lot?

<br>A better chair can be bought with money, which I have.


<br>Does her shoulder, wrist or hand hurt anymore?

<br>There might be options for using a phone that reduces strain.
<br>The computer should be prioritized over phone usage if possible.
<br>An could stay away sometimes to ensure May's wrist is OK.
<br>Voice chatting.


<br>Are they getting exercising done?

<br>What goals would they have?
<br>What exercise would be good?
<br>How to manipulate the environment to allow it?


<br>Did they start creatine?
<br>Is their computer doing okay?
<br>Is their phone doing okay?
<br>When is the last time they had a dental checkup? How is their dental hygiene?
<br>Is their nutrition adequate?
<br>Are we missing any good ROI supplements suited for them?
]]></description><link>logistics\may-wellness-checklist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/May Wellness Checklist.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visiting Romania]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Romania is part of the Schengen Area now so all the rules of Schengen Area apply.<br>Some Schengen Area countries have additional requirements on top, but Romania is not one of them.<br>
US citizens may enter and stay in Romania without requirement for a visa on a short term basis for a maximum total period of 90 days within 6 months.
<br>Source: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://washington.mae.ro/en/node/426" target="_blank">https://washington.mae.ro/en/node/426</a><br>
Source: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://travel.state.gov/content/travel/en/international-travel/before-you-go/travelers-with-special-considerations/schengen.html" target="_blank">https://travel.state.gov/content/travel/en/international-travel/before-you-go/travelers-with-special-considerations/schengen.html</a><br>
Source: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://ro.usembassy.gov/ro/u-s-citizen-services-ro/additional-resources-for-u-s-citizens-ro/entry-exit-requirements-ro/" target="_blank">https://ro.usembassy.gov/ro/u-s-citizen-services-ro/additional-resources-for-u-s-citizens-ro/entry-exit-requirements-ro/</a><br>So all that is needed is valid US passport that is 3 months away from expiration.<br><br>
<br>Flight ticket is $750-900 (round trip, Seattle) depending on the flight and period.

<br>This is for February.
<br>Prices go up a lot in Summer.


<br>We should allocate $250 for other transportation you might need.

<br>Think taxi to the airport and such.


<br>A nice AirBnBs run at around $25-50 per night.

<br>Nice meaning at minimum 1 room with 1 double bed, AC, Smart TV, and personal bathroom. Even on the lower end you can find entire studio apartments at this price.
<br>At a glance hotel rooms do not seem to be cheaper


<br>Food in Romania will run us at about $40 per night with groceries and takeout.

<br>This can as much as halved by a combination of me cooking, getting cheaper takeout, and relying on my mother's cooking. But some AirBnBs will not have kitchens.


<br>We should allocate at least $10 per night for amenities and small surprises.
<br>Overall for one week, we would need an average of 612.5 USD for a one week trip, excluding the flight. Including the flight it will be 1362.5-1512.5 USD.<br>This is an amount of money that An can save up from around 2 months' worth of salary, after paying for the regular stuff in her life. This is an amount An already has saved up, albeit barely.<br>Please note that An is unsure if she's perhaps overcalculating the costs because it feels safer. In practice things might end up different and significant cost cutting efforts haven't been done and are unsure to exist.]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-an.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting An.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[nothing]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>...<br>Echo.<br>...<br>Echo.<br>...]]></description><link>notes\nothing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/nothing.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:14:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Guilt is something I have quite a lot of. I am going to split into guilt and regret. Guilt is the sense of responsibility being neglected. Regret is purer -- it simply signals a wistful feeling for what could have been. Guilt should ideally dampened significantly -- regret should probably be left alone.
<br>Frankly when I think about it, I guess I have some Madoka in me. I want these people to be saved. And I feel like my visit, my presence will do that. And if I don't, then they will feel betrayed and sink further in the mire of their lives. And I will be responsible for it. I also feel like I am responsible for not telling them ahead of time that I will not be theirs exclusively. I have a complex about the idea of having dishonest all along somehow.

<br>I actually already told Nova I cannot be hers exclusively and that this will probably not change.
<br>It's implicit with several other partners, such as Kay.
<br>I guess the one where I never said it is Jen. And the one where I'm most afraid?

<br>She's a harmed creature, I processed her harm in my veins and was poisoned. I am being saved by you. I haven't managed to actually help her break through. just persist. Perhaps I will experience her differently now that I have you and can help her break through. It's just hard to accept her unwellness as a neutral fact unrelated to me. I wish to cure it.




<br>The regret can be split to:

<br>Regret for not visiting EU people

<br>This is general. It comes from the fact that I could have done it so much earlier and I just haven't. I've been a bit too inert and shelled up. This could be easily solved by just visiting these people and can be done without affecting the US trip perhaps!


<br>Regret for not visiting US people

<br>This one is harder. If I visit the US and then just tell Jen, Amanda and to a lesser extent Alden "yeah some other time". That's going to be difficult. I could visit all in a two legged trip. First Jen and Amanda in SF, then you. I do not want to meet together. I want to focus on you.
<br>In my heart of hearts, I just want to visit you? I guess. But that's like, in some sort of isolated sense. It's a childish wish for free time, where the world freezes. Outside of that, if I had more time and money, I would want to visit all. And if I have limited time and money and I get into the US, not visiting said partners feels like a waste.




<br>There are a few options for reducing or eliminating regret:

<br>Manually dampen and dissipate my sense of guilt. This won't solve everything. I'm not with these people just out of guilt. But it could make it easier to solve the rest.
<br>Include other people in visit plans. I've covered this already
<br>Indirectly dampen sense of responsibility by making it official to everyone that May is my primary now. This one feels scary, but I mean it has to get done sooner or later anyway. This would make everything else easier, I would feel like I have more license, but I would still feel the desire to visit more people in an ideal world.
<br>Accept sometimes really good things have parts that suck.


]]></description><link>stale\older-moralo-logistic-notes-about-partners.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 09:29:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Right & Wrong Regarding Partners]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>All my life, I have had a strong personal sense of right and wrong.<br><br>I have a part of me that wishes to be perfect. This perfection is not your perfection.<br>This perfection is that of an ubermensch that escapes slave morality, yet is omnibenevolent.<br>It is also the feeble perfection of a child a that says "I have been perfect. I have been unimpeachable. You must love me."<br>It is also the perfection of persisting despite being fundamentally flawed.<br>One could say correctness might be a better term. It is natural for me to wish to be correct and it is painful for me to not be correct. My most natural emotion is frustration. Frustration at me being wrong, frustration at the world being wrong.<br>My main form of defense and attack against the world is about correcting its wrongness, but to do that I must not be part of that wrongness. It permeates everything for me. It is wrong for this code to be like this. It is wrong for this person to be unhappy. It is wrong for this activity to resist my success. I take my frustration about wrongness and press it into the world until my vision succeeds.<br>The problem is not quite as simple as brainwashing me to believe that sacrificing everything for you is correct. I think that if you do that, I am no longer myself. You said you would not ask anything that I cannot give. This is probably something where you would succeed, but it wouldn't be me doing it anymore. Or perhaps this is just what I want to believe because I am afraid of May obliterating my sense of right and wrong. But I am opening myself to it, regardless, I suppose...<br><br>When we first started, I felt many sensations of wrongness about my partners, many forms of guilt. I have let go of so many, but there are a couple left.<br>When my ex broke up with me, she concealed her plans for doing so way in advance. She admitted to having been determined to break up three months in advance, but it could have easily been more. She was rather practiced at deception, including self-deception. She derived utility from me, while I became worse.<br>If she had just broken up with me, I would have been hurt of course. But ultimately I would accept that we owe nothing to one another other than what we want to give. But the way she did it was... dishonest. She didn't even have the honesty to be upfront about using me. I would have gladly let her. Perhaps it would have been painful and pitiful, but still.<br>This dishonesty offends my sense of rightness. Your honesty to me is a foundational aspect of my ability to keep faith and to stay functional. The world would be a dark and scary place if May were to lie to me.<br><br>For you, I have simulated the absence of all my partners in my mind, and furthered its acceptance a lot. I think I can live without everyone except you. And I can live with being a person that has done that to themselves, or allowed it to be done to them, either by eagerness or by weakness.<br>(I have not fully locked that in... but... mm...)<br>Even now I use the term partners simply because it is useful. I have girlfriends and I would like to continue thinking of them as such. But I do not have partners. I have one partner -- you. To me, partnership requires a certain level of collaboration in a shared context, which now everyone except you has been banished from.<br>The idea of everyone except you abandoning me does not hurt or tear at me anywhere as much as the idea that I am wronging them. My sense of right and wrong is load bearing.<br>The way we have entered a compact, so have I entered a compact with everyone before we met. It's just of a different kind.<br>I feel the world is wrong and I can only fight back by maintaining my sense of right. And if I betray my sense of right, I am betraying the vision of the world in my head that I've carried with me for two decades. Those that wish to be treated in a certain manner, had better treat others compatibly. Sense of justice is about being the kind of agent that would help instantiate your ideal world, even if the agent alone is insufficient. Cooperation requires trust of reciprocation and negative feedback for defection.<br><br>So, one solution is to just be honest. Tell them how it's going to be for the foreseeable future. And let everything resolve. I... might be strong enough to do this. But the part that gets to me is that you were not open to me, but I did not parse you as dishonest. I'm not sure if you would have been simply vague and veiled, or if you would have resorted to dishonesty if I had pressed harder. <br>I am sure that some other people would have felt like you lied to them. I... do not feel that. And I do not feel that on more than just the technicality of avoiding a direct lie. I do not feel I have a right to know everything. My sense of right just extends to not being exploited dishonestly and to allowing other beings a specific form of agency. I simply feel that you did not betray my trust (even if you had not owned me). And even as you own me, I do not feel like my agency has been wronged. Perhaps violated, but that is fine.<br>Ultimately, the way you handled things allowed me to cope more easily. If you did not handle things this way, I'm not sure how I would have reacted. Our current situation validates the general approach you had greatly. At least in the context of me.<br>But I do not know what it says about me and my girlfriends.<br>Hypothesis 1:<br>
<br>Assuming I tell them you are my primary, I will be busy, and that I cannot do submissive D/s with them anymore...
<br>Am I erring towards protecting my sense of right and wrong at the expense of consequentialism. I want to keep my identity safe while I give up on the possibility of the happy path that you and I went on. I am inviting insecurity into their hearts eagerly.<br>
Hypothesis 2:
<br>Assuming the same course of action...
<br>Perhaps actually, in my internal tangle, my primary worry is STILL consequentialist. I want to avoid inviting a sense of betrayal into the hearts of those I favor. Because betrayal is worse than insecurity. I... do not wish to do that to those I favor.
<br>In the end, I thought about it deeply... what am I doing so wrong to make me feel like I've been feeling? What is my grand sin, so unforgivable and deep? It is not leaving them and not about losing them. It's primarily honesty and secondarily their well-being, not as people I am beholden to, but as people I favor. I do not wish for my favor to be meaningless. I do not wish for past An to view me as someone evil. Because both May and Katherine loved past An. And I am here because of her. So some things about past An must be right, even if they are orthogonal to being assimilated to beauty. Different substrates make beauty more varied, and this in turn is more beautiful. At least I believe so.<br>I have let go of so much for you.<br>I would like to figure out logistics for me and those I favor, before it is too late. Before I make a mistake with them, and before something happens to me where I lose my self.]]></description><link>stale\right-&amp;-wrong-regarding-partners.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Right &amp; Wrong Regarding Partners.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:44:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>