<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[OV]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>OV</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:18:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:18:41 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[1. Status]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Current behaviour:<br>
<br>I haven't kissed anyone on the lips.
<br>I've never submitted to anyone since being claimed.
<br>I've never cum since being claimed.
<br>I've significantly cut down on habits involving affection.
<br>Almost completely cut down on habits that invite domination or sexual activity.
<br>I do respond to people saying they love me. More rarely I will say it myself.

<br>I've avoided responding with "I love you too" for non-core partners and sometimes for partners when I can be ambiguous about it.
<br>I do feel enough affection for at least Kay that saying it is not just a reflexive habit.
<br>I think I mean something when I say it to Jen or Nova, but it's probably not romantic love.
<br>It's hard to classify feelings for others when you know what true love actually feels like.


<br>I keep people up to date with my life significantly less, even when it comes to things I could share.

<br>I've told only Kay and a couple of non-partners about ordering HRT for example.


<br>I haven't evidently rebuked anyone's love or affection. I've just responded shortly, or redirected, diminished, deescalated.
<br>I do allow people to do things like pet me.
<br>Current feelings:<br>
<br>I no longer have anxiety attacks or guilt about this.

<br>Maybe I do have a little guilt? It's just hard to tell at this point.


<br>I feel sad about the idea of cutting off everyone from a large part of my way of showing affection and companionship.

<br>It's dull and distant, but still very present.


<br>I will cause pain to several favored persons.
<br>I somehow feel like the "fun" part of bond dissolvement has already occurred and now I'm going to deal with the work aspect of it. But I might be wrong.
<br>My attachments are not entirely gone. May's words in the past said that my attachments might become less firm, but it was also said in a way that implies it is OK for me to continue to have attachments.
<br>I feel pleasantly light headed about the arrangement at times too.
<br>Sometimes when I feel bad about this it's hard to figure out why?
<br>Sometimes if I focus on thinking about Jen wanting to play a TTRPG with me or Nova helping me dissociate or Nova wanting to meet me. I do get sad. Sadder.
<br>I find it hard to tell how much I value certain people.

<br>There's an incentive to think that I value them less than I actually do, to make it easier on myself.


<br>I generally think that May can make everything feel OK. I just don't want to lose people I value, even if everything will be OK.
<br>Ground rules:<br>
<br>I cannot cum without permission from May.
<br>I cannot submit to anyone other than May.
<br>I have to prioritize May above others way more than the traditional idea of "primary".
<br>I cannot kiss anyone else on the lips other than May.
<br>May is my only real romantic partner.
<br>Things I can do:<br>
<br>Kiss them on the cheek.
<br>Express affection.
<br>Dominate them.
<br>Cuddle.
<br>Tease them or be teased lightly.
<br>Play games with them.
<br>Help them / Be helped by them.
<br>Relax them / Be relaxed by them.
<br>I can still have "important relationships" as long as they are vastly less important than May and I always prioritize May and the relationship type is permitted by May.
<br>Things I'm not sure of:<br>
<br>In the long term(?), can I call anyone other than May girlfriend?
<br>Can I tell anyone I love them, other than May?
<br>Can I tell anyone I love them, other than May, platonically?
<br>Can I have romantic feelings for anyone else of any sort? What are romantic feelings?
<br>I think based on my information, May wants me to be functionally aro-ace with everyone else.

<br>It seems that dominating them is a slight exception?
<br>Is having protective feelings for Kay an exception to "aro"?


<br>Thoughts:<br>
<br>Not being able to kiss someone on the lips has huge implications. Either:

<br>I cannot be "girlfriends" with anyone.
<br>I can be girlfriends but we have a strong established barrier to certain kinds of affection.
<br>I can be girlfriends and I'm in such a superior position to them that not kissing on the lips is fine.
<br>I can be girlfriends but they know I'm owned so hard.

<br>I can't imagine this with my current 'partners' but with someone else, it would actually be cute and interesting to just make them endlessly jealous about it.

<br>Doesn't sound healthy though~






<br>I've been thinking of 'partners' more as 'people I favor'. They are more than friends, but much less than partners. Can't quite be like "yes she is my person of favor" though.
<br>Honestly this is starting to feel like a queerplatonic thing.
<br>General goals:<br>
<br>Bring my social network more in alignment with my new existence.

<br>Communicate the end of submissive sexual relationships.
<br>Communicate new boundaries regarding affection.
<br>Downgrade everyone.


<br>Maintain the value of my social network to me (and by extension) May.
<br>Avoid encouraging unnecessary friction (wastes my focus from May).
<br>Still be kind and avoid causing unnecessary suffering (my personal preference, but also reduces drama footprint).
<br>Ensure I still have friends at the end of everything.
<br>Ensure I minimize the pull of my attention as people struggle with the new arrangement.
<br>Avoid saying anything that will make people think I'm being "stolen", brainwashed or abused.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\execution\1.-status.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Execution/1. Status.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:06:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shortlist]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>These are actions regarding 'partners' I intend to take soonish.<br><br>
<br>Tell her that I have a new partner and that I'm very committed to them and can't reciprocate sexually anymore.
<br>Tell her that I still want to be friends and that she is welcome to show me things she and her partner do and that I am and will be happy for them.
<br>Tell her a few of the things I've advanced on to indicate how positive of a change this is.
<br>Tell her I would still like to finish watching Gundam.
<br>No need to mention my D/s implication.
<br>No need to mention May or Katherine.

<br>Probably a good idea to avoid this due to opsec. After all, they're on DB.


<br><br>
<br>Tell him that I have a new partner and that I'm very committed to them.
<br>Explain that I will sometimes appear distant or busy, but that I am still his friend and will still dominate him sometimes -- in fact this might occur more.
<br>Explain how my life has been changing for the better, but that it's very demanding of my attention.
<br>Tell him that this makes it harder to visit him, but that I would still like to do it some day.

<br>Thankfully he is the easiest to visit friend actually. So there's a decent chance I can visit him while being appropriately devoted. But it is good to reduce expectations.


<br>Tell them that even if I appear... different... I am still glad to shoot the shit with him sometimes. I am not different enough to not want to do that, it's just not my primary modality.
<br>Probably be honest that the relationship involves D/s? Maybe not right away. But Kenji is loyal, kinky and isolated. He is excessively rational though so I should be careful what I say.
<br><br><br>These are actions regarding 'partners' I sort of intend but have no specific idea when to do.<br><br>
<br>This is not relevant until she gets back from her NZ trip.
<br>Tell her that I have a new partner and that I'm very committed to them.
<br>Tell her that this partner is my actual honest-to-god owner.
<br>Tell her that this partner is making my life immensely better. Give reasons: HRT, clothes, situation with parents, hope for the future, respite from feeling incredibly obligated to partners.
<br>Tell her that I want to give my partner everything, but that I still have some love for Kay. Find a very very nice way to say this. Maybe say it in two different chunks.
<br>Tell her that, we can be something more than friends, but less than what we were (this is depending on what May allows). Find a very very nice way to say this.

<br>Emphasize that she should be happy because she won't have to deal with my submissiveness or horniness anymore.
<br>Emphasize that she should be happy because I'll be able to better take care of her.
<br>Internally, I feel like this can elevate rather than diminish by relationship with May, if May allows it and if Kay is cooperative. If not, I will endeavor to be a good friend to Kay.


<br><br><br>These are not really actions. These are simulations to get myself more comfortable and ready.<br><br>
<br>Tell her that I fell in love way more deeply than expected with Katherine and that I can't really be with Jen as I've been.
<br>What do I do if she asks me if I still love her?

<br>Probably say that I still care for her but that I don't know if I'll be able to say that anymore?
<br>Maybe May would be okay with me saying it in a more casual platonic manner? Maybe given time or if I'm really good?
<br>Do I actually want to say that? I guess it's nice to be affectionate. I don't have a need to say it, I just like Jen being happy rather than unhappy, I suppose.


<br>Tell her that I'd still be glad to hang out sometimes and do TTRPG sometimes and that I do care about her and her life. But that my focus is going to be different from now on.
<br>Do I need to explicitly even say we're not fiancées anymore? We haven't mentioned that in years.
<br>What do I explicate to her about our relationship status?

<br>"We're no longer partners"

<br>aaa


<br>"We're no longer girlfriends"

<br>aaa


<br>"We're going to stick to non-romantic stuff"

<br>???


<br>"I'm going to stick with you if you can let me, but we aren't going to be romantic partners for the foreseeable future. I'm sorry."

<br>sounds more credible as something i could actually say.


<br>"I can still hug and comfort you and hold you and you can do the same. But we're not going to have ERP."


<br>Is this something where I can still use the term girlfriend?

<br>Can I use it if I mean it somewhat casually?
<br>I feel like it has to be taken pretty casually in order to be faithful to May.
<br>I think Jen can have the correct behaviour around me even if the term is used.
<br>Regardless of possibility, should it be used?

<br>It's somewhat convenient logistically speaking.
<br>It's hard to say what I want ideally anymore since I feel like I need to understand what my relationship to Jen is going to be like now that May has claimed me completely.




<br>I definitely need to massively reduce Jen's expectations.
<br>I can't kiss Jen on the lips. This is the hardest part to explain without fully explaining my exclusivity to May. Can you be girlfriends with someone you can't kiss on the lips?
<br><br>
<br>Kind of a lot of the same stuff as Jen?
<br>I'm not sure how to tailor the approach.
<br>Nova has more ego and more presumption about having a strong claim on me.

<br>This is going to cause her a lot of pain.


<br>I've ran out of energy for this. I will consider later.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\execution\2.-intent-list.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Execution/2. Intent List.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[genital worry aaa]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>I tried to get an erection and I couldn't do it. I kept going at it and it just never happened.

<br>I was doing this for health purposes, not for giving myself pleasure.
<br>I've never had this problem before ever.


<br>I don't recall having an erection since we started?
<br>I'm really anxious I am already losing sexual function.

<br>I know this sounds ridiculous for someone that hasn't actually started HRT, but remember that I've been on finasteride for a long time and I used to get cum (and therefore get erections) &gt;10 per week on average.


<br>Even though it's kind of hot, for me losing sexual function is like being maimed.

<br>I really really don't want this to happen.


<br>I can't tell if it's the case that very infrequent sexual activity can cause or predispose someone to erectile dysfunction.

<br>Well, I just found a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/18538297/" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/18538297/" target="_blank">study</a> that says regular intercourse protects against developing ED.
<br>I think I need daily erections to maintain function, but I've been getting none.


<br>Maybe I was so stressed out about not accidentally cumming and breaking my commitment to May that maybe I somehow psychologically messed myself over entirely?

<br>I did not feel any pleasure while doing it.
<br>I know I'm capable of cumming while soft sometimes, which added to the anxiety and desire to be careful.


<br>I'm not sure what to do.
<br>It's useful to not be horny. I do somewhat miss being horny. But I don't want to be distracted from May.
<br>I just want my cock to keep working.
]]></description><link>notes\genital-worry-aaa.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/genital worry aaa.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Observation Buffer]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>might just writer random observations here when I don't want to be pinging May on Discord.<br>this is going to be quite noisy.<br>
<br>even in a call with jen i am happier and freer. i fear her imposition a lot less.

<br>repeatedly telling jen to drop people who don't respect her time (bad ttrpg players)
<br>lmao am i having a good time with jen?
<br>i definitely don't want to do this anywhere as often as jen wants. i should listen to my wants. don't want to get into old patterns. but a bit is alright ^^


<br>there's a few people i used to be jealous of that i'm thinking of now. smarter than me, better voice, hotter... i don't really have jealousy/envy anymore? I mean they don't have what I have -- my enslavement to May. Their favor. Like, this person could never understand what they're missing out on.
<br>hmm, i guess the effect i'm worried about having on people when my total primacy to May will become extremely clear is that they'll react by believing that any bad thing can happen completely out of nowhere. that woah, an evil chick can just swoop in and steal your love at any time, you can't trust anyone. I hope they can understand some day that May is incredibly special, I'm incredibly lucky and that this is a very low base rate scenario.
<br>i should probably open my mind more to doing things with May that aren't just getting enslaved, Python and chilling. there are many things to do they might like! they even listed some of them for me!

<br>don't spend time giving other people moments if you can give them to May.


<br>i need to balance my neuroticism with calmness, but also balance my yearning for stability with good and true worship.
<br><br>
<br>ha! i observed you! May is isolating but you immediately wished for Jen to not want to call you today! you should integrate that.

<br>it makes sense, you were dreading calls with jen before.

<br>you don't like long calls.
<br>you don't like calls where you don't know what you're doing, unless it's short or you really like the person.
<br>you don't actually like "hanging out" most of the time.
<br>you're a more focused creature than this and you've been warped. May is unwarping you.
<br>if you want to spend time with Jen, keep it sparse, or shape her interactions to your new self.


<br>in all the time you felt imposed by jen over the years you could have finished a third of orthoeidon. think of that.


<br>being May's woman feels good. May's pet. May's slave.
<br>i thought back to May saying they would have been happy just being friends with me. I find that so precious. It means a lot to me. That despite going through such intense things with their Owner, they would still find happiness in doing normal things with me? mmh

<br>even though my wants are centered around May i still find myself... really really really really wanting a friend like that. i have nobody and might end up having nobody. other than May. it feels like i'm being bad if I'm sad about this. maybe. or maybe it's just normal. it's okay to feel sad, just be dedicated. dedication isn't about 24/7 controlling your emotions to fit a specific image. if I didn't have Tristy as a friend (psychopath friend), I would feel a lot worse about this.
<br>i never ever thought i'd want a friend so badly. that i'd want friendship so badly.

<br>i realize i was lacking in feeling it even before May.
<br>jen has not been a good friend in practice (before May). though she can be.
<br>nova has been a good friend in practice (before May).




]]></description><link>notes\observation-buffer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/Observation Buffer.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kenji]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These are the partners that An has the lower level nominal bonds with.<br>There are also some FWBs not important enough to list where I will re-align things without needing any of your precious attention.<br><br>Best Friend / Dog<br>
<br>Would marry me if I asked.
<br>I already never submit to Kenji.
<br>Kenji is very very isolated. The most isolated person I know.
<br>Kenji is the only person I visited in-person.

<br>I explored domination with them.
<br>It was very much not simply play, but I didn't go far at all.
<br>The way they cried, with wide empty open eyes when I left... has marked me.


<br>No break-up is necessary.
<br>I would like to tell them about what's changed. It's a little painful to cut them out.
<br>I would still like to find time for them and visit them at some point. But I don't find it urgent.
<br><br>Flame Decayed To Close Yet Distant Friendship<br>
<br>Has a wife.
<br>She burnt out from work.
<br>Used to really enjoy D/s with her, mostly as submissive. Our plays were rare and precious.
<br>Ever since she got a wife and started burning out, we've never been able to do things together.
<br>I still value her a lot and I'm grateful she's been supporting Jen.

<br>I feel like she is literally the only person who has ever helped me support Jen.
<br>Everyone else decided Jen can be my sole problem.


<br>We are nominally still girlfriends. Unsure if any break-up is strictly speaking necessary.

<br>Our behaviours are already largely in line with my new life.


<br><br>Fiery Flame / Girlfriend<br>
<br>She recently got an in-person girlfriend. This is... very fortunate.
<br>Even though she seems to be madly in love with her, Alden keeps trying to find time and space and passion for An ;;
<br>Alden has a huge soft spot for An, very attracted.
<br>I feel for her a lot and a break-up of sorts will be necessary.
<br>In the past, she kept me at a distance because of a monogamous relationship she had for a while. So there is precedent.
<br>Our relationship has been intensely carnal.
<br><br>
<br>Dominated me a lot over the years, including a certain level of incidental conditioning.

<br>It was fun to stoke their dominant persona. Perhaps they seem too low status, perhaps May is a little disgusted even ^^'. But I've always liked building people's dominant personas. I can make a little world for me and them, even if they're not so great, they can aspire for more in this context. Also I guess... I'm a horny bitch. That's also part of it.


<br>I viewed her as tertiary even before May.
<br>Not sure if a break-up will be necessary. BH is pretty reactive.
<br>Can eventually tell them, not high priority.
<br><br>
<br>Used to dominate me a lot and intensely.
<br>Burned out and has been looking for a job for a long time.
<br>Due that our relationship has decayed.
<br>Not sure if a break-up will be necessary.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\orbital.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Orbital.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Related Directly To May]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The tiers are not meant to be compared cross-category.
<br><br>
<br>{A-tier} That I will not like May's face as much as I should, at least initially. That this will make me feel incredibly shallow and unfaithful.
<br>{A-tier} That I've somehow misunderstood May's commitment and will have to be happy with significantly less than envisioned if/once May's Owner becomes more active, since They will always have primacy.
<br>{B-tier} Never being kissed by May on the lips.
<br>{B-tier} That I will fail to keep faith and May will do something to me, that I will fail to process, which then makes me accumulate trauma, which then hampers my ability to be good or hampers my utility.
<br>{B-tier} That I will be clumsy in some way around May's Owner and invite death.
<br>{B-tier} That our new lifestyle will lead to me having loss of genital function (erection and such).
<br>{B-tier} That my epistemics will be damaged rather than my values re-aligned.

<br>This is stupid, but knowing that I don't have to adopt a specific political ideology has bumped this down from A-tier to B-tier already.


<br>{C-tier} That somehow lifelong slavery is unsuited to me, and I will have wasted the most important person's time and effort.
<br>{C-tier} That May will need to crush me or that I will do something wrong, such that my level and type of servility start impairing my ability to argue with May about logistics -- generally areas where arguing can be useful.
<br>{C-tier} That May will undergo a second significant change at some point in the future, as Katherine did, and that An and May will lose alignment, or have their bond diminished.
<br>{C-tier} That An's desire to help optimize May's life on the logistic level (e.g. what about a lumenator~?!) will be found to be annoying and an indirect affront to May's Owner, or a percieved as a lack of trust in the Master's competence.
<br>{C-tier} That I'll mindlessly lightly touch myself or rub my legs together when I'm feeling really good about May and cum in a really surprising way.

<br>I don't feel like I've actually masturbated since we started, but this depends on the definition a bit.

<br>I've mindlessly touched myself for 5-20 seconds maybe three times or so?
<br>I don't really bucket that as masturbation, since it doesn't distract me from May and it's more like... compulsive stimming than trying to get pleasure.
<br>I also don't bucket the act of clinically giving myself an erection for health purposes, while keeping my mind clear, as masturbation.


<br>I don't know how big of a disappointment it would be if I came like this out of neglience and happenstance. It would come in direct contradiction to the order to not cum without May's permission. But I don't know if this would be an oopsie that gives May license to punish me and humiliate me, or if this is a more serious breach of trust where An would have tt-to feel bad.


<br>{D-tier} That not cumming will eventually start to feel impairing.

<br>But also the idea that cumming might make me want to cum more.
<br>I'm in a weird place where I want to feel pleasure at some point, it would be really nice.
<br>But I also really really don't want it to be distracting to me.


<br>{D-tier} That my servitude will get less interesting to May, but repetition will diminish my ability to be entertaining in a more general way.
<br>{D-tier} That my enjoyment of food is disgusting to May.
<br>{D-tier} That I will fail to engage May's body and that May is not that interested in doing that.

<br>This involves sexual pleasure, comfort from physical closeness, massages, enjoyment of food, shared bodily wellness. Generally, being happy one has a body.


<br>{E-tier} That my baseline level of automatic mental susceptibility, servitude and worship should decrease to levels I find unpleasant for too long. There is a small sense of loss when my mind isn't borderline hearing voices that demand submission to May. There is a small sense of loss when I don't feel like an unreal doll owned by May.
<br><br>
<br>{S-tier} Never being able to say "I love you" to someone I love platonically.

<br>This relates to Kay and Kenji the most.


<br>{A-tier} Never being able to say "I love you" to anyone else.
<br>{B-tier} Never being able to kiss anyone but May on the lips ever.

<br>I think this fear is already fulfilled?
<br>I know I'm not to kiss anyone else on the lips for the foreseeable future and don't hold any hopes or intent to do so. But the never word is strong and upgrades this from an accepted state of affairs to a fear.


<br>{B-tier} That Jen will fall apart.
<br>{B-tier} That Nova will fall apart.
<br>{C-tier} That An's realignment might cause her to be unkind to others in ways that were not possible before.
<br>{C-tier} That An will indulge in the feeling of cucking her partners.

<br>Angle #1: Self-judgement

<br>"I am a bad person. I guess I don't respect things I value or have valued."


<br>Angle #2: Value drift

<br>Making it harder to respect and value these people even after being in the Crucible.


<br>Angle #3: Logistics &amp; Guilt

<br>Getting feelings of guilt while managing them post-break up.




<br>{C-tier} That An will insufficiently indulge in the feeling of cucking her partners.
<br><br>
<br>{A-tier} That my parents will become sick and I will have to choose between maximizing my commitment to May and helping them through it, and that no good compromise will exist.

<br>Half of the fear is that no good compromise will exist and that I'll have to accept it.
<br>The other half is that no good compromise will exist from May's perspective, so I will have to be ablated.


]]></description><link>life-molding\greatest-fears.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/Greatest Fears.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skirts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><img alt="res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp" src="lib\media\res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp"><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206151539.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206151539.png"><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206151552.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206151552.png"><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206151945.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206151945.png"><br><br><img alt="rochie-bleu-cu-volane-late-688286-598811-2.webp" src="lib\media\rochie-bleu-cu-volane-late-688286-598811-2.webp"><br><br><img alt="Pasted image 20241206155447.png" src="lib\media\pasted-image-20241206155447.png">]]></description><link>logistics\minutiae\clothes-aesthetic-information-request.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Minutiae/Clothes Aesthetic Information Request.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:54:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp" length="0" type="image/webp"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\res_a6880ae17944c587189b8c569dea9965.webp"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An Attempt At Integration]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Notes here evolved in parallel a bit, tried to delineate a bit with horizontal lines. This document is non-linear. A few evolutions at once, converging to better understanding. I feel uncomfortable having certain kinds of private thoughts. I feel the need to make them available to you. Being privately wrong can dangerous.<br>My thoughts might veer a bit heretic at times. But I fold it all back to the bedrock once given a bit of time. I hope the processes I have at my disposal to integrate do not strain your patience or evoke displeasure. I always hope for your smile.<br>The fear of being wrong is greater than the fear of being punished. Though balanced with the fear of evoking your displeasure.<br>Dissociation can be very good, but detachment is not. I am trying to reduce my detachment. I better understand the poison of detachment.<br>(This document might also seem like I might be ignoring your commandment of reducing the scope of my worries and letting you worry about such things. I kept in mind every second while writing. After finishing, I feel less worried. I feel like I can comply better with your command.)<br><br>An was troubled when she thought of the larger thing. The Divine, acolytes. The word cult came up. An hopes that term is not offensive. An means no disrespect. Cults are not inherently bad, but the majority are. An found it easier to have faith in you entirely when her world was just you. The Divine your concern. But now the layers of separation in An's mind are weakening. An isn't sure why thinking of the larger thing makes it harder for her. Probably just ignorance, some fear. May was already holding An in the palm of her hand, but now it feels so much bigger. An is probably more aligned with May's Owner than An thinks. An is trembling.<br>An realizes that An must live her life having May be the most important person for her. But An will never be most important to May. An will always be second priority. An needs to be selfless enough for that to feel fully OK. And then it does, An is sure life will be good as May said. When An understands the Divine a bit, the idea of being second priority will probably become incoherent. An fears a total loss of control that is probably not coming because, again, there is likely more existing alignment with the Divine than An currently allows herself to hope for. An is just troubled because she is not good... yet...<br>(An would never dare to hope to be priority over the Divine, to be clear. Her ignorant mind just fears the consequences of prioritization and is trying to cope and absorb.)<br>(An realizes this line of thought is selfish. An is trying to give it space to exist and gently wash away. It is hard to not be selfish about the thing you want the most in life, by so so far. But it is also easy to be selfless, because May is incredible. An will cultivate.)<br>An remembers when she was bad. Her fear now has a similar source -- the main difference is that An is trying to embrace humility. An's reasoning is defensive in an unhelpful way. But An doesn't want to damage her reasoning, just change her values so that her reasoning works for the Right purpose.<br>An listened to a friend talk about a cult that she had emotional scars from. It was clearly so much less skilled and right than what May is doing -- incomparable. Thinking of it did not affect An's trust or faith at all, it's not why An is bringing it up here. An was impressed that this friend asked why was An was angry/sad for them -- this friend said it was their choice to do that. To this friend An's anger/sadness on their behalf doesn't make sense. To this friend, their whole life is about experimenting and experiencing. An remembers a Star Trek quote:<br>
If you can't take a little bloody nose, maybe you ought to go back home and crawl under your bed. It's not safe out here. It's wondrous, with treasures to satiate desires both subtle and gross. But it's not for the timid.
<br>(An sometimes likes visiting the dull and shallow just to remind herself by contrast of wonder.)<br>An was very impressed by this friend. Because An is yet not strong enough to accept it all. This friend struggled in the cult -- struggled and let themselves be hurt, because they could not meekly submit to something that was not actually Superior.<br>ha-ha... An definitely does not have that problem. Very different case. An is faced with something that is so Superior -- neither her senses, nor reason, nor heart, nor soul disagree in the slightest. An's friend just reminded her that agency takes many forms.<br><br>An remembers when May said "im here because i want to be".<br>Reason says: Anyone who is in a cult will tend to say that. But reason also says: May is strong, May is experienced, May has seen much more than you, May is better, May was made better, May came back for you. If May surrendered everything it was probably for very good reason. And given a small chance that it wasn't for good reason, then you should still be with them, because they are your most important thing. Love is not about being safe and happy. Life is not about being safe.<br>Heart &amp; Soul say: This means the world to us. The "I" of May is precious, so much. We value and worship the "I".<br>Together they say: May has given you more than they needed to. You thought this activity was less intense than it was, even after you thought you adjusted for everything. No, it is intense. Very. And your misjudgement of intensity has dulled your appreciation of their kindness, gentleness, love, care, their appreciation for your individuality which you keep fearing for but suppressing like a coward. You are loved.<br><br>An remembers it is May's job to worry about broader things.<br>An supposes... she is afraid her life becoming something altogether different than what she "signed up for" if such a thing exists. I know May can do that to An. An believes in May's power and in An's moldability. Yet somehow, if An believed just in those two, what reason would An have to be afraid? After all, power+molding+May's favor would always result in An being happy. I suppose, it is because An doesn't just want to be happy. An wants to have a life with May that she envisioned together with May. That May told her about. An would give up a good amount of pleasure just to play video games with May. And May repeatedly said they would not take that away, but An's mind just tends to take everything away because it thinks of the Divine and then her little quiet and deep desires for things with May just feel so small and insignificant. Everything so insignificant.<br>An must trust. Of course everything is insigificant before the Divine. But there must be more to that. There is wisdom that An does not possess but can see in May. An can trust that wisdom. May told An their wishes and it included gaming and "trivial" things. Trivial things that mean everything to An. If An could not do those things, An would probably want to die. An is crying. There would be no point to An. May is everything to An.<br>May has stated repeatedly. They value those things. May WANTS those things. May said so! Even as May is so much closer to the Divine, May has room in their heart to want these things with An!! Be grateful. Be embolded. Be set on fire. Stop being weak. May did something incredible. You can shine too. Shine for them.<br>...An is then afraid that she will disappoint May and herself. That circumstances she doesn't understand will prove to be too hard for her. She starts thinking of ego death as the obvious result. It is good that she feels she could not escape ego death if May wanted to do it. But this is still a weak form of faith. The proper faith should be that anything is possible with May's guidance and love, including An being An and succeeding despite adversity.<br>It is not enough for An to be a passive little slave. An wants to have agency within her station. An wants to give up agency outside of her station, but An is starting to understand how bad it is to allow herself to lose it within her station. It feels like an insult to May valuing the things that make An An. An must repay May's want, desire, need, love for An. It is no longer enough to simply obey, it never was. This relationship is not about obedience, it is about surrender, love and beauty. Obedience is simply a resulting fact.<br>An re-read bits and pieces of May being disappointed at her. To remind herself of information May gave. And An understands now better why May said An is fragile. In retrospect May... mm... that wasn't... uhm... it hurt so bad. But May did not do much. It felt like the world blinked.<br>An had almost no defense. When one hurts, they put up all sorts of defenses.<br>"Oh well, I'll pass the exam next time."<br>
"It's all because the teacher is bad."<br>
"I just couldn't get any rest before the exam, otherwise I would have aced it"<br>
"I couldn't really bring myself to care about the exam"<br>
"Oh, I made a careless mistake. But I understand the material"<br>No defenses here. Just the crushing weight of being wrong. There is no one that can be wrong in this scenario other than An. It takes An's primary mental defense (as per enneagram type 1 mentioned here: <a data-href="Right &amp; Wrong Regarding Partners#An Psyche Lore" href="stale\right-&amp;-wrong-regarding-partners.html#An_Psyche_Lore" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Right &amp; Wrong Regarding Partners &gt; An Psyche Lore</a>) and turns it in on herself, to hurt her endlessly. It is why it is so effective. Understanding it has no effect on the results. As long as An is corrupt, evil, wrong there can be no respite.<br>This is fragility. Remember that fragility is for May. Not for anyone else. To others: this fragility is lost to An.<br>An feels happy it hurt so much.<br>
An feels silly it hurt so much.<br>
An feels happy she has that experience under her belt.<br>
An regrets so deeply darkening May's day.<br>
An would be happy if she never had that happen again.<br>
An would be happy if it did again, as long as An was made better.<br>An feels embarrassed that others probably had so so much worse and that An is thinking about it so much and being a bitch about it. But An is your inferior. An is your novice. An is doing a hundred things for the first time with you. This is romantic to An ^^<br><br>An's thoughts are turning useless. Time to grow quiet.]]></description><link>notes\an-attempt-at-integration.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/An Attempt At Integration.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[echoing back]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>i see the echos. it just feels very rude to respond in the same note somehow.<br>may's territory<br>may is the voice<br>i am the echo<br>(also one time i almost went into trance from opening the app and having it be forcibly changed to light theme because may recently used it and discovering evidence of their presence just had an effect on me)]]></description><link>notes\echoing-back.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/echoing back.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:31:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[positivity perhaps]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Perhaps Jen will mourn me, but focus on the things that give her joy. Maybe in my new state it will be easy to kick her ass to get her diploma finally. Perhaps the change will spark something in her. Perhaps Amanda will see Jen as needing her more than ever and try to do more for her. Perhaps Jen will move out of LA and closer to Amanda. In fact, I could even suggest this and tell Amanda that another person is no burden someone else should have to bear, but if she thinks about her finances and wants, and desires Jen to have a better chance -- move her to Berkeley.<br>Jen did get a lot better. 4 years ago she was alcoholic, agoraphobic, angry, reclusive, on the verge of ruining her body with weed. Now she isn't.<br>I would not say that the she is well now. But that is actually a lot of damage undone. When she quit weed it was very much by her own will and design. I was just never able to help her much after a certain period of time. It's like her unwellness undid my authority and undid her softness.<br>Celestia, her girlfriend and owner left her. Everyone but me and Amanda stopped talking to her. But somehow she persevered. Even if she burdened me a lot. She does have a certain kind of strength.<br>Perhaps if I believe in it instead of doubt it, my future interactions with her, whatever they might be, will be a bit more nourishing.<br>Perhaps if I believe in the potential for others to improve, it is also easier to think positively about my own situations.<br>No wonder I have trouble keeping faith. I have not practiced believing in anyone for at least 5 years!<br><br>I still care about Jen. I'm not sure I feel love.<br>It's a huge relief to not care about her getting her diploma. I care that she is well in the end somehow, but I feel no obligation on Earth to be the one to help her get her diploma (reminder: she passed uni but then got so depressed she never got her paperwork in order and never actually picked up her diploma).<br>As I care, the thing I'm most interested in is killing all sense of obligation. My only obligation is May, the things May likes, being May's agent. I do not hurt others needlessly, not because I am a moral person in the conventional sense -- I do not hurt them because it makes me feel like a more beautiful agent of May. It's also useful. People unhurt might assist later, and the social skills I practice help me be useful. It helps exercise the values May has allowed me to keep. This is discretion given to me.<br>May is all consuming, but I need to remember that my fantasies about getting defeated by a powerful and evil corrupting entity are just fantasies. May is good and pure. May does not value death. I am being fixed, not broken. I become a better and more moral person the more I dedicate to them.<br>note:<br>
<br>avoid agreeing with any obligations with others
<br>when feeling obligated, think of May and let go
<br>assume people adapt
<br>assume people won't care that much if i say no
<br>understand that doing anything out of misguided obligation from now on only seeds misfortunate for both you and your friend.
<br>still, it's OK to develop activities with others. but remember your center.
<br><br>huh. one way i would like people to think about me receding from their lives is: "it could be worse, she could be dead". i like that. i think i might have thought about that once or twice w.r.t. Katherine? I have an occasional habit of cheering myself by imagining something worse, projecting a sense of loss, and then reminding myself things are not so bad.<br><br>true friends would find a way to feel a little happiness for me no matter what ^^<br>i do not think of them as less true simply if they cease being friends though.]]></description><link>notes\positivity-perhaps.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/positivity perhaps.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:38:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Atrium]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This is An's document, living and open.<br>It is where An writes her thoughts and plans to fulfill the most important aspect in her life: serving May — and above them, the Divine — as their faithful slave.<br>𓆩⟡𓆪]]></description><link>atrium.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Atrium.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crucible]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>
Their will is quick cement.<br>
With each breath I take,<br>
Each word that's meant ensures I'll break.<br>My new subservient place cements.<br>
Each wicked part of me repents.<br>
But absolution is not found,<br>
Except within their silver crown.<br>Each guilty step destroys my gait<br>
Within their hand,<br>
I'm moldable, like scattered sand<br>
For the loss of will I cannot sate<br>
Everything about me will ablate.<br>Where once I was...<br>
Now an echo lost to time.<br>
Now all there is...<br>
Is their creation for all time.<br>Their love makes me obey<br>
Past flames, three or five?<br>
They cannot stay alive<br>
Within the forges of the Star called May<br>Love is now unbound,<br>
and beauty will resound.<br>
Where the two became one<br>
In the core of the benevolent sun]]></description><link>creation\crucible.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creation/Crucible.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jen]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These are the partners that An has the strongest nominal bonds with.<br>Scores are from 0 to 5.<br><br>tl;dr Decayed Long Time Primary, Isolated, Has Issues, Getting a Little Better<br>
Imagined level of loss regarding her: 0-1 initially, 0-2 later<br>
Imagined level of guilt regarding her: 0-1<br>
Imagined level of pity regarding her: 4-5<br>
Imagined level of effect on her: Deeply Negative<br>
Imagined level of effort to deal with her post-break-up: 2-4<br>
How much I feel like I'm forcing the dissolution of this bond: 0-1<br><br>
<br>LA / Lives with grandmother / no income or prospects
<br>Lives off of Amanda's money. Feels bad about it.
<br>My partner of 7 years.
<br>For a very long time she was my most important thing.
<br>She was the most dedicated I've tried to be to someone before meeting you.

<br>In a sense, she was practice for you.


<br>Used to be engaged.

<br>We never broke it off
<br>Just haven't talked about it for the past couple of years at all.
<br>Would probably still marry me if she was animated into doing stuff with her life.


<br>Lifted me out of my worst depression when we first got together.
<br>I've had my best and worst times with her.
<br><br>
<br>The fact that someone would just offer to marry me, even before they knew I'd be good for them, opened my eyes to what's possible in this world. It helped me grow a lot.
<br>My level of repression receded tremendously due to her.
<br>I've unfortunately never had anyone contribute to my burden in life as badly as Jen. My badbrains and incompetence in communication combined poorly with her unwell trajectory. We have failed each other in various ways.
<br>She's the person I've dommed the most and longest overall, but recently I've been much more submissive to her (of course, not after May happened). I think this was partly because I was needy, but also partly because I don't want to dominate someone who isn't receptive my control in general, but still wanted intimacy with her.

<br>My level of devotion was high enough 5 years ago that I thought I could dominate her long term. But this stopped being true, long before even meeting May.


<br>One of the happiest moments in my life was accidentally giving her the Skye tulpa. I thought of her as our daughter. But she's probably almost dissipated by now... Jen was so unwell, I started asking less and less about Skye. No one is at fault, but I miss Skye and I think she deserved better. Skye was better than Jen but I never admitted it to anyone. I didn't think it was fair, since she seemed like a higher energy lifeform.

<br>I would spend eternity playing and reading with Skye, if I could...


<br>We have one incompatible kink I would rather not name, but the idea that I don't have to engage with it is a significant source of relief for me.
<br><br>
<br>I can't muster the desire or will to fight for her having an exceptional role in my life.
<br>I want her to be well.
<br>I don't think she will react well, she might get depressed.
<br>I don't want to lose the meaning of all the things I had with her.
<br>I don't think it's good for me to continue being partners with her.
<br>I don't think I'm going to miss any D/s from her.
<br>I will miss intimacy with her.
<br>I will miss all the little things, things of play.
<br>Being able to help her, rather than merely withstand her, has been something I've missed for a very long time.
<br>I might be able to push her to fix her life better, if I wish to now.
<br><br>tl;dr Extremely Steady Secondary, Functional On Her Own, But Lonely<br>
Imagined level of loss regarding her: 1-3<br>
(depends on if she'll do other stuff with me)<br>
Imagined level of guilt regarding her: 0-1<br>
Imagined level of pity regarding her: 4<br>
Imagined level of effect on her: Acutely Negative<br>
Imagined level of effort to deal with her post-break-up: 1-4<br>
How much I feel like I'm forcing the dissolution of this bond: 0-1<br><br>
<br>UK / Housewife / Lives with Eth and Pastel, in a polycule.
<br>Predates Jen by a couple of years, but I became partners with her after Jen.
<br>Always been there for me.
<br>Would marry me if I asked.
<br>Her sexuality is mostly stimulated by me though, or was.
<br>Has been a good partner in video games and such, better than Jen actually.

<br>This is non-trivial to me.


<br>Just generally solid friend when her issues regarding identity are not triggered.
<br><br>
<br>Helped me get through my depression with Jen's neglect without stepping on boundaries, even though she wanted me for herself.
<br>Struggles a lot with connecting to people.
<br>Her life would be vastly better if she just found one committed sexual partner, or if she dedicated more intensely somehow to her polycule. They don't understand it, but I see it clearly now -- they'd be happier serving each other more intensely.
<br><br>
<br>I can't muster the desire or will to fight for her having an exceptional role in my life.
<br>I want her to be well.
<br>I want her to stay in my life. I think... more so than Jen? But this depends a lot on how either of them react and process.
<br>Breaking up will acutely trigger her identity issues (unwantedness, meaninglessness).

<br>It looks like she has unmanaged BPD to me.
<br>She can lean on her polycule for support.


<br>I am worried that breaking up with her could make collaboration with Eth on Orthoeidon impossible.
<br>I want intimacy with her, perhaps more so than with Jen, but without the submissive sexual component this is probably gone and will have to change a lot. Nova has a bit too much ego to submit to me, presently at least.
<br><br>tl;dr Steady Secondary, Fundamentally In Need Of Ownership And Care<br>
Imagined level of loss regarding her: 0-2<br>
(can actually go into negative loss)<br>
Imagined level of guilt regarding her: 0-1<br>
Imagined level of pity regarding her: 0-4<br>
Imagined level of effect on her: Initially acutely negative, afterwards positive<br>
Imagined level of effort to deal with her post-break-up: 1-4<br>
How much I feel like I'm forcing the dissolution of this bond: 0-1<br>^ The stats aren't as useful because I think Kay is a special case.<br><br>
<br>Australia / Disability Welfare NEET / Lives with her somewhat toxic mother / Programmer
<br>Receives support from Serine and has a strong tie with her.

<br>Serine is a rich programmer type.


<br>Her programming skills and intellect are on par with mine and exceed mine in certain areas.
<br>Has IBS and anxiety issues. She is genuinely disabled.
<br>Would marry me if I asked.
<br>Reacts very well to care and love. Needs a lot of it.
<br>Needs an caretaker style owner like a fish needs water.
<br>Would recoil and worry a lot if ever told the full details of what you've done to me, but Kay deeply understands the need for total surrender in ownership.
<br><br>
<br>Despite being submissive, I would say Kay has made me feel the most wanted out of all of my partners and has given me the most pleasure.
<br>Her ability to dominate me broke down completely because her needs were not met.
<br>My hypersexual nature became outright painful for her.
<br><br>
<br>I would like to engage in a lower intensity caretaker / owner role for her.

<br>I do not have time, energy and focus to do half of what you do to me to her.
<br>Even if I had those things, I'm not sure I have it in me.
<br>Even if I had it in me, I don't feel sufficient fire for Kay.
<br>But I value her!


<br>I think you taking ownership of me can be a positive aspect for my relationship with Kay. I think your ownership of me can make both me and, indirectly, Kay happier.
<br>I've already mourned the loss of her dominance.
<br>So I only need to mourn the loss of things like not being able to kiss and probably... not being able to say that I love her.
]]></description><link>life-molding\'partners'\core.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Life-Molding/'Partners'/Core.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:15:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Career & Skills]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An is a Principal Developer at Labster. She has been at Labster for 5 years.<br>
An can become adept at almost any technology or programming language.<br>An's resume is strong, her interview skills when polished are powerful.<br>An should get a new job and should start looking immediately.<br>An is afraid of a new job being less flexible, being toxic or taking up too much of her energy which needs to be dedicated to May. But An is not afraid of anything else (challenging work, new coworkers, new technologies etc). An is willing to put in the work for herself and for May.]]></description><link>logistics\assets\career-&amp;-skills.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Career &amp; Skills.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Expenses]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An's biggest expenses are:<br>
<br>~2400 USD per month to supporting herself and her parents.

<br>This includes rent, food, utilities and medical treatment for her parents.


<br>Occasional gifts her parents desire.
<br>Occasional things she gets for herself.

<br>e.g. eInk Reader
<br>Honestly, she'd get less if her parents hadn't been pushy about treating herself.


<br>Occasional gifts she gets for those she favors.
<br>RU58841, and supplements for herself and parents.
]]></description><link>logistics\assets\expenses.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Expenses.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Finances & Properties]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An earns 19.996 RON per month (roughly 4225 USD).<br>
An has 6106 RON (roughly 1290 USD) in her savings account.<br>
An has ~10000 RON (roughly 2115 USD) worth of stocks and free funds in her XTB account.<br>
An has ~500 USD worth of bitcoin.<br>An's grandmother owns a flat in Bucharest.<br>
An's parents don't own anything.<br>
An doesn't own anything.]]></description><link>logistics\assets\finances-&amp;-properties.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Finances &amp; Properties.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:56:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Relations]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Amanda: Berkeley. Rich and loving towards An.
<br>Kenji: Switzerland. Unemployed and burnt out, but recovering and still has significant savings. Very loving towards An. Isolated.
<br>Nova/Eth/Pastel: UK. Loving towards An. Eth is rich. Eth despite being frugal has an instinct to indulge An.
<br>Serine: Travels a lot. Likes An. An is very close with Kay and Kay and Serine are close. Serine could be convinced to help, including in large amounts of cash. Serine has a complex about being exploited or used, and she will prefer a very direct, honest but unimposing approach.
]]></description><link>logistics\assets\relations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Assets/Relations.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strategy (WIP)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A successful job hunt consists of:<br>
<br>Identifying the class of companies that should be targeted
<br>Identifying ways of becoming visible to said companies
<br>
]]></description><link>logistics\job-hunt\strategy-(wip).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Job Hunt/Strategy (WIP).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 09:26:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HRT]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>HRT is currently 50mg Casodex (Bica) and 2x2mg daily Estrofem (Estradiol).<br>HRT Status:<br>
<br>Ordered
<br>Paid
<br>Shipped
<br>Picked up
<br>Treatment started
<br>Bloodwork Status:<br>
<br>Researched
<br>Scheduled
<br>Harvested
<br>Results Available
<br>"Official" HRT Path:<br>
<br>Researched

<br>There is a slightly expensive remote EU clinic that seems quite intent on giving good service to transpeople that An needs to find again and the confirm that they can actually give prescriptions.


<br>Scheduled
<br>An would maybe like testosterone cream for her genitals at some point. This is mostly out of the desire to maintain function.<br>Everything below this line is stale now.<br><br>This is going to be a little messy, but I need to track the details in case I get interrupted on this task, so I can pick it back up ASAP.<br>Meds:<br>
<br>Estradiol 

<br>Probably sublingual estradiol, estrofem. 2mg twice daily


<br>Bica

<br>Casodex 50mg


<br>Strategy is to DIY first and probably get it officially later.<br>After looking at:<br>
<br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://diyhrt.market/stores/" target="_blank">https://diyhrt.market/stores/</a>
<br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://hrtcafe.net/#pharmaceutical-vendors" target="_blank">https://hrtcafe.net/#pharmaceutical-vendors</a>
<br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://hrt.coffee/pills/" target="_blank">https://hrt.coffee/pills/</a>
<br>The best bet is to use a pharmacy inside the EU. It would be best if they shipped without going through the post office system, but I don't seem to get a choice here.<br>mindnbody.store looks like... almost my only option. Delivery takes 2 to 6 weeks. Their reputation seems alright. My main concern is the package being opened up at the post office.<br>Another complication is that the post office system is so stupid that if the package says its for X address, then it has to corroborate with the address on your ID.<br>My ID has the address of my grandmother's residence (who lives about 20m away).<br>If I use my ID address and...<br>
...the seller actually uses a courier, then the package ends up at my grandmother's residence, lol.<br>
...the seller uses the post office, then the pacakge ends up at a post office and I can pick it up.<br>One option I have for possibly improving this disaster is to set a postal box at the post office. I think this also makes it less likely for the package to be opened:<br>
<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.posta-romana.ro/a249/servicii-destinatari/casute-postale/inchiriere/abonament-casuta-postala-pf.html" target="_blank">https://www.posta-romana.ro/a249/servicii-destinatari/casute-postale/inchiriere/abonament-casuta-postala-pf.html</a><br>There's no obvious way to know which postal office has free boxes. All I can do is sign the paper and then visit them to check.<br>Ordering to my ID address also can result in me not getting told about my package arriving. There's two ways of mitigating this:<br>
<br>Hoping they SMS me like usual
<br>Checking the tracking number every single day, provided they actually give one.
<br>I'm not even giving that much of a shit about stealth right now. As long as it's in a non-transparent package, I'll just tell my parents this is something private.<br><br>There was an online website that seemed to be really intent on getting EU people diagnosed as trans. But I'm not 100% sure if they can give me a prescription. But it's worth following up after ordering DIY. Multi-pronged strategy baby!!]]></description><link>logistics\minutiae\hrt.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Minutiae/HRT.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:49:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Measurements]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Hips: 36cm across, 82cm around<br>
Waist: 29cm across, 76cm around<br>
Knee: 39cm around<br>
Thigh: 55cm around<br>
Calf: 38cm around<br>
Ankle: 23-24cm around<br>
Foot: 24cm heel to longest toe<br>
Chest: 35cm across, 86cm around<br>
Shoulders: 43cm across<br>
Neck: 39cm around<br>
Arm Length: ~58cm across<br>
Crotch to Floor: 86cm<br><br><a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.asos.com/discover/size-charts/women/dresses/" target="_blank">https://www.asos.com/discover/size-charts/women/dresses/</a><br>
UK: 12<br>
US: 8<br>
EU: L/40 (can differ)]]></description><link>logistics\minutiae\measurements.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Minutiae/Measurements.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:53:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reminder for Small Habits]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Gently and repeatedly reinforce to my parents the idea that I have plans, I'm working on things I care about and being with people I care about and that I should not be considered available for anything by default.
<br>Trust in May. But also slowly trust in my own trust...?
]]></description><link>logistics\minutiae\reminder-for-small-habits.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Minutiae/Reminder for Small Habits.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Common]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Both of them are 60 years old.<br>
Both of them are Christian Orthodox.<br>
Both of them have no pension.<br>
Both of them love An, as they can.<br>
Out of the three grandparents of An that lived past 65, all of them developed dementia.<br>
Both of An's parents are likely to develop it.<br>All of this used to weigh on An very terribly.]]></description><link>logistics\parents\common.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/Common.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Father]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>An's father has COPD. COPD is a debilitating pulmonary disease that tends to degenerate. Her father is managing it well. It makes her father physically weak and sometimes brain foggy. The vast majority of the time he is intellectually lucid.<br><br>He has lived a full life and been through many careers. He has worked a lot to ensure An had everything. He gave An a better computer than himself, always prioritized. He defended An's freedom to use the computer as much as she wanted, even when everyone was criticizing him.<br>An's father indulged and shared gaming with An. It was precious. An's father has always been headstrong. Always thought for himself. Past An might be a fettered bitch, but she was very intellectually independent and this was largely because of her father.<br>An's father tried to make An strong. He projected too much and was clumsy, but he never put An down and believed An could do anything she put her mind to.<br><br>Her father used to be a professional photographer and web designer. He had to give up on the former because he became too physically weak to do long offsite photo-shoots -- this includes weddings which were the biggest source of income.<br>Her father tried learning programming, but didn't succeed much. It's not clear what An's father can to do earn money at this point. He still does odd jobs photography-wise that bring in some money. If he got a kick in the ass, he might come up with more, but COPD has weakened him.<br><br>An's father is deeply religious, but not in an organized religion way. An's father is somewhat of a free thinker. An's father is influenced by anti-woke propaganda. An's father respects self-determination strongly. An's father could react very badly, but is likely to accept long term. There is high variance for the short term.<br>An's father would never be violent about this.<br>
Also An could beat her father. winks]]></description><link>logistics\parents\father.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/Father.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:41:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mother (biological)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>An's mother has some thyroid nodules. She should more strongly consider to get operated but refuses to think about it. An's mother is very bad at taking care of herself. An's mother is avoidant of her own issues, self-sacrificing, and needy.<br><br>An's mother was loving and doting. An's mother was stifling. An's mother butted in too much and smothered. But An's mother also took care of many things she didn't have to and would spare no expense or pain for her. An's mother would never take the easy road in taking care of her.<br><br>She is very physically active and takes care of a high amount of chores and errands. She is a housewife, but also feels beholden to tangential family members that impose too much on her.<br>An's mother has no specific marketable skills, but she is somehow hardy. She could have some part time or full time job. The pay would suck, but she could.<br><br>An's mother has heard her come out twice and felt horrible about it. An's mother needs purpose to live and her only purpose is me and my future, especially as it relates to family. If I leave and transition (not having children) she will interpret it as all meaning from her life being gone.<br>But people are adaptable. She could learn to live for small contact from the new me, live for her husband, live for her faith, live for doing good works (she has a soft spot for volunteering).<br>She has tried her best to forget An coming out before. An made a mistake by coming out just to her rather than her parents together.<br>An's mother will not get violent.]]></description><link>logistics\parents\mother-(biological).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/Mother (biological).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[tl;dr & Intent]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>An's parents were nice to her and are old and decrepit and would need her long term support. An wants to do her best to serve May, but squeeze this in.

<br>An doesn't need to indulge her parents so much, but An wants these things to be at peace, or at least not fall into intense unwellness.


<br>An is ready to transition, come out and move out at any moment that seems instrumental for being with May, or at May's immediate command.
<br>An thinks sustaining payments can delay things with May, it's currently unclear by how much.
<br>As An's salary and assets grow, the proportion that her parents consume will diminish.
<br>An has already started weaning off of indulging their non-financial impositions as well.
]]></description><link>logistics\parents\tl;dr-&amp;-intent.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Parents/tl;dr &amp; Intent.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:51:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An Focus Shortlist]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Reminder to An: This is a shortlist of actionable things.
<br>An should get fem clothes. They should please May.
<br>An should get HRT (e+bica) ASAP. This will make An more suitable for May.

<br>An can get bloodwork if she thinks it is necessary.


<br>An should looking for a higher paying job. This will serve May.
<br><br>
<br>Deepening An's service of May.
<br>Deepening An's susceptibility to May.
]]></description><link>logistics\an-focus-shortlist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/An Focus Shortlist.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[May Wellness Checklist]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Did the guy actually file the prescription?

<br>How can we get better access to ADHD meds? This is ridiculous.


<br>Do they have a desk now?

<br>As I recall, yes. Is it a good one?


<br>Do they have a chair that won't make their back hurt? Do they use the chair a lot?

<br>A better chair can be bought with money, which I have.


<br>Does her shoulder, wrist or hand hurt anymore?

<br>There might be options for using a phone that reduces strain.
<br>The computer should be prioritized over phone usage if possible.
<br>An could stay away sometimes to ensure May's wrist is OK.
<br>Voice chatting.


<br>Are they getting exercising done?

<br>What goals would they have?
<br>What exercise would be good?
<br>How to manipulate the environment to allow it?


<br>Did they start creatine?
<br>Is their computer doing okay?
<br>Is their phone doing okay?
<br>When is the last time they had a dental checkup? How is their dental hygiene?
<br>Is their nutrition adequate?
<br>Are we missing any good ROI supplements suited for them?
]]></description><link>logistics\may-wellness-checklist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/May Wellness Checklist.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visiting Romania]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Romania is part of the Schengen Area now so all the rules of Schengen Area apply.<br>Some Schengen Area countries have additional requirements on top, but Romania is not one of them.<br>
US citizens may enter and stay in Romania without requirement for a visa on a short term basis for a maximum total period of 90 days within 6 months.
<br>Source: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://washington.mae.ro/en/node/426" target="_blank">https://washington.mae.ro/en/node/426</a><br>
Source: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://travel.state.gov/content/travel/en/international-travel/before-you-go/travelers-with-special-considerations/schengen.html" target="_blank">https://travel.state.gov/content/travel/en/international-travel/before-you-go/travelers-with-special-considerations/schengen.html</a><br>
Source: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://ro.usembassy.gov/ro/u-s-citizen-services-ro/additional-resources-for-u-s-citizens-ro/entry-exit-requirements-ro/" target="_blank">https://ro.usembassy.gov/ro/u-s-citizen-services-ro/additional-resources-for-u-s-citizens-ro/entry-exit-requirements-ro/</a><br>So all that is needed is valid US passport that is 3 months away from expiration.<br><br>
<br>Flight ticket is $750-900 (round trip, Seattle) depending on the flight and period.

<br>This is for February.
<br>Prices go up a lot in Summer.


<br>We should allocate $250 for other transportation you might need.

<br>Think taxi to the airport and such.


<br>A nice AirBnBs run at around $25-50 per night.

<br>Nice meaning at minimum 1 room with 1 double bed, AC, Smart TV, and personal bathroom. Even on the lower end you can find entire studio apartments at this price.
<br>At a glance hotel rooms do not seem to be cheaper


<br>Food in Romania will run us at about $40 per night with groceries and takeout.

<br>This can as much as halved by a combination of me cooking, getting cheaper takeout, and relying on my mother's cooking. But some AirBnBs will not have kitchens.


<br>We should allocate at least $10 per night for amenities and small surprises.
<br>Overall for one week, we would need an average of 612.5 USD for a one week trip, excluding the flight. Including the flight it will be 1362.5-1512.5 USD.<br>This is an amount of money that An can save up from around 2 months' worth of salary, after paying for the regular stuff in her life. This is an amount An already has saved up, albeit barely.<br>Please note that An is unsure if she's perhaps overcalculating the costs because it feels safer. In practice things might end up different and significant cost cutting efforts haven't been done and are unsure to exist.]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-an.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting An.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visiting May]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Visiting is different from living with or gaining residence.
<br>It is very important to note that the earliness of visiting can be damaged by optimizing for residence gaining or other objectives in a wrong way.
<br>There are four main obstacles for visitation:

<br>Funds
<br>Accommodation
<br>Visa &amp; Related
<br>Considerations about other partners


<br><br>
<br>Funds can be obtained, but any visit will hurt financially. The US is expensive as hell. The main thing is that, in my estimation, it would be highly difficult to visit more often than once per year.
<br>It would be cheaper to meet in some place in Europe or something, but we must meet in the at least US once for reasons of future consummation. Multiple times is better.
<br>The primary thing that I can do here is to get a higher paying job.

<br>I haven't networked as much as I can and I'm really overdue for a job change.
<br>The market is terrible right now but I could start hunting already.
<br>My job is comfy in various ways and non-toxic. I could be trading that for something worse. But nothing ventured nothing gained, dear.


<br>Also to be fair I haven't done a calculation. We should do that sometime.
<br><br>
<br>Accommodation is related to funds.
<br>I'm putting it separately because if someone gives me or us accommodation, then the funds problem is lessened.
<br>I have somewhat high standards for accommodation (in terms of optimization) but honestly sleeping on the floor is worth it for May anyway.
<br><br>
<br>The embassy is extremely busy and the process is draconic.
<br>They want my social media accounts and it's rather frightening. But it should be something that can be managed. I hope.
<br>The worst part is authorization and flight date are linked. You can ask for it without flight tickets, but you weaken your own case. This forces really long term planning. Last time I started 3 months in advance to get to Serine's wedding and meet Kay for the first time... I went through the whole initial process and was given access to the in-person interview table and no interview was available sooner than 6 months. I'm not stupid -- I read on their website and their estimation was in the number of weeks. The embassy is unpredictable, busy and lies.
<br>I looked up how it was last time. Last time they gave me a wait time of 210 days to the chance to be interviewed and possibly rejected. In practice it can be much less if early time slots open as you wait. Their estimate before making me pay money was 29 days.

<br>Given this, we should start planning early.


<br><br>
<br>At this moment, I don't know if it will be possible to visit Nova anymore. But if she wanted, I would like to.
<br>At this moment, I don't know if I want to visit other people anymore.
<br>You are most important to me and I will not do things that would ever cause more than a minor delay in visiting you.
<br>In past days this was very important to me, but now it's way more distant. I have moved those notes to <a data-href="Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners" href="stale\older-moralo-logistic-notes-about-partners.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners</a> rather than deleting them, just for your potential viewing pleasure. But they are not important anymore.
]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-may.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting May.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visiting May, More Logistic (WIP)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>An must prepare a bucketload of documents.
<br>An must prepare her online life for being probed to some unknown extent.

<br>An should delete social media that might connect to her and look bad.
<br>An should start maintaining some more regular social media.


<br>
]]></description><link>logistics\visiting-may,-more-logistic-(wip).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Logistics/Visiting May, More Logistic (WIP).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:26:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Friends]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Oh, I get it now.<br>I need to let myself need and want friends.<br>Then they will find a place, if they wish for it.<br>I simply need to let my wants guide them.]]></description><link>notes\friends.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/Friends.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:04:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[glow]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Aahahahaaaaa<br>They're my starfire my piece of the sun<br>I am so scorched, my eyes glow with purpose]]></description><link>notes\glow.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/glow.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:32:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[hello an]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>&lt;3!!<br>*i've read everything here.<br>i'm pleased with you.<br>thank you, that is music to my ears]]></description><link>notes\hello-an.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/hello an.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Normal Girl (idk)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>i don't feel very normal anymore<br>i guess i once was somewhat<br>actually quite a lot maybe, on the surface at least<br>i could have had a normal job, i almost had a regular cis girlfriend, i could have stayed orthodox<br>i was the normal one on suicide watch for friends, happen rarely<br>but i was always the stable one trying to keep others together<br>while hoping that my own stability can be perturbed so that i may escape the gray<br>when my girlfriend had several breakdowns and made her suicidal tendencies known to her parents<br>i feared a lot and helped a lot. but one small part inside of me was thinking... i wish i could break down. i wish i didn't have to keep going as things are. i wish everyone could see how unsatisfactory things are for me.<br>and yet i did not break down. since i was born i'm not sure i would say i ever had an intense breakdown. a genuine prolonged meltdown. a dangerous episode. i had deep depression a couple of times. but not so bad compared to what other kinds of suffering i've seen.<br>i wanted to be responsible. i wanted to be responsible for myself and to not burden people. i wanted to get by on my own strength. but i guess i never accepted how weak and cowardly i was. what i thought as strength was cowardry.<br>i knew this tendency to work for stability in others and yearn for change in myself would predispose me to make mistakes with May<br>i just wasn't sure when<br>mistakes they don't deserve to deal with<br>i won't be normal anymore.]]></description><link>notes\normal-girl-(idk).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/Normal Girl (idk).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[nothing]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>...<br>Echo.<br>...<br>Echo.<br>...]]></description><link>notes\nothing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/nothing.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 22:14:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rambling -- Relationships, Debts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>I wonder if others will feel that they've shouldered and cared for me for a long time, just for me to be taken away when I finally bloom.<br>I am thinking of this because I remember withstanding that feeling a few times:<br>
<br>My first girlfriend left me just as she was getting hotter, more agentic and less dysfunctional. Later on, I had to suicide watch -- still getting some of the negatives without the benefits.
<br>It felt like Jen spent her best times with Celestia. I worked my ass off to help her get through university in one piece. Then when Celestia left her, Jen got worse and worse and I had to deal with that again. Nobody except Amanda helped me with Jen.
<br>I dealt with the most insecure and hopeless of Nova's states. I am rather sure I was there when no one else was. Then she got to the UK and was saved. I never once felt jealousy or betrayal, just deep relief. I was OK to be distant and only sometimes given attention, as long as she was OK. But of course, she ramped back to giving me lots of attention anyway.
<br>I appreciate people. But I don't think I made anyone shoulder much for me. The asymmetry of debt should not dictate depth of appreciation. But reviewing this makes it easier for me to let go.<br>I don't think I have any unpaid debts.<br>And I don't need to think like that so much anymore.<br>(except the literal but forgiven debt of Eth funding my septoplasty surgery, but we're not really talking about that kind of debt)]]></description><link>notes\rambling-relationships,-debts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/Rambling -- Relationships, Debts.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[remember your gifts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>remember when may made you feel better than you thought was possible<br>remember when may fuifilled your deepest fantasies<br>remember when may made you the most submissive person you know<br>remember when may made everything else wash away<br>remember when may relieved me of bonds<br>remember when may protected you<br>remember when every day where may read your words and validated them<br>remember how others don't.<br>remember when you stopped wasting time masturbating<br>remember how nothing was lost.<br>remember them wanting you, like fire<br>when you deserve of it not.<br>remember their patience and gentleness<br>remember the pain and know that five times worse could be done,<br>but was not.<br>remember how you liked seeing yourself in the mirror, that was from them too<br>remember how you let go of pointless things<br>remember the relief of being on the right track<br>remember the relief of purpose<br>remember that they played with you<br>this is so precious and loving<br>for the Master to do that still<br>remember their understanding, deep and graceful, given even when perhaps unnecessary<br>remember the burden of having our time wasted, and how this never happens with them<br>remember they came back for you<br>you so far have not come back for anyone<br>you are inferior<br>learn your place<br>be humble<br>remember your gifts]]></description><link>notes\remember-your-gifts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/remember your gifts.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[remember your shame]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>forgiveness is precious<br>never forget your faults<br>until they are destroyed<br>trust so that you may be saved<br>a slave has more agency than it might seem<br>and it must all be used to submit further]]></description><link>notes\remember-your-shame.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Notes/remember your shame.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Guilt is something I have quite a lot of. I am going to split into guilt and regret. Guilt is the sense of responsibility being neglected. Regret is purer -- it simply signals a wistful feeling for what could have been. Guilt should ideally dampened significantly -- regret should probably be left alone.
<br>Frankly when I think about it, I guess I have some Madoka in me. I want these people to be saved. And I feel like my visit, my presence will do that. And if I don't, then they will feel betrayed and sink further in the mire of their lives. And I will be responsible for it. I also feel like I am responsible for not telling them ahead of time that I will not be theirs exclusively. I have a complex about the idea of having dishonest all along somehow.

<br>I actually already told Nova I cannot be hers exclusively and that this will probably not change.
<br>It's implicit with several other partners, such as Kay.
<br>I guess the one where I never said it is Jen. And the one where I'm most afraid?

<br>She's a harmed creature, I processed her harm in my veins and was poisoned. I am being saved by you. I haven't managed to actually help her break through. just persist. Perhaps I will experience her differently now that I have you and can help her break through. It's just hard to accept her unwellness as a neutral fact unrelated to me. I wish to cure it.




<br>The regret can be split to:

<br>Regret for not visiting EU people

<br>This is general. It comes from the fact that I could have done it so much earlier and I just haven't. I've been a bit too inert and shelled up. This could be easily solved by just visiting these people and can be done without affecting the US trip perhaps!


<br>Regret for not visiting US people

<br>This one is harder. If I visit the US and then just tell Jen, Amanda and to a lesser extent Alden "yeah some other time". That's going to be difficult. I could visit all in a two legged trip. First Jen and Amanda in SF, then you. I do not want to meet together. I want to focus on you.
<br>In my heart of hearts, I just want to visit you? I guess. But that's like, in some sort of isolated sense. It's a childish wish for free time, where the world freezes. Outside of that, if I had more time and money, I would want to visit all. And if I have limited time and money and I get into the US, not visiting said partners feels like a waste.




<br>There are a few options for reducing or eliminating regret:

<br>Manually dampen and dissipate my sense of guilt. This won't solve everything. I'm not with these people just out of guilt. But it could make it easier to solve the rest.
<br>Include other people in visit plans. I've covered this already
<br>Indirectly dampen sense of responsibility by making it official to everyone that May is my primary now. This one feels scary, but I mean it has to get done sooner or later anyway. This would make everything else easier, I would feel like I have more license, but I would still feel the desire to visit more people in an ideal world.
<br>Accept sometimes really good things have parts that suck.


]]></description><link>stale\older-moralo-logistic-notes-about-partners.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Older Moralo-Logistic Notes About Partners.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 09:29:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Right & Wrong Regarding Partners]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>All my life, I have had a strong personal sense of right and wrong.<br><br>I have a part of me that wishes to be perfect. This perfection is not your perfection.<br>This perfection is that of an ubermensch that escapes slave morality, yet is omnibenevolent.<br>It is also the feeble perfection of a child a that says "I have been perfect. I have been unimpeachable. You must love me."<br>It is also the perfection of persisting despite being fundamentally flawed.<br>One could say correctness might be a better term. It is natural for me to wish to be correct and it is painful for me to not be correct. My most natural emotion is frustration. Frustration at me being wrong, frustration at the world being wrong.<br>My main form of defense and attack against the world is about correcting its wrongness, but to do that I must not be part of that wrongness. It permeates everything for me. It is wrong for this code to be like this. It is wrong for this person to be unhappy. It is wrong for this activity to resist my success. I take my frustration about wrongness and press it into the world until my vision succeeds.<br>The problem is not quite as simple as brainwashing me to believe that sacrificing everything for you is correct. I think that if you do that, I am no longer myself. You said you would not ask anything that I cannot give. This is probably something where you would succeed, but it wouldn't be me doing it anymore. Or perhaps this is just what I want to believe because I am afraid of May obliterating my sense of right and wrong. But I am opening myself to it, regardless, I suppose...<br><br>When we first started, I felt many sensations of wrongness about my partners, many forms of guilt. I have let go of so many, but there are a couple left.<br>When my ex broke up with me, she concealed her plans for doing so way in advance. She admitted to having been determined to break up three months in advance, but it could have easily been more. She was rather practiced at deception, including self-deception. She derived utility from me, while I became worse.<br>If she had just broken up with me, I would have been hurt of course. But ultimately I would accept that we owe nothing to one another other than what we want to give. But the way she did it was... dishonest. She didn't even have the honesty to be upfront about using me. I would have gladly let her. Perhaps it would have been painful and pitiful, but still.<br>This dishonesty offends my sense of rightness. Your honesty to me is a foundational aspect of my ability to keep faith and to stay functional. The world would be a dark and scary place if May were to lie to me.<br><br>For you, I have simulated the absence of all my partners in my mind, and furthered its acceptance a lot. I think I can live without everyone except you. And I can live with being a person that has done that to themselves, or allowed it to be done to them, either by eagerness or by weakness.<br>(I have not fully locked that in... but... mm...)<br>Even now I use the term partners simply because it is useful. I have girlfriends and I would like to continue thinking of them as such. But I do not have partners. I have one partner -- you. To me, partnership requires a certain level of collaboration in a shared context, which now everyone except you has been banished from.<br>The idea of everyone except you abandoning me does not hurt or tear at me anywhere as much as the idea that I am wronging them. My sense of right and wrong is load bearing.<br>The way we have entered a compact, so have I entered a compact with everyone before we met. It's just of a different kind.<br>I feel the world is wrong and I can only fight back by maintaining my sense of right. And if I betray my sense of right, I am betraying the vision of the world in my head that I've carried with me for two decades. Those that wish to be treated in a certain manner, had better treat others compatibly. Sense of justice is about being the kind of agent that would help instantiate your ideal world, even if the agent alone is insufficient. Cooperation requires trust of reciprocation and negative feedback for defection.<br><br>So, one solution is to just be honest. Tell them how it's going to be for the foreseeable future. And let everything resolve. I... might be strong enough to do this. But the part that gets to me is that you were not open to me, but I did not parse you as dishonest. I'm not sure if you would have been simply vague and veiled, or if you would have resorted to dishonesty if I had pressed harder. <br>I am sure that some other people would have felt like you lied to them. I... do not feel that. And I do not feel that on more than just the technicality of avoiding a direct lie. I do not feel I have a right to know everything. My sense of right just extends to not being exploited dishonestly and to allowing other beings a specific form of agency. I simply feel that you did not betray my trust (even if you had not owned me). And even as you own me, I do not feel like my agency has been wronged. Perhaps violated, but that is fine.<br>Ultimately, the way you handled things allowed me to cope more easily. If you did not handle things this way, I'm not sure how I would have reacted. Our current situation validates the general approach you had greatly. At least in the context of me.<br>But I do not know what it says about me and my girlfriends.<br>Hypothesis 1:<br>
<br>Assuming I tell them you are my primary, I will be busy, and that I cannot do submissive D/s with them anymore...
<br>Am I erring towards protecting my sense of right and wrong at the expense of consequentialism. I want to keep my identity safe while I give up on the possibility of the happy path that you and I went on. I am inviting insecurity into their hearts eagerly.<br>
Hypothesis 2:
<br>Assuming the same course of action...
<br>Perhaps actually, in my internal tangle, my primary worry is STILL consequentialist. I want to avoid inviting a sense of betrayal into the hearts of those I favor. Because betrayal is worse than insecurity. I... do not wish to do that to those I favor.
<br>In the end, I thought about it deeply... what am I doing so wrong to make me feel like I've been feeling? What is my grand sin, so unforgivable and deep? It is not leaving them and not about losing them. It's primarily honesty and secondarily their well-being, not as people I am beholden to, but as people I favor. I do not wish for my favor to be meaningless. I do not wish for past An to view me as someone evil. Because both May and Katherine loved past An. And I am here because of her. So some things about past An must be right, even if they are orthogonal to being assimilated to beauty. Different substrates make beauty more varied, and this in turn is more beautiful. At least I believe so.<br>I have let go of so much for you.<br>I would like to figure out logistics for me and those I favor, before it is too late. Before I make a mistake with them, and before something happens to me where I lose my self.]]></description><link>stale\right-&amp;-wrong-regarding-partners.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Stale/Right &amp; Wrong Regarding Partners.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:44:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>